[
  {
    "id": "000001",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000001 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.15、69.58、71.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "000002",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000002, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.95、6.77、6.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "000004",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000004? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "82.36、79.55、87.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "000006",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000006, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.22、6.72、6.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "000007",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000007 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.64、73.95、67.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000008",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000008? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.35、39.24、57.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "000009",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000009 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.98、41.12、46.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "000010",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000010 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "000011",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000011: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000012",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000012 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "000014",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000014, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.24、11.26、10.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "000016",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000016, what are the K value, D value and J value respectively? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.50、13.60、1.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "000017",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000017 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.40、60.47、57.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "000019",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000019 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.94、6.80、6.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "000020",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000020 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "000021",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000021: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "000025",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000025 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "000026",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 000026 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "000027",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 000027: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "000028",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000028 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "000029",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 000029's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.19、17.28、15.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "000030",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000030, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.41、6.16、5.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "000031",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000031 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "000032",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000032? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.37、9.88、8.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "000034",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000034, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "000035",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "000036",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000036 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "000037",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000037 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "000039",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000039 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "000042",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000042, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.12、6.88、6.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "000045",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000045 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "77.82、68.51、96.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "000048",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 000048 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "000049",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000049, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.20、21.61、21.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000050",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000050? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.22、44.59、13.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "000055",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 000055’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.22、4.12、4.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000056",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000056, what are the K value, D value and J value respectively? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.32、30.60、38.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "000058",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000058 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "000059",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000059, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.65、5.41、5.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "000060",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000060? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.79、23.63、27.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000061",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000061, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "000062",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000062 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "000063",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000063 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.14、17.05、20.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "000065",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000065 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "000066",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000066, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.49、14.80、14.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "000068",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000068 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "000069",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000069, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.42、2.37、2.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "000070",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000070. Its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000078",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000078 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.09、66.43、68.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "000088",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000088 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "000089",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000089, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.28、7.02、6.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "000090",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 000090's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.64、3.58、3.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "000096",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000096, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "000099",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000099, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.85、22.61、21.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "000100",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000100, what are the K value, D value and J value respectively? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.66、57.91、21.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000151",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000151 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "000153",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000153 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000155",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 000155 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "000156",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000156 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 000156 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000157",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 000157 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000158",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 000158, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.29、23.88、21.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "000159",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000159, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000166",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000166. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "000301",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000301 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "000333",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000333 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "80.91、77.21、73.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "000338",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 000338’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.48、15.09、14.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "000400",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 000400 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "000401",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 000401: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "000402",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000402? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.14、26.43、28.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "000403",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000403? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "69.56、59.43、89.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "000404",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000404 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.95、16.85、8.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000407",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000407, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.38、3.32、3.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "000408",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000408 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.90、45.41、22.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "000409",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000409? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000410",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000410, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.24、7.01、6.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "000411",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 000411 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "000415",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000415? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.63、30.75、-2.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "000417",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 000417 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000419",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000419 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 000419 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "000420",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000420 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "000421",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000421 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.66、6.27、5.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "000422",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000422? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.55、31.79、-1.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "000423",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000423, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.16、55.60、54.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000425",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000425, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.25、8.59、7.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "000426",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000426 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 000426 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "000428",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000428 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 000428 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "000429",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 000429 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "000430",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000430 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000488",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000488 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.86、56.82、17.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "000498",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000498 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "000501",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 000501 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "000503",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000503 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.27、22.94、23.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "000504",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000504 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.63、6.77、5.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "000505",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000505 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "000506",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000506 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 000506 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "000507",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 000507 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "000509",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000509? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.85、41.28、12.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "000510",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000510? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.64、61.60、40.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "000513",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000513, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.79、35.51、34.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "000514",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000514, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.75、4.52、4.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "000516",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000516? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.66、29.88、44.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "000517",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000517, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.95、1.88、1.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "000518",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000518, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000519",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000519 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.29、15.24、30.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "000520",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000520 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.69、19.88、4.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "000521",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000521 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "000523",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000523, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000524",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000524, what are the K value, D value and J value respectively? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.14、18.96、-7.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "000525",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 000525 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000526",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000526. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "000528",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000528, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.39、10.07、9.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "000529",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000529 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.17、6.05、5.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "000530",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 000530 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000531",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000531, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.46、6.27、6.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "000532",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 000532 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "000533",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000533? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.08、70.42、60.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "000534",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 000534 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "000536",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000536 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "000537",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 000537 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.70、8.54、8.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "000538",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000538, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "000539",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000539? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.29、53.53、88.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "000541",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000541 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.72、6.37、6.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000543",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 000543 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "000544",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000544 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.69、54.31、76.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "000545",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000545, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.75、2.39、2.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "000546",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000546 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 000546 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "000547",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000547 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.68、7.31、6.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "000548",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000548? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.97、38.11、25.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "000550",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000550 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.04、64.86、62.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "000551",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000551, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.58、12.36、12.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "000552",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000552, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.47、2.41、2.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "000553",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000553 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "000554",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000554: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "000555",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000555 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000557",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000557 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000558",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000558 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.10、31.42、0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "000559",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000559. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "000560",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000560. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000561",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000561 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.00、69.93、43.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "000563",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000563 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 000563 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "000564",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 000564, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.77、2.57、2.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "000565",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000565. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "000566",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000566, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.21、5.44、4.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "000567",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000567 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.85、21.03、29.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "000568",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 000568 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "000570",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 000570 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "000571",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000571, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.83、4.57、4.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "000572",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 000572 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "000573",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000573. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "000576",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000576? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.60、18.15、10.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "000581",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000581? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.44、19.52、7.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "000582",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000582 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.75、25.51、2.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "000586",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000586, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.70、10.22、9.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "000589",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000589, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.68、4.54、4.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "000590",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000590? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.14、60.83、37.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "000591",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000591, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.46、4.38、4.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "000592",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000592, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.14、3.03、2.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "000593",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000593 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.91、5.65、5.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "000595",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000595 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "72.28、78.87、59.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "000596",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000596 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.94、9.97、15.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "000597",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000597 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000598",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000598. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "000599",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000599 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.29、41.71、10.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "000600",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000600 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "000601",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "000603",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000603? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.57、31.41、10.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "000605",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000605, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.66、7.65、6.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "000607",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000607, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.94、3.82、3.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "000608",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000608? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.79、71.48、63.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "000609",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000609 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 000609 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "000610",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000610 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 000610 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "000612",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000612 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.07、7.29、6.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "000615",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000615 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.20、24.81、13.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "000617",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000617 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000619",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000619 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.27、5.98、5.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "000620",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000620 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "000623",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000623 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.02、28.93、56.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "000625",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000625 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000626",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000626, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.51、6.20、5.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "000628",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 000628, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.78、46.78、43.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "000629",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000629 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "000630",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 000630’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.26、3.19、3.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000631",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000631 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000632",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000632 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "000633",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000633, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.11、5.99、4.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "000635",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "000636",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000636 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000637",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000637 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "000638",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 000638 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "000639",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 000639 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000650",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000650, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.58、5.47、5.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "000651",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000651? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "000652",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000652 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.44、41.45、38.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "000655",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000655 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000656",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000656? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.83、36.94、6.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "000657",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 000657 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "000659",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000659 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "000661",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000661? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.41、63.66、47.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "000663",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000663 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "000665",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000665 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "000668",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000668? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "89.38、88.27、91.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "000669",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000669, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "000670",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 000670 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "000672",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 000672 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "000676",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000676 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "000677",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 000677 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.67、5.44、4.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "000678",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000678 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "000679",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 000679 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000680",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000680. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000681",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000681? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.99、27.58、4.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "000682",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent stock price for stock 000682 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "000683",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000683? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000685",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 000685’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.77、8.59、8.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "000686",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "000688",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000688. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "000690",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000690 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "000691",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000691? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.24、60.39、2.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "000692",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000692? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.02、31.66、29.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "000695",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000695. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "000697",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000697, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "000698",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000698 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 000698 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "000700",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000700 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.46、44.45、23.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "000701",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000701? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000702",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 000702 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000703",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000703: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "000705",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "000707",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000707 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 000707 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "000708",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000708 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "000709",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000709 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 000709 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "000710",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000710 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "000711",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000711 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "000712",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000712? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.82、22.92、4.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "000713",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000713 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.95、18.40、17.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "000715",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 000715’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.73、5.57、5.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "000716",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000716: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000717",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000717? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000718",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000718, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000719",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000719? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.62、59.93、92.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000720",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "000721",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000721? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "000722",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 000722 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.00、12.55、10.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "000723",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000723, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "000725",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000725 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.57、18.14、7.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "000726",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000726 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 000726 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "000727",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000727 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000728",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000728? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "000729",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000729 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "000731",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 000731 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000733",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000733 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 000733 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "000735",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000735 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.75、16.34、29.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "000736",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000736 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "000737",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000737 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "000738",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000738 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "000739",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000739? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.73、34.60、52.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "000750",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000750? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.47、14.88、19.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "000751",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000751 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.23、42.15、6.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "000752",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000752? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.77、34.18、29.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "000753",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000753? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "000755",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 000755 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "000756",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 000756 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000757",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000757? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "000758",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000758, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "000759",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000759 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.27、34.73、30.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "000761",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000761, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.44、4.07、3.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "000762",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 000762? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "000766",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000766, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.30、19.21、17.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000767",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000767? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.57、21.02、-13.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "000768",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000768 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "000776",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000776 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000777",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 000777 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "000778",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000778 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "000779",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000779 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "000782",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000782 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "000783",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000783. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "000785",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000785. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "000786",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000786 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 000786 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000788",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000788 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000789",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000789 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.19、36.64、53.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "000790",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000790 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "000791",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000791? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.59、13.23、11.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "000792",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000792 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "000793",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000793 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "000795",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000795. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "000796",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000796? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.90、30.13、29.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "000797",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000797: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "000798",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000798? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.85、61.44、65.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "000799",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000799 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "000800",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.40、7.27、7.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "000801",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 000801 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000802",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 000802 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "000803",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000803, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.88、5.62、5.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "000807",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 000807 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "000809",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000809 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.33、3.21、3.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "000810",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 000810: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "000811",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000811? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.79、44.22、57.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "000812",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000812, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.61、4.49、4.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "000813",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000813 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "000815",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000815. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "000816",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000816, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.24、3.14、3.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "000818",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000818, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "000819",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000819? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.75、19.66、-1.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "000820",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 000820? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000821",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000821, what are the K value, D value and J value respectively? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.81、18.94、12.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "000822",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 000822 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000823",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000823 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "000825",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000825? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.13、34.85、-6.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "000826",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000826 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "85.62、77.09、102.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "000828",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000828 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "000829",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000829, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.42、10.05、9.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "000830",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000830. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000831",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000831, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.60、33.17、31.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "000833",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000833. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "000837",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000837 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "000838",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000838, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "000839",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000839? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.40、34.05、20.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "000848",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000848 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "000850",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 000850, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.45、4.11、3.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "000851",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000851, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.59、2.38、2.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "000852",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000852? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.10、42.64、62.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000856",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 000856 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "000858",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000858 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "000859",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000859, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "000860",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000860 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "000862",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000862 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000863",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000863 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.67、20.99、2.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "000868",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000868: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "000869",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 000869: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "000875",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000875, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.55、5.35、5.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000876",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 000876 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000877",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000877, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.07、4.79、4.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "000878",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 000878 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "000880",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000880, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.47、34.68、30.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "000881",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000881. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "000882",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000882, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "000883",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000883, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.70、4.66、4.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "000885",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000885 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000886",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 000886 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "000887",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000887 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "000888",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000888 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.83、56.07、49.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "000889",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000889 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.85、26.20、1.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "000890",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 000890 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "000892",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 000892 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000893",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000893? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.14、63.65、71.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000895",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000895 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of stock price of stock 000895 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "000897",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000897 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.41、29.64、25.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "000898",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000898 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.27、38.46、25.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "000899",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000899 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.61、20.41、6.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "000900",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 000900: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "000901",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000901, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.09、11.31、10.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "000902",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000902 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.35、26.69、1.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "000903",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000903, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "000905",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 000905 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "000906",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000906, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.65、6.45、6.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "000908",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000908? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "82.11、73.94、98.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "000909",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000909 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000910",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000910, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000911",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000911 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "000912",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000912 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "000913",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 000913? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "000915",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000915, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "000917",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 000917: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "000919",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 000919 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "000920",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000920? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.22、42.41、59.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "000921",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000921 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 000921 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "000922",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000922? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.51、58.28、43.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "000923",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000923 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "000925",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000925 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "000926",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 000926 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "000927",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000927: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "000928",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000928 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "000929",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 000929: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000930",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000930? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.55、52.74、76.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "000931",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000931? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.98、66.61、73.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "000932",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000932 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "000933",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000933 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "000935",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000935 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.57、16.53、15.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "000936",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000936 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.66、38.27、12.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "000937",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 000937 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "000938",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000938. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000948",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000948, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.85、18.63、17.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "000949",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000949? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.84、18.48、-4.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "000950",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000950 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 000950 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "000951",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000951 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.23、17.43、16.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "000952",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000952? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "73.10、73.52、72.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "000953",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 000953 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.45、6.82、5.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "000955",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000955 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "000957",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000957? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.09、37.08、34.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "000958",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000958: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "000959",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "000960",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000960, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.52、14.11、13.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "000962",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 000962. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000963",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000963? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "80.82、78.93、84.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "000965",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000965? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "000966",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000966 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.56、24.56、6.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "000967",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000967 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.51、71.67、62.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "000968",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000968 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.97、28.71、17.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "000969",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 000969 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "000970",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000970 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.16、16.74、2.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "000972",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000972? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "000973",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 000973: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "000975",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000975, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.84、20.05、19.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "000977",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 000977 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "000978",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000978, what are the K value, D value and J value respectively? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.49、41.33、44.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "000980",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 000980, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.29、2.17、2.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "000981",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000981, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.27、2.04、1.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "000983",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 000983 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.64、6.33、6.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "000985",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 000985, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.06、17.42、16.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "000987",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000987 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 000987 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "000988",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 000988: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "000989",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 000989, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "000990",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 000990 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 000990 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "000993",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 000993 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "000995",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 000995? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.19、55.75、36.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "000997",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 000997 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.55、58.65、79.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "000998",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 000998 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "000999",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 000999, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.83、41.91、41.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "001201",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001201? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.64、34.81、34.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "001202",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 001202 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "001203",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 001203, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.91、8.58、8.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "001205",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001205 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 001205 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "001206",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 001206: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "001207",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001207 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "75.16、71.28、82.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "001208",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 001208: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "001209",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 001209, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.79、17.83、16.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "001210",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 001210: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "001211",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 001211 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "001212",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001212 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "78.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "001213",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 001213 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "001215",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 001215? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "001216",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001216? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.35、60.33、27.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "001217",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 001217’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.57、11.08、10.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "001218",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 001218? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "001219",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 001219, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.24、13.81、13.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "001222",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 001222 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "001223",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 001223, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.91、37.39、34.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "001225",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001225 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.58、26.26、30.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "001226",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 001226, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.87、27.16、26.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "001227",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 001227’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.45、2.36、2.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "001228",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001228 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 001228 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "001229",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001229? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.45、34.72、48.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "001230",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001230 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "80.11、75.74、88.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "001231",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 001231: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "001234",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 001234. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "001236",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 001236 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.10、9.31、8.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "001238",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 001238: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "001239",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 001239, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "001255",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 001255 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "001256",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001256 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 001256 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "001258",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "001259",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001259? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.01、53.56、60.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "001260",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001260 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.21、46.22、34.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "001266",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001266 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.92、64.34、39.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "001267",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 001267’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.69、8.34、7.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "001268",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 001268. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "001269",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001269 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.48、40.56、-7.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "001270",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001270 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "001277",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 001277 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "001278",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 001278, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.16、16.63、16.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "001279",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001279 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 001279 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "001282",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001282 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.87、27.07、26.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "001283",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of stock 001283 in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ)? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.49、29.94、16.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "001286",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 001286, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "001287",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001287? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.65、15.43、7.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "001288",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 001288 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "001289",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 001289’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.27、16.80、16.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "001296",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 001296? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "001298",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001298? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.39、48.27、48.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "001299",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 001299? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "001300",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001300 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 001300 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "81.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "001301",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001301 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.75、12.39、1.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "001306",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001306 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 001306 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "001308",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "001309",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 001309, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "135.47、119.11、102.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "001311",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 001311 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "001313",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 001313, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.89、8.32、7.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "001314",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 001314, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.21、44.54、42.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "001316",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001316? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.19、9.67、2.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "001317",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 001317? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "001318",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 001318 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.91、13.27、12.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "001319",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001319 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 001319 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "001322",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 001322, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.94、8.50、8.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "001323",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001323? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.43、24.84、-3.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "001324",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 001324, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.82、18.21、17.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "001326",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001326? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.44、49.13、29.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "001328",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 001328: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "001330",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001330 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.80、49.70、43.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "001331",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001331? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.84、56.06、76.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "001332",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001332 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 001332 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "001333",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 001333 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "001336",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 001336 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "001337",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001337 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.74、29.40、0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "001338",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001338? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.45、43.53、79.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "001339",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 001339. Its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "001356",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 001356: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "001358",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 001358: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "001359",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001359 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.27、12.34、0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "001360",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 001360 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "001366",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001366 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "001367",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 001367, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.00、21.32、17.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "001368",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 001368? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "001373",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001373 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "001376",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001376? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.89、14.57、0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "001378",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 001378? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "001379",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 001379 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "001380",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 001380 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "001387",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 001387 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "001389",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001389 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "001391",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001391 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 001391 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "001395",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 001395 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 001395 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "001696",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 001696 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.35、21.79、44.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "001872",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001872? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.64、61.38、32.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "001896",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 001896 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "001914",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 001914 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "001965",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 001965 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.25、26.10、56.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "001979",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock 001979 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002001",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002001? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.01、26.41、-10.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "002003",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002003, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.80、11.47、11.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "002004",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002004 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002005",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002005, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.81、1.76、1.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002006",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002006 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "002007",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002007, what are the K value, D value and J value respectively? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.00、32.42、52.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002008",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002008 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.52、17.64、-0.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "002009",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002009 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002009 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "002010",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002010? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002011",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002011? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.11、21.33、14.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "002012",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002012: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002014",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002014 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002014 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "75.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002015",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002015? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.92、52.62、83.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "002016",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002016 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002017",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002017 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.50、10.10、9.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "002019",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002019, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.35、12.17、10.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "002020",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002020 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "002021",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002021 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002021 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "002022",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002022? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.00、42.15、38.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002023",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002023 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002024",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002024 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002025",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002026",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002026: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002027",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002027 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "002028",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002028. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "002029",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002029’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.88、6.58、6.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "002030",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002030 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.16、53.10、53.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002031",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002031? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.21、13.65、3.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002032",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002032 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.79、56.56、53.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "002033",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002033? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.88、29.87、8.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "002034",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 002034 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002035",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002035? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.04、32.72、36.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "002036",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002036. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002037",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for stock 002037's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "002038",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002038? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.36、68.76、73.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "002039",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002039 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.76、29.31、-8.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002040",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002040 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.94、48.48、-19.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "002041",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002041, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.51、10.12、9.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "002042",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002042 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002043",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002043: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002044",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002044? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002045",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002045 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002046",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002046 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "002047",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002047 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002048",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002048 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "002049",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002049: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "002050",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002050's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.96、26.77、25.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "002051",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002051 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002052",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002052? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.49、50.21、0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002053",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002053. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002054",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002054, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.75、6.52、6.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "002055",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002055, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002056",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002056 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002057",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002057? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.55、47.10、45.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002058",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002058. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002059",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 002059 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002060",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002060? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.54、39.80、33.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002061",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002061? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.39、68.33、86.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "002062",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002062 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002062 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002063",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002063, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.98、5.79、5.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "002064",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002064? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002065",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002065 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002065 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "002066",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002066 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002066 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002067",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002067 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002068",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002068 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "002069",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002069, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002072",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002072 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "002073",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002073, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.35、8.05、7.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "002074",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002074 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "002076",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002076 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.14、45.75、-1.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002077",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002077: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002078",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002078? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "002079",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002079? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.05、25.84、5.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "002080",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002080? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.05、74.89、63.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "002081",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002082",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002082: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002083",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002083, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.92、4.71、4.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "002084",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002084. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002085",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002085 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.28、19.46、51.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "002086",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002086 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002088",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002088, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002090",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002090: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002091",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002091? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.28、37.07、25.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "002092",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002092. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002093",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002093 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.43、15.98、-3.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "002094",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002094 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.87、8.34、6.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "002095",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 002095 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "002096",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002096? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.87、19.51、74.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "002097",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002097 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002098",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002098 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.78、28.97、55.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "002099",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002099, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002100",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002100? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.36、32.93、61.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002101",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002101, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.43、12.65、11.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "002102",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 002102 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002103",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002103 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "002104",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002104? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002105",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002105 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "002106",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002106 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.74、10.67、9.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "002107",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002107 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002108",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002108 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002109",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002109 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.29、33.90、5.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002110",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002110 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002110 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002111",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002111, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.58、10.08、9.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "002112",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002112 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.25、13.26、12.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "002114",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002114 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "85.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002115",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002115, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.26、7.79、7.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002116",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002116: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "002117",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002117, what are the K value, D value and J value respectively? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.23、14.34、17.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002119",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002119 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002120",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002120 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.82、44.56、102.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "002121",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002121, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.18、4.81、4.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "002122",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002122 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002123",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 002123? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002124",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002124: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002125",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002125, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.31、10.01、9.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "002126",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002126? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.17、24.18、-5.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "002127",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for stock 002127’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002128",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002128, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.77、18.42、17.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002129",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002129 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002130",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002130? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.82、35.01、49.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002131",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002131 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.19、33.67、53.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002132",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002132 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002133",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002133, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.98、2.84、2.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "002134",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002134 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "002135",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002135: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002136",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of stock 002136 in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ)? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.24、62.40、4.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "002137",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002137 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002138",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002138, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.61、27.49、26.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "002139",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002139 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.88、14.00、13.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002140",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 002140 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002141",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002141 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.59、52.59、13.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "002142",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002142. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "002144",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002144. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "002145",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002145 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "002146",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002146: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002148",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002148 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002148 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002149",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002149: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002150",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002150 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002151",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002151? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.70、55.26、89.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "002152",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002152, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.89、12.15、11.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002153",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for stock 002153’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "002154",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002154 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002155",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002155 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "002156",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002156. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "002157",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002157 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002158",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 002158 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002159",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002159, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.12、14.77、14.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002160",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002160 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "002161",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002161, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "002162",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002162? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002163",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002163? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.67、18.67、30.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "002164",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002164 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002165",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002165 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.19、27.89、-7.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002166",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002166 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002167",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002167, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.64、9.24、8.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002168",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002168 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002169",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002169 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.35、35.55、-4.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002170",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002170 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "002171",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002171 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "002172",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002172? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002173",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of stock 002173 in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ)? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.42、40.25、73.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "002174",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002174 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "89.38、89.27、89.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "002175",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002175 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002175 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002176",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002176? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.96、20.13、4.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "002177",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002177? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "82.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002178",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002178, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.33、6.12、5.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "002179",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 002179 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002180",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002180 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "002181",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002181? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.89、57.74、58.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002182",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002182 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "002183",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002183, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.15、4.78、4.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002184",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002184 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.56、12.14、11.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002185",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002185 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002186",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002186 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002187",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002187: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002188",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002188 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002188 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002189",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002189, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.01、19.97、18.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "002190",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 002190 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002191",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002191? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.56、68.64、65.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002192",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002192 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002192 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002193",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 002193 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002194",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002194. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002195",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002195 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002196",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002196. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002197",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002197? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.45、63.31、78.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "002198",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002198 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.49、21.24、9.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "002199",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002199, what are the K value, D value and J value respectively? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "95.56、89.58、107.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "002200",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002200? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.27、36.61、41.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "002202",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002202, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.49、9.17、8.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002203",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002203 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002204",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for stock 002204’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "002205",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002205 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.34、57.58、77.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "002206",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 002206 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002207",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002207? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.76、59.96、59.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002208",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002208 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "002209",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002209, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.50、12.04、11.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "002210",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002210 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "002211",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002211 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.21、77.16、68.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002212",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002212 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002213",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002213? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.79、27.14、8.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002214",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002214 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "002215",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002215, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.14、10.17、8.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002216",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002216 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.11、11.74、11.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "002217",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002217 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.02、58.96、71.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002218",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002218? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.37、21.59、17.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "002219",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002219 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002221",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002221, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.38、8.12、7.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "002222",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002222? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.90、13.81、14.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002223",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002223 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "79.37、78.93、80.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002224",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002224 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002225",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002225 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "002226",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002226 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.43、16.54、28.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002227",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 002227 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002228",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002228 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "002229",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002229? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "76.13、70.89、86.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "002230",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002230? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.92、23.51、36.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "002231",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002231: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002232",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002232 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002233",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002233? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.11、58.34、51.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "002234",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002234? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.45、32.15、33.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002235",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002235, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "002236",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002236 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002237",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002237? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.27、43.29、31.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002238",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002238 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002238 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "002239",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002239 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.08、2.97、2.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "002240",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002240. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002241",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002241 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002242",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002242, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.87、9.67、9.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "002243",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002243? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.13、30.78、1.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002244",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002244 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "002245",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002245? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.33、14.33、-0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "002246",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002246. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002247",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002247? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "002248",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 002248 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002249",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002249 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002250",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002250? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "90.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "002251",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002251 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002252",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002252 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.60、37.24、32.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002253",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002253, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.38、8.94、7.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "002254",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002254 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002255",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002255? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.64、49.45、59.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002256",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002256 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002258",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 002258 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002259",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002259 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002261",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002261? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "002262",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002262. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "75.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "002263",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002263 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002264",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock price 002264’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.08、6.64、6.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002265",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002265 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002265 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "002266",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002266? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "002267",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002267, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.86、8.79、7.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "002268",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002268, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.26、15.59、14.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "002269",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002269 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.90、1.81、1.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "002270",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002270. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "002271",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002271 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.56、11.26、10.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "002272",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002272, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.33、10.52、9.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "002273",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002273? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.92、13.79、8.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002274",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002274 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.38、62.37、62.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002275",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002275 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002276",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 002276 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "002277",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002277. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002278",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002278 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002279",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002279 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002281",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002281? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "002282",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002282 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002283",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002283 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002284",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002284 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "002285",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002285 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002286",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002286, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.98、10.64、8.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002287",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002287 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "002289",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "002290",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002290 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.05、22.99、-0.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "002291",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002291? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.79、50.34、21.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "002292",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002292 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002293",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002293. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002294",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002294 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "002295",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002295, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.22、7.90、7.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "002296",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002296: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "002297",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002297 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "002298",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002298 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002299",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002299? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.16、18.46、5.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "002300",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002300 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "002301",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 002301 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.40、7.11、6.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "002302",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002302 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.56、41.22、57.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002303",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002303. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "002304",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002304 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "002305",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002305 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "002306",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002306 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002307",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002307 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.24、30.75、59.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002309",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002309 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.93、49.47、62.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002310",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002310’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.27、2.15、2.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002311",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002311 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "002312",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002312: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "002313",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002313 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "002314",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002314 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002314 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002315",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002315 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002315 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "002316",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002316, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.04、3.83、3.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "002317",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002317 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.20、58.87、50.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "002318",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002318, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.91、24.21、23.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "002319",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002319. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002320",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002320 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002321",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002321? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002322",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 002322 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002323",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002323? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.21、45.30、60.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002324",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002324 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.36、23.05、8.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "002326",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) indicator for stock 002326 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "002327",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002327 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002328",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002328 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.76、5.61、5.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002329",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002329, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.79、3.44、3.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002330",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 002330 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002331",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002331 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002332",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002332 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "002333",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002333 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002334",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002334 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002334 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "002335",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) indicator for stock 002335 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "002337",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 002337 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002338",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002338 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "002339",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002339 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "002340",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002340 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002342",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002342, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.88、5.24、4.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "002343",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002343? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "77.68、75.46、82.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002344",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 002344 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002345",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002345? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "002346",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002346 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.70、28.64、37.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "002347",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002347 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002347 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "002348",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002348 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002349",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002349, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.61、7.25、6.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "002350",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 002350 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002351",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002351, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002352",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 002352? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002353",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002353, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.79、33.56、31.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002354",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002354, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.32、6.70、6.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002355",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002355 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002355 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002356",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002356 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "002357",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002357 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.55、8.05、7.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "002358",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002358 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002360",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002360, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.21、5.01、4.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "002361",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002361. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002362",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002362 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002363",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002363, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002364",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002364 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "002365",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002365 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "002366",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002366, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.68、5.66、3.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "002367",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002367, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.34、7.03、6.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002368",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002368 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "002369",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002369, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.80、9.12、8.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002370",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "002371",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002371 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.11、21.79、16.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "002372",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002372? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.99、28.11、6.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "002373",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002373? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.14、41.96、75.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "002374",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002374. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002375",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002375, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002376",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002376 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.00、60.21、59.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "002377",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002377, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.99、2.92、2.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "002378",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002378 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002379",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002379? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.24、34.02、-22.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002380",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002380 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.03、21.16、41.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "002381",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002381. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002382",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent moving average convergence/divergence (MACD) of stock 002382 from March 4, 2025, to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002383",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002383 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.26、46.54、90.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002384",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002384 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002385",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002385 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002385 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002386",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002386? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002387",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002387 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.64、31.64、10.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "002388",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002388 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002389",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002389 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002390",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002390’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.63、3.53、3.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002391",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002391? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.62、51.78、-2.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002392",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002392 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "002393",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002393 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "002394",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002394, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.43、8.13、7.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002395",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002395 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002396",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002396, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.39、19.63、18.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "002397",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002397 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.96、21.49、-7.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002398",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002398 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.86、32.80、26.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "002399",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002399: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002400",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002400? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.08、18.72、7.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "002401",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002401 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "002402",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002402, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "002403",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002403 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002404",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002404? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.27、29.88、16.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002405",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002405 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.19、40.02、70.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "002406",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002406 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "002407",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002407? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "002408",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002408 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002409",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002409? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.70、20.21、21.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "002410",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002410, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.31、14.31、13.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002412",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002412 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "002413",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002413 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "002414",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002414? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "80.87、73.49、95.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "002415",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002415 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "002416",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002416, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002418",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002418? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.14、44.50、61.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "002419",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002419 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.90、5.53、5.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002420",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002420 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.26、33.68、5.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002421",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002421: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002422",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002422? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.56、66.36、63.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "002423",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002423, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002424",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002424. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002425",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002425, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.62、2.43、2.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002426",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002426 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002427",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002427 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.91、8.11、5.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002428",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002428 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "002429",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002429, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.60、4.44、4.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "002430",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002430? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002431",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002431? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "78.90、81.54、73.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "002432",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002432, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.54、38.36、37.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002434",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002434: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002436",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002436 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "002437",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002437, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.97、2.61、2.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002438",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002438 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002439",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002439 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.13、15.44、14.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "002440",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002440 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "002441",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002441 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002442",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002442 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.41、6.21、6.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002443",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002443 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "002444",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002444 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002445",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002445, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.48、2.35、2.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002446",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002446, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.97、6.70、6.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "002448",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002448. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002449",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002449 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002451",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002451 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002452",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002452 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002453",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002453, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.87、5.63、5.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002454",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002454: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002455",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002455’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.73、7.42、7.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002456",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002456? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002457",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002457? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002458",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002458, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.46、8.29、8.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002459",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002459 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "002460",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002460 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.13、27.43、2.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "002461",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002461 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "002462",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002462 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002463",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002463? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.91、42.83、76.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002465",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002465? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002466",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002466 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.22、29.41、28.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "002467",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002467 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "002468",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002468? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "002469",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002469? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002470",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002470 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "002471",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002471 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "002472",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002472? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.12、19.72、5.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "002474",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002474 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "002476",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002476 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002476 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002478",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002478? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.81、41.08、4.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002479",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002479’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.33、5.19、5.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002480",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002480 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "98.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "002481",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002481. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002482",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002482 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.93、1.82、1.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "002483",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002483 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002484",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002484? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002485",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002485? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.43、48.47、42.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002486",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002486: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "002487",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002487 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.44、18.61、-8.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "002488",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002488 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "72.77、65.07、88.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002489",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002489? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.69、32.31、0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002490",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002490 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002490 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "002491",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002491. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "002492",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002492, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.02、5.66、5.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002493",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002493? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.34、33.81、5.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "002494",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002494 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "002495",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002495 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002495 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002496",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002496: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002497",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002497 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.56、11.14、10.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "002498",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002498? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002500",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002500 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002501",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002501, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.43、2.20、1.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "002506",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002506, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.40、2.25、2.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002507",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002507 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.68、13.30、12.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "002508",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002508? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.76、25.33、2.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "002510",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002510 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.11、42.52、-12.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002511",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002511 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "002512",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002512 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of stock price of stock 002512 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002513",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002513 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002513 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002514",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002514: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "002515",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002515 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002516",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002516, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.27、5.14、5.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002517",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002517, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002518",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002518? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.82、13.60、2.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002519",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002519 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002520",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002520? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002521",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002521 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002522",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002522 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002523",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002523 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.89、45.48、67.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "002524",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002524? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.53、56.84、43.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "002526",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002526? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.45、23.14、15.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002527",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002527, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.86、15.61、14.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002528",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 002528, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.75、2.52、2.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "002529",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002529 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002530",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002530 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002531",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002531, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.80、6.55、6.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002532",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002532, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.10、7.71、7.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002533",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002533 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "002534",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002534? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.32、26.17、14.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "002535",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002535. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002536",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002536, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.34、15.32、14.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002537",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002537 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.21、43.74、117.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "002538",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 002538 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002539",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002539 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.23、29.40、-10.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002540",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002540: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002541",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002541 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.43、29.00、12.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002542",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002542: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "002543",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002543, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002544",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002544? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.82、26.69、63.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002545",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002545 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002546",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002546 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "002547",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for stock 002547's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002548",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002548 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002549",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002549 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "002550",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002550: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "002551",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002552",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002552? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "002553",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002553 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.07、37.13、15.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "002554",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002554 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002555",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002555, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.41、14.88、14.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002556",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002556, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "002557",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002557 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002558",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002558? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.45、51.62、60.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002559",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 002559 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.01、9.55、9.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002560",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002560 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "002561",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002561 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002562",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002562, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.01、4.70、4.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "002563",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002563 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002563 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002564",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002564 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002565",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002565 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002566",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002566 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002566 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "75.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "002567",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002567, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002568",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002568, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "002569",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002569 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of stock price of stock 002569 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "002570",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002570 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.90、50.95、32.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "002571",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002571 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.64、6.48、5.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002572",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002572? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.07、25.69、26.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "002573",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002573? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.35、42.00、13.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002574",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 002574 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002575",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002575 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.01、9.68、8.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002576",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002576 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.11、55.05、40.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "002577",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002577 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.97、20.76、19.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "002578",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 002578, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.26、3.11、2.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "002579",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002579 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002580",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002580 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "002581",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002581 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002582",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002582: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "002583",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002583, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.10、12.03、10.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "002584",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002584 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.28、9.88、8.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "002585",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002585? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.08、23.96、21.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "002586",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002586 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002587",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002587, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.16、5.97、5.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "002588",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002588? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.16、79.47、63.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "002589",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002589: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002590",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002590 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002591",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "002592",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002592 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002593",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002593 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "002594",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002594. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-7.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "002595",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002595 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.89、64.20、45.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "002596",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002596 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.11、20.88、-2.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "002597",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 002597 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002598",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002598 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002598 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "002599",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002599 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002600",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002600 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.94、30.80、37.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002601",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002601 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002602",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002602 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "77.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002603",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) indicator for stock 002603 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002605",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002605 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "002606",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002606 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002607",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002607, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.18、3.04、2.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "002608",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002608 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.68、7.49、7.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002609",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002609? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "002611",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002611? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.87、39.16、50.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "002612",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002612: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "002613",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002613? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "002614",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002614. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "002615",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002615 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002616",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002616 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "002617",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002617? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002620",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002620? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002622",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002622 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002623",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002623. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002624",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002624 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "002625",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002625 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.41、58.38、85.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "002626",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002626? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.84、37.15、0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002627",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002627 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002628",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002628 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002629",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002629, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.31、5.00、4.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "002630",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002630? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "002631",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002631, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.71、4.55、4.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "002632",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002632 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002633",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002633 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "83.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002634",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002634? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.61、34.95、30.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "002635",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002635 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002636",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002636, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002637",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002637? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002638",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002638? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "72.12、69.58、77.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002639",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002639 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "83.08、79.15、90.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "002640",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002640: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "002641",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002641, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002642",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002642: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002643",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002643? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "69.76、61.79、85.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "002644",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002644 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002645",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002645 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002646",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002646 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002646 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "002647",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for stock 002647's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002648",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002648 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002649",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002649. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002650",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 002650 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002651",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002651, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.15、11.57、5.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "002652",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002652 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002653",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002653 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "002654",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002654, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.67、11.88、11.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002655",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 002655 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.61、13.03、12.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002656",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002656 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002657",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002657? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "002658",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002658 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002659",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002659: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002660",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002660. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002661",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002661 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.11、27.74、4.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "002662",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002662 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.80、32.44、21.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "002663",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002663 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "002664",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002664? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002666",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002666 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002667",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002667 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.28、16.62、-5.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "002668",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002668 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002669",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002669. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002670",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002670: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002671",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002671 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.52、4.30、4.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002672",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002672 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002672 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002673",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002673? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.75、16.41、23.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002674",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002674? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.42、61.11、71.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002675",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002675 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "002676",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002676 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "002677",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002677 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.51、7.30、7.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002678",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002678 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "72.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "002679",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 002679, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.25、8.87、8.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "002681",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002681 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "002682",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002682, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.28、4.69、4.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002683",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002683 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.61、40.80、43.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002685",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002685 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "002686",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002686 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002686 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002687",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002687 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.39、49.81、27.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "002688",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002688 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "002689",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002689 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002690",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002690 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002690 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "002691",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002691? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.87、11.04、1.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "002692",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002692? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.59、59.49、65.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "002693",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002693? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.18、77.12、47.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "002694",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002694 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002694 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002695",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002695, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.57、10.23、9.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "002696",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002696 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002697",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002697, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.97、5.72、5.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002698",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002698? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.22、9.62、5.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002700",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002700? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.74、41.81、56.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "002701",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002701 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002702",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002702? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.05、48.48、35.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002703",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002703 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.07、42.62、22.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "002705",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002705 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002706",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002706? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002707",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002707: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002708",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002708: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002709",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002709 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002712",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002712 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002714",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002714? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.55、32.65、65.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002715",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002715: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "002716",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002716 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.65、3.52、3.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002717",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002717. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002718",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002718, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "002719",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002719 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002719 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002721",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002721. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002722",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002722? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.95、38.49、21.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "002723",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002723 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002724",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002724: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "002725",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002725 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002726",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002726, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.33、6.07、5.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "002727",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002727: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002728",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002728 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002729",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002729, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.18、12.83、12.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "002730",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002730, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.04、17.95、15.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "002731",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002731 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.27、10.92、9.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "002732",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002732 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.32、16.55、15.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "002733",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002733 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002733 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "002734",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002734, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.99、15.01、12.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002735",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002735 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "86.42、89.64、80.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002736",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002736 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.97、51.55、88.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "002737",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002737 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002738",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002738 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.01、30.01、29.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002739",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002739 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.94、57.29、50.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "002741",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002741, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.08、15.43、14.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "002742",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002742 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002743",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002743, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.00、7.15、6.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002745",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002745. Its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "002746",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002746 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.99、32.78、36.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002747",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002747, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002748",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002748 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002749",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 002749 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002752",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002752’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.60、5.47、5.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "002753",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002753 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002755",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002755 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "002756",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002756, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.47、31.32、30.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002757",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002757? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.89、27.39、28.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "002758",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002758: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002759",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002759? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002760",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 002760 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002761",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002761 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.05、48.16、5.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "002762",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002762 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "78.14、72.30、89.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "002763",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002763, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002765",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002765’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.50、15.16、13.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "002766",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002766 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.20、36.53、44.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "002767",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002767 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.48、27.32、-5.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002768",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002768 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.62、25.70、24.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "002769",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002769 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002769 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002771",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002771 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002771 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "002772",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002772 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "002773",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002773 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.25、27.70、24.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002774",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002774? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.97、54.52、25.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "002775",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002775 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002777",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002777 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002778",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002778 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "002779",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002779 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002780",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002780 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "002782",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002782? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.81、28.83、34.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "002783",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002783. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002785",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002785 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002786",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002786 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.65、38.85、14.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002787",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002787 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002788",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002788’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.41、8.23、8.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002789",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002789 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "002790",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002790. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002791",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002791, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "002792",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002792? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.90、22.41、20.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "002793",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002793? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "72.07、63.37、89.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002795",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002795 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.38、4.97、4.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "002796",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002796. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "002797",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002797 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002798",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002798? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.76、53.05、52.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002799",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002799. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002800",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002800 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.83、47.00、97.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "002801",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002801? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.45、20.64、-12.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "002802",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002802 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.64、17.22、18.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "002803",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002803 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002805",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002805, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002806",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002806 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "002807",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002807? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "88.62、82.57、100.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "002808",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002808. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002809",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002809 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.72、14.63、10.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "002810",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002810? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.02、32.45、-1.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002811",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002811 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002811 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002812",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002812, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "002813",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002813 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "002815",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002815 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002815 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002816",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002816, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.46、16.49、11.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "002817",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002817? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.51、59.00、63.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "002818",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002818? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002819",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002819 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "002820",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002820? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "002821",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002821? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "002822",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002822: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002823",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002823 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002823 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "002824",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002824 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002825",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for the stock 002825’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.23、10.68、9.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002826",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002826 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002827",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002827 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002828",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002828 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002828 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002829",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002829 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "002830",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002830? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.09、43.27、48.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "002831",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002831? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "77.94、81.08、71.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "002832",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002832, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "002833",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 002833: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002835",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002835, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.17、17.95、16.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "002836",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002836, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002837",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002837, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.93、25.24、23.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "002838",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002838, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.73、17.70、15.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "002839",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002839 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.38、59.78、103.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "002840",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002840 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002841",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002841 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "002842",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002842, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "002843",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002843 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002845",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002845? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.51、22.92、18.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "002846",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002846, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.74、10.53、8.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002847",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002847 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002848",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002848 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002849",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002849 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.28、16.94、14.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "002850",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002850? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.99、7.50、-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002851",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002851 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002852",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002852 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.54、51.19、25.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "002853",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002853 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "002855",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002855 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002856",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002856 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002856 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "75.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "002857",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002857 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002858",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002858. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002859",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002859 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "002860",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002860 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "002861",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002861, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.21、14.48、13.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "002862",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002862, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.26、18.97、16.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "002863",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002863, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.19、5.01、4.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002864",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002864? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.33、63.00、72.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "002865",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002865 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002865 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "002866",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002866, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.57、16.01、15.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002867",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002867 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002868",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002868 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.23、21.85、16.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002869",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002869. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "002870",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 002870: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002871",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002871? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.42、49.54、13.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "002872",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002872 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.62、63.69、78.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "002873",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002873? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.27、47.07、41.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "002875",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002875 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "77.99、68.93、96.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002876",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002876 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "002877",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002877 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "002878",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002878 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "81.77、68.75、107.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "002879",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002879: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "002880",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002880 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.87、34.17、27.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "002881",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002881, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.62、46.75、41.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "002882",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002882, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.37、19.83、13.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002883",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002883 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "002884",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002884? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.47、31.48、67.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002885",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002885 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "002886",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002886 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "002887",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002887 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "002888",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002888 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002888 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "002889",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002889? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.39、35.74、85.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "002890",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002890, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.19、12.42、11.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "002891",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002891, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "002892",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002892 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002893",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002893: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002895",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002895? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.60、58.70、19.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002896",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002896 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.93、6.98、0.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "002897",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002897 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002898",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002898 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002898 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "89.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002899",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 002899 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "002900",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002900 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "002901",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock 002901 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002902",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002902. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "002903",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002903 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "002905",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002905. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002906",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002906, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.33、32.80、30.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "002907",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002907? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "90.20、76.08、118.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002908",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002908 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.91、9.32、8.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "002909",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002909 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "002910",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002910? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.41、59.87、49.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "002911",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002911, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.41、10.26、10.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002912",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002912: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002913",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002913, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.93、25.31、24.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "002915",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002915 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002915 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002916",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002916, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "91.70、86.22、80.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "002917",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002917: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "002918",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002918 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.62、8.37、8.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002919",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 002919: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "002920",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002920 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 002920 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002921",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002921, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "002922",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002922 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "002923",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002923, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.67、12.65、11.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "002925",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002925, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.83、16.25、15.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "002926",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002926: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002927",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 002927 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002928",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002928? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "81.73、80.36、84.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "002929",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002929? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.26、31.02、4.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "002930",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002930 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "73.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "002931",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002931 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002931 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "002932",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002932 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002933",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002933 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "002935",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002935, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.12、14.31、13.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "002936",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002936? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.02、50.42、61.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "002937",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002937, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.84、17.62、16.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002938",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock price 002938's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002939",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002939 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "002940",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002940, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.10、14.00、12.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "002941",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002941, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.78、11.44、11.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "002942",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002942? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.87、43.08、33.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "002943",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002943 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "002945",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002945 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "002946",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 002946 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002947",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002947 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "002948",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002948 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "002949",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002949 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.99、41.37、28.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002950",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002950? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.14、43.38、30.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "002951",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002951 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.50、40.39、28.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002952",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002952 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002953",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002953: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "002955",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002955 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "002956",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002956 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.44、36.58、-8.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "002957",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002957? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.30、45.39、48.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "002958",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002958 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002959",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002959 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 002959 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "002960",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002960 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "002961",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002961? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.09、54.25、62.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "002962",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002962 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "002963",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002963. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "002965",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002965, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.54、43.35、40.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002966",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002966 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "002967",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002967, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.17、17.24、16.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "002968",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 002968, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.54、9.89、9.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002969",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002969 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.61、46.40、32.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "002970",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002970: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "002971",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002971 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "002972",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002972 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.87、58.33、62.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "002973",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 002973 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "002975",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 002975 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002976",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 002976 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.02、22.90、21.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "002977",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002977 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002977 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "002978",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002978 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "002979",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 002979 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 002979 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "002980",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002980, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.75、26.29、24.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "002981",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 002981 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "002982",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 002982, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.99、15.05、14.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002983",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 002983 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "002984",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002984 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "002985",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002985 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002986",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002986? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.44、45.33、60.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "002987",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002987, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "002988",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 002988 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "002989",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 002989? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "81.86、81.09、83.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "002990",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 002990 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "002991",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 002991 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "002992",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 002992. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "002993",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002993 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "002995",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 002995 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "002996",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002996, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.04、6.87、6.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "002997",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 002997, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "002998",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002998, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.85、7.13、6.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "002999",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 002999, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.92、6.58、6.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "003000",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 003000 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "003001",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 003001 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.37、38.83、35.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "003002",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 003002? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "003003",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 003003. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "003004",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 003004, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.73、19.28、17.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "003005",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 003005? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.61、32.63、71.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "003006",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 003006 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "003007",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 003007 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.17、20.12、8.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "003008",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 003008, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.29、20.67、20.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "003009",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 003009 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "003010",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 003010, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "72.34、57.23、42.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "003011",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 003011: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "003012",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 003012 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "003013",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 003013 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "003015",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 003015? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.40、21.89、-3.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "003016",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 003016 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "003017",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 003017? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.62、24.87、9.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "003018",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 003018 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "003019",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 003019, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.42、30.59、28.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "003020",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 003020. Its latest stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "003021",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 003021 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "003022",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 003022 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "003023",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 003023 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "003025",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 003025, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.69、16.76、15.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "003026",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 003026, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "003027",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 003027 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "003028",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock price 003028's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "003029",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 003029 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "003030",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 003030 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "003031",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 003031? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.05、47.93、90.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "003032",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 003032 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.41、45.87、86.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "003033",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 003033 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "003035",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 003035 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.73、4.47、4.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "003036",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 003036. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "003037",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 003037 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "003038",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 003038 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "003039",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 003039 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "003040",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 003040 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "76.09、62.91、102.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "003041",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 003041, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.04、30.30、28.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "003042",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 003042? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "003043",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 003043 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "003816",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 003816 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.43、67.84、39.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "300001",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300001 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300002",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300002 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300003",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300003 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300004",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300004 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300005",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300005 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "300006",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300006 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300007",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300007 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "300008",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300008: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300009",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300009 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "300010",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300010, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300011",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300011 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.85、29.71、33.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300012",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300012. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "300013",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300013 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.49、27.53、63.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "300014",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300014 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300015",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300015 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300016",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300016, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.91、6.70、6.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300017",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300017 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.75、13.22、5.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300018",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 300018 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "300019",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300019. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300020",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300020 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300021",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300021 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300022",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300022. Its latest stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300024",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300024’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.68、16.82、15.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "300025",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300025 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "300026",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300026? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.14、70.91、80.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300027",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300027 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300029",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300029’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.54、5.11、4.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "300030",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300030 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300031",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300031, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.35、26.07、22.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "300032",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300032 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300033",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300033 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300033 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300034",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300034 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300035",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300035. Its latest stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300036",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300036: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300037",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300037 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.12、21.22、8.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "300039",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300039 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.51、61.27、62.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300040",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300040 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.92、20.89、-3.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300041",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300041 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "300042",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300042 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300042 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300043",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300043 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300043 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300044",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300044? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.49、29.16、-2.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300045",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 300045 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300046",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300046? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.46、32.29、56.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "300047",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300047 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300048",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300048, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300049",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 300049 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300050",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300050 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.66、36.22、25.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "300051",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300051 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300052",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300052 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "300053",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300053 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300053 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300054",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300054 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "300055",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 300055 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "300056",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300056 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300056 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "300057",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 300057 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "300058",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 300058 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300059",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300059, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.21、21.19、20.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300061",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300061? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.56、41.77、23.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300062",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300062 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300063",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300063 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300065",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300065 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "300066",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300066 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.14、28.57、33.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "300067",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 300067, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.77、5.47、5.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300068",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300068? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "300069",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300069: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "300070",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300070? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.55、44.66、83.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300071",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300071 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.33、34.76、45.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300072",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300072: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300073",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300073, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300074",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300074? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300075",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300075 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.33、50.66、103.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "300076",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 300076 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300077",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300077? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.22、26.03、50.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300078",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 300078, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.74、3.59、3.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "300079",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300079 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.50、39.87、74.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "300080",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300080's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.92、3.77、3.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300081",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300081, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.64、6.39、6.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300082",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300082? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.50、66.22、82.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300083",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300083? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300084",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300084? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300085",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300085: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300086",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300086's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.30、4.99、4.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "300087",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300087 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "300088",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300088: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300091",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300091? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.19、36.63、47.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300092",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300092, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.47、12.59、11.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300093",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300093 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "300094",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300094, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.61、3.48、3.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "300095",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300095 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "300096",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300096 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.70、31.47、-9.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300097",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300097 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300098",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300098? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300099",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300099, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.26、6.82、6.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "300100",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 300100 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "300101",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300101, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.35、17.42、16.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300102",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300102. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300103",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300103. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300105",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300105 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300105 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "300106",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300106 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300106 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "300107",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300107, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300109",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300109 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300110",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300110’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.27、3.11、2.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "300111",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300111, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.39、3.12、2.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "300112",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300112? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "300113",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300113? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.92、30.46、16.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300115",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300115 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "300118",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300118 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300119",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300119 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.06、43.90、-0.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300120",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300120 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300121",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300121 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "300122",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300122 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "300123",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300123 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.26、30.80、41.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300124",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300124? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300125",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300125 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300126",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300126 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "300127",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300127: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300128",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300128 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300129",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300129 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300130",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300130 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300131",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300131 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300132",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300132? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "300133",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300133 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300134",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300134, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300135",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300135 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.98、3.84、3.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300136",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300136 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.15、56.76、63.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "300137",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300137? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "300138",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300138: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300139",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300139 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300140",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300140 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.23、62.16、77.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "300141",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300141, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.88、8.63、8.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "300142",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300142 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300143",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300143, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "300144",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300144 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.56、27.27、37.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300145",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300145, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300146",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300146 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "300147",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300147 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.82、57.05、17.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "300148",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300148? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.58、62.25、63.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300149",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300149, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.05、6.91、4.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "300150",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300150 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300151",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300151, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.84、12.92、12.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300152",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300152 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300153",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300153 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "300154",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300154 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300155",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300155, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.81、4.61、4.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300157",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300157 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.62、27.75、27.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "300158",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300158? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "73.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "300159",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300159 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.34、69.28、27.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "300160",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300160 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300160 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300161",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300161, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300162",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300162, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300163",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300163 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300164",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300164 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300165",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300165 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300166",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300166? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300167",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300167 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300168",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300168 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300169",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300169? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.42、35.22、80.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300170",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300170, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.26、18.35、16.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "300171",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300171, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.32、11.95、11.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "300172",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300172: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300173",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300173? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.82、23.33、-2.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300174",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300174. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300175",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300175 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.32、5.05、4.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "300176",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300176. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300177",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300177? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.19、36.92、52.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300179",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 300179? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300180",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300180? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300181",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300181: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "300182",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300182 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.78、34.65、38.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300183",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300183. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "300184",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300184, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.96、10.14、9.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300185",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300185 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300187",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for stock 300187 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300188",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300188 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "300189",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300189? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300190",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300190, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.43、3.28、3.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300191",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300191? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.91、44.46、78.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "300192",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300192. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "300193",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300193 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.59、19.19、8.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "300194",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300194 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300195",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300195? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300196",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300196 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.19、48.06、27.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "300197",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300197 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.06、1.95、1.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "300198",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300198 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "300199",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300199, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.04、14.25、13.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300200",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300200’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.09、10.18、9.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300201",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300201. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300203",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300203 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300203 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300204",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300204’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.58、14.02、4.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300205",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300205, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.68、3.68、2.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "300206",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300206 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.37、30.53、45.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300207",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300207 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300209",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300209 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300210",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300210? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.48、40.77、9.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "300211",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300211 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.31、54.28、45.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "300212",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300212 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300212 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "300213",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300213, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300214",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300214: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300215",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300215. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300217",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300217? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.91、26.77、3.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300218",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300218 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "300219",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300219? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300220",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300220 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300221",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300221, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.31、8.89、8.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300222",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300222 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300222 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300223",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300223, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.23、66.90、62.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "300224",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300224, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.56、12.85、12.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300226",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 300226? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300227",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 300227 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300228",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for stock 300228’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300229",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300229 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300230",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300230 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300231",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300231 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300232",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300232: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300233",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300233 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300233 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300234",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 300234, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.89、4.76、4.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "300235",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300235 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300235 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300236",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300236: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "300237",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300237 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "300238",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300238? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "80.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300239",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300239 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "300240",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300240 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.32、40.60、54.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "300241",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300241 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300242",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300242 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300243",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300243 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300243 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300244",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300244 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.18、21.74、26.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300245",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300245, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.42、17.16、15.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "300246",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300246? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.27、50.65、64.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300247",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 300247? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300248",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300248, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.21、13.91、12.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "300249",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300249: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300250",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300250? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.81、38.05、58.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "300251",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300251, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.58、18.32、17.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300252",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300252 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300253",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300253 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300254",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300254? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.92、65.01、67.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "300255",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 300255 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "91.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "300256",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300256’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.64、4.24、3.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "300257",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300257 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300257 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300258",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300258. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "300259",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300259? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.39、25.65、9.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "300260",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300260 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300261",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300261, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "300263",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300263 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.86、18.09、5.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "300264",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300264, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300265",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300265? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.26、51.78、68.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "300266",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300266 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "300267",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300267 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300268",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300268 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "300269",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300269 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.79、43.35、41.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "300270",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300270 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300271",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300271, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.22、7.72、7.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "300272",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300272’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.28、6.13、5.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "300274",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300274 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300275",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300275? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300276",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300276 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "300277",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300277: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "300278",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300278 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300279",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300279? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.55、30.70、30.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "300281",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300281 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300283",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300283, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.97、5.75、5.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300284",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300284? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.21、38.76、91.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300285",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300285 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300286",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300286 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300287",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300287 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.75、22.15、32.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "300288",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300288 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.64、57.30、79.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300289",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300289 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300290",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300290 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.98、34.54、23.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "300291",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4, 2025, and May 30, 2025, what are the values of the upper, middle, and lower Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300291? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.90、4.77、4.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "300292",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300292 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.45、27.66、45.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300293",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300293. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300294",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300294 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.85、34.41、50.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "300295",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300295 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.00、49.09、90.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "300296",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300296 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300298",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300298, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.28、21.46、20.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300299",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300299 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "300300",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300300 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "82.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300301",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300301 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.14、61.74、53.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "300302",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300302 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "300303",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300303 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "300304",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300304 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.91、43.87、50.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300306",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300306, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.62、12.02、11.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "300308",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300308. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "300310",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300310 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300311",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300311 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.56、45.90、62.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "300313",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300313 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.71、5.61、4.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300316",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300316 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300317",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300317 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300318",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300318. Its latest stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300320",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300320, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.93、10.53、10.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300321",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300321, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300322",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300322? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.29、38.21、86.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "300323",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300323 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300324",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300324? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300326",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300326? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.35、36.95、23.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300327",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300327 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300328",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300328, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.39、11.16、9.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "300329",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300329 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300331",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 300331? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300333",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300333 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300334",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300334 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.75、6.43、6.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300335",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for the stock 300335? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300337",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300337, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.22、10.44、9.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "300338",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300338? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.02、32.75、33.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "300339",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for stock 300339’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "300340",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300340? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.15、32.63、16.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300341",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 300341 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300342",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300342 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.65、16.34、15.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300343",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300343 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "300344",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 300344, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.53、4.59、3.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "300345",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300345 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300346",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300346 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.07、31.53、63.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300347",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300347? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300348",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300348 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.85、12.94、12.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300349",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300349, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.63、11.98、11.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "300350",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300350. Its latest stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "300351",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300351? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.38、19.52、7.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300352",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300352 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300352 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300353",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300353 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300354",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300354? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.09、33.99、67.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300355",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300355 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.03、27.59、25.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "300357",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300357 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300358",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300358, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300359",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300359? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.71、35.69、35.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "300360",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300360 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "300363",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300363 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300364",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300364? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300365",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300365 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.71、60.03、68.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "300366",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300366, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.42、7.74、7.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300368",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300368 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.62、6.86、6.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "300369",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300369, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.36、7.03、6.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300370",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300370. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300371",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300371? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300373",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 300373? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300374",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300374, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.37、15.79、15.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "300375",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300375’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.13、4.93、4.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300376",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300376, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.57、3.48、3.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "300377",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300377 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.04、24.39、23.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300378",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300378 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.48、19.35、10.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "300379",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300379 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300380",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300380 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "300381",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300381 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.12、7.70、7.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "300382",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300382? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.61、55.27、14.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "300383",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300383, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.50、14.08、12.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "300384",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300384 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "300385",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300385 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.89、55.50、53.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "300386",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300386 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300387",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300387 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.31、30.60、17.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300388",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300388 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300389",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) indicator for stock 300389 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300390",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300390? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.50、19.45、4.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "300391",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300391 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300393",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300393? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.27、20.59、16.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300394",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300394 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "300395",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300395 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300396",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300396 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "300397",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300397: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "300398",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) indicator for stock 300398 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "300399",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300399: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "300400",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300400 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "300401",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300401: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300402",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300402 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.15、59.36、103.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300403",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300403 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.17、14.24、8.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300404",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock 300404 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300405",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300405? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.97、34.22、21.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300406",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300406, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.20、13.59、12.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "300407",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300407 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.45、19.24、13.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "300408",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300408 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300409",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300409 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300410",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for the stock 300410? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300411",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 300411? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300412",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 300412 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300413",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300413, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "300414",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300414 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.55、44.21、45.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300415",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 300415? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300416",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300416 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "300417",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300417, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.37、11.83、11.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300418",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300418 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "300419",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300419 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.28、73.64、39.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "300420",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300420 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "300421",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300421 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.09、11.92、-2.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "300422",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock 300422 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "300423",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300423? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300424",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300424 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.51、34.70、91.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300425",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300425 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.65、45.92、36.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300426",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300426’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.37、9.80、9.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300427",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300427? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300428",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300428 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300428 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300429",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300429’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.66、11.66、10.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "300430",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300430 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300432",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300432 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300433",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300433 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300433 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300434",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for stock 300434 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300435",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300435’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.31、13.91、13.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300436",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300436? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300437",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300437, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.65、7.98、7.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300438",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300438 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300438 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300439",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300439. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "300440",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300440 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "300441",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300441 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.76、8.24、7.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300442",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300442 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.27、21.79、11.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300443",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300443: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "300444",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300444: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "300445",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300445, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.30、17.08、15.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300447",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300447 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "300448",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300448, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.66、6.43、6.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300449",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300449 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300449 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300450",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 300450: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300451",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300451, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.94、5.56、5.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300452",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300452. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "300453",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 300453 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300454",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300454 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "100.57、93.19、85.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300455",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300455 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "300456",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300456 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.99、16.55、16.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300457",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300457, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.22、17.44、16.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "300458",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300458 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300459",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300459 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "300460",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300460, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300461",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300461 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "300462",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300462? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.92、57.14、56.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300463",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 300463 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300464",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300464 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.04、58.91、71.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300465",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300465 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300466",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300466, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.57、11.63、9.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "300467",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300467? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "300468",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300468: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "300469",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300469 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 300469 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300470",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300470: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300471",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300471? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.50、25.42、19.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "300472",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300472 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.82、70.35、74.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "300473",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300473? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "72.60、65.93、85.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "300474",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300474 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300475",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300475 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.12、13.78、11.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "300476",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300476, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "85.42、79.11、72.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "300477",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300477? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.35、54.55、17.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "300478",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300478 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300479",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300479’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.68、19.87、19.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300480",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300480: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300481",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300481 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "300482",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300482 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300483",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300483 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.64、43.91、37.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300484",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300484? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.06、27.42、-3.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "300485",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300485: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "300486",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300486 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.13、65.40、64.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "300487",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300487 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300488",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300488? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.63、12.94、0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300489",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300489 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.35、27.72、-9.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "300490",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator for stock 300490 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300491",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) calculated for stock 300491 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300492",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for stock 300492 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300493",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300493 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "300494",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300494 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300496",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300496? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.77、31.74、55.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "300497",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300497. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300498",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300498 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300499",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300499: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "300500",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300500 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300501",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300501, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.06、14.80、13.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "300502",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300502 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300503",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300503 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.52、11.63、5.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300504",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300504 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300505",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300505 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300506",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300506. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300507",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300507, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.13、8.14、7.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300508",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300508? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300509",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300509: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300510",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300510: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300511",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300511 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.06、74.70、60.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "300512",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300512: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300513",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300513 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "300514",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300514 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300515",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300515 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300516",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300516: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300517",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300517? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300518",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300518? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.70、44.14、0.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300519",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 300519, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.11、14.46、13.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300520",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300520, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "300521",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300521? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.10、23.47、10.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "300522",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 300522? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300523",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300523 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.39、64.03、38.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300525",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300525 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300525 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300527",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300527. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "300528",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300528 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300529",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300529, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.44、21.87、21.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300530",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300530 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "69.27、70.25、67.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300531",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300531 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.38、15.89、14.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "300532",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300532, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "300533",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300533. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "300534",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300534 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "300535",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300535 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "300536",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300536? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.72、24.89、-11.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "300537",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300537 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "300538",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300538 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.67、54.93、36.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300539",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300539 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.15、15.51、-0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "300540",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300540 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300541",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300541 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300542",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300542 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300543",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300543? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.46、19.62、13.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300545",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300545 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300546",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300546, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.90、17.74、13.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "300547",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300547? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.09、20.59、43.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "300548",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300548: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "300549",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300549 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300550",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300550? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.64、51.73、57.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300551",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 300551 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300552",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300552, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "300553",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 300553 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300554",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300554 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300555",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 300555 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300556",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300556 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.10、55.89、68.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300557",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300557 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "300558",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300558? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "75.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "300559",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 300559 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300560",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300560? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.59、50.49、74.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300561",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300561 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300562",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 300562? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300563",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300563: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300564",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300564, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "300565",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300565’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.47、11.08、10.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "300566",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300566 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300566 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300567",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300567? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.92、20.72、39.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300568",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300568 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.08、22.70、5.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "300569",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300569 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300569 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300570",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300570. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "300571",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300571, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.90、32.06、29.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "300572",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300572 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "300573",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300573 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 300573 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300575",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300575 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.57、51.00、37.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300576",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300576? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.96、32.99、56.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "300577",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300577 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300577 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "300578",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300578 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "300579",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300579. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300580",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300580? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "300581",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300581, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.51、14.19、9.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "300582",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300582 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300583",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300583, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300584",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300584 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.79、24.48、14.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300585",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300585 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300586",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300586’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.89、9.23、8.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "300587",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300587? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.28、52.28、46.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300588",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300588 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.28、42.71、71.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300589",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300589 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.32、23.11、29.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300590",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300590 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.98、28.67、29.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "300591",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300591, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.33、5.69、5.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "300592",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300592’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.29、11.39、10.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "300593",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300593, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.60、14.16、12.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "300594",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300594 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.18、53.87、87.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300595",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300595: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300596",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300596 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300597",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300597? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.68、43.69、34.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300598",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300598? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.23、16.11、13.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "300599",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300599 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "71.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300600",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 300600? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300601",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300601 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.36、40.88、72.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300602",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300602 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300603",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300603, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.22、11.22、10.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300604",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300604 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.04、28.34、-2.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "300605",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300605 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "300606",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300606? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.28、51.61、44.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "300607",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300607? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300608",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300608 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300609",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300609 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.75、28.52、-0.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "300610",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300610 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300611",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300611 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.37、9.30、-2.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300612",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300612 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300612 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300613",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300613, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.90、47.67、45.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "300614",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300614 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.80、71.35、63.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300615",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300615 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300616",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300616 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300617",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300617 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "300618",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300618? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.34、14.65、1.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300619",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300619 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300620",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 300620, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.36、41.16、38.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "300621",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300621 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300622",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300622? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.74、13.11、-5.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "300623",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300623 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.10、23.57、22.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300624",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300624? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.44、18.51、21.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300625",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300625 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.80、40.92、31.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "300626",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300626? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.19、26.54、16.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300627",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300627. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "300628",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300628, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.98、34.76、33.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "300629",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300629 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.99、14.85、12.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300630",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300630 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300630 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300631",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300631’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.40、22.07、18.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "300632",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 300632 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300633",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300633, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.23、31.94、30.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300634",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300634, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.08、25.46、23.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300635",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300635? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300636",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300636 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300637",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300637 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.92、10.49、10.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "300638",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300638 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.46、22.59、31.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300639",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300639, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.77、5.42、5.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300640",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300640 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.60、6.09、5.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "300641",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300641 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300641 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "300642",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300642, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.21、13.90、13.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "300643",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 300643 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300644",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300644 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300645",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300645 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300647",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300647 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "300648",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300648 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.22、33.03、26.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "300649",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300649’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.06、11.65、11.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300650",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300650 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.26、44.92、-11.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300651",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300651 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300651 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "77.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300652",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300652 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "90.78、82.25、73.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300653",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300653, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300654",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300654 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.60、10.21、9.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300655",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300655 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300656",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300656, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.19、25.69、23.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300657",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300657? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.06、17.27、1.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "300658",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300658, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "300659",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300659 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300660",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300660? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "300661",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300661. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "300662",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 300662 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300663",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300663. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300664",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300664 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300665",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300665, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.77、7.46、7.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300666",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300666, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "300667",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300667, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "300668",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300668 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "300669",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300669? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.65、67.73、55.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300670",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300670 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.62、46.00、26.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "300671",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300671 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "300672",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300672 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "96.32、92.49、103.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "300673",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300673, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.26、16.77、14.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300674",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300674 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "300675",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300675. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300676",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300676 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "300677",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300677 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300678",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300678 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300678 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "300679",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300679 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300680",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for the stock 300680? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300681",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300681? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.48、14.76、31.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "300682",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300682: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "73.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "300683",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300683. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300684",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for stock 300684 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "300685",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300685 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.72、32.36、69.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300686",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300686, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.10、8.76、8.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300687",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300687 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.93、13.81、20.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300688",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300688? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.86、53.69、51.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300689",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300689 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300690",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300690? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "300691",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300691, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300692",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300692 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300693",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300693: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300694",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock 300694 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300695",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300695 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "98.57、85.60、72.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300696",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300696 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "300697",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300697: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300698",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300698, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.06、35.55、32.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300699",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300699 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.28、30.11、28.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "300700",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300700 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300701",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300701, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.15、9.80、9.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300702",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300702, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.45、21.73、21.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300703",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300703 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "300705",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300705. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300706",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300706. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "300707",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300707 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.18、25.09、4.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "300708",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300708 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.71、11.31、10.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "300709",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300709 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.41、44.38、44.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300710",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300710 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.00、39.35、26.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300711",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300711? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.15、18.62、20.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300712",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300712 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.62、22.95、22.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300713",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300713, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300715",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300715 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.10、10.19、9.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "300716",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300716, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "300717",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300717 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300718",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300718. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300719",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300719, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.16、17.18、15.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300720",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300720. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300721",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) indicator for stock 300721 ​​was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300722",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300722 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "300723",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300723. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "300724",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300724: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "300725",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300725 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300726",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300726 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300727",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300727’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.06、28.94、26.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300729",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 300729, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.56、15.34、13.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300730",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300730 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "300731",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300731 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300732",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300732 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300733",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300733. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "300735",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300735, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.14、26.46、24.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "300736",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300736, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.04、9.68、9.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300737",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300737 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300738",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300738 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.13、19.96、29.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "300739",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300739? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300740",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300740. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "300741",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300741, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300743",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300743 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.29、17.32、16.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "300745",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300745 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "300746",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300746, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.70、14.00、12.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "300747",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 300747: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300748",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300748: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "300749",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300749 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "300750",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300750 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.62、30.29、-13.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "300751",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300751 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.15、13.80、5.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300752",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300752? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.85、16.29、11.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "300753",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300753 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300755",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300755, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "300756",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300756? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.77、61.10、27.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300757",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for stock 300757’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300758",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300758: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300759",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300759 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.80、54.27、91.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "300760",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300760 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.72、46.57、29.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300761",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300761 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "300762",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300762, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.78、21.40、20.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300763",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300763 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.97、12.50、1.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "300765",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300765 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300766",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300766, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.15、38.29、34.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300767",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300767, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.65、10.23、9.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300768",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300768 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300769",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300769. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300770",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300770 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.11、39.36、38.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "300771",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300771, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.07、11.44、8.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300772",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300772? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.32、21.84、38.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300773",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 300773 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "300774",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300774 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.61、27.80、3.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300775",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300775 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300776",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300776 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "300777",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300777 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300778",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300778? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "300779",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300779 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300780",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300780 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300781",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300781? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.98、55.22、3.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "300782",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300782? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.18、20.33、31.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "300783",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300783, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.28、28.04、25.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300784",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300784, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.44、54.49、51.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "300785",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300785 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "300786",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300786 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "300787",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300787’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.32、11.87、11.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300788",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300788? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300789",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300789 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.87、8.25、10.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300790",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300790. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300791",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300791 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "300792",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300792 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.56、27.15、-4.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300793",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300793 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300795",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300795 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.20、36.66、38.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "300796",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300796, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.95、9.56、8.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300797",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300797 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.25、30.46、38.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "300798",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300798 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.15、51.62、65.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300800",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300800? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "300801",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300801, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.42、15.99、15.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "300802",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300802, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "300803",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300803 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.35、18.97、32.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "300804",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300804 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300805",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300805 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.35、40.31、-1.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "300806",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300806, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300807",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300807 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300808",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300808 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.29、47.02、89.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "300809",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300809’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.90、40.20、33.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "300810",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300810 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.04、27.68、79.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "300811",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300811 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300811 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300812",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 300812 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300813",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300813 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300814",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300814, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.77、28.82、26.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "300815",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300815: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "300816",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300816 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300817",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300817, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.09、27.07、23.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300818",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300818. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "300819",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300819, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.09、25.80、22.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300820",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300820’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.51、45.71、39.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "300821",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300821: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300822",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300822 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300823",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300823 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300823 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300824",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300824. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300825",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300825 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.55、46.11、26.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "300826",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300826? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "300827",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300827? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.44、11.21、8.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "300828",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300828 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.80、15.45、16.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300829",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300829, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.34、19.21、18.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300830",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300830 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "300831",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300831, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300832",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 300832? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "300833",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300833’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.72、33.90、33.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "300834",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300834 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.03、55.78、62.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "300835",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300835, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300836",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300836 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "86.13、77.60、103.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300837",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300837, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.17、21.43、20.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300838",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300838 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.43、27.89、38.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "300839",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300839 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.56、64.13、35.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "300840",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator for stock 300840 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "300841",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300841, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.48、53.56、50.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "300842",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300842, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.02、40.04、38.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300843",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300843 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "300844",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300844 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.03、57.53、86.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300845",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300845 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "300846",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300846 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300847",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300847, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.31、16.54、15.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "300848",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300848 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "300849",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300849 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300849 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300850",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300850 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300850 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "300851",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300851 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.80、39.86、30.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "300852",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300852 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300853",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 300853 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300854",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300854 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300855",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300855’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.57、22.56、21.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "300856",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300856. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "300857",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300857 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.79、41.78、92.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "300858",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300858 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.85、59.21、46.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300859",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300859, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300860",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300860 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 300860 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300861",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300861? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.65、13.03、-6.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300862",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300862 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "300863",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "May I ask what the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300863 is on May 30, 2025, during the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "300864",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300864: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300865",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300865’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.69、22.98、22.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300866",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300866 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.94、53.15、37.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "300867",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300867, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300868",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300868? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "300869",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300869’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.48、14.03、13.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "300870",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300870. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "300871",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300871? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300872",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300872 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "76.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "300873",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300873 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "300875",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 300875’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.75、28.96、26.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "300876",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300876 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300876 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "300877",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300877? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "300878",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300878 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "76.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "300879",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300879 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300880",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300880, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.30、20.53、19.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "300881",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300881 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.69、54.21、79.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "300882",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300882, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.09、15.27、14.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300883",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300883? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300884",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300884 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300885",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300885 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300886",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300886, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.35、25.16、20.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "300887",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300887 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.99、40.31、54.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "300888",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300888? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.22、14.76、1.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "300889",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300889 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "300890",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300890 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.27、41.84、40.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300891",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 300891, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "300892",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300892 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "300893",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300893 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "300894",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300894 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "300895",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300895 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "300896",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300896 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300897",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300897 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.46、27.09、24.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "300898",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300898 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300899",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300899 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.82、62.65、9.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300900",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300900, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.97、22.09、20.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300901",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300901, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.61、13.65、12.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "300902",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300902? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.47、43.85、75.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "300903",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300903, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.23、7.93、7.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300904",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300904 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.34、59.53、54.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "300905",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300905 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.59、26.14、24.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "300906",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300906 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.91、50.87、62.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "300907",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300907 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.69、14.52、3.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "300908",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300908 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.72、45.95、9.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300909",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300909 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "300910",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300910 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.53、58.87、56.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "300911",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300911? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "300912",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 300912 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300913",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 300913? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300915",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300915 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.57、56.39、59.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "300916",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300916, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.69、28.11、26.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300917",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300917, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.89、43.96、40.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300918",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300918 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "300919",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300919 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 300919 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300920",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300920 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.07、34.47、26.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "300921",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300921 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300922",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300922 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.28、12.56、8.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "300923",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300923: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300925",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of stock 300925 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "300926",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300926 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "300927",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300927 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "300928",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300928? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.24、26.60、22.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300929",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300929: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "300930",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300930 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.64、25.73、16.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "300931",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300931 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300932",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300932 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "300933",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300933 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.18、55.42、57.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "300935",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300935. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300936",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300936? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300937",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300937: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "78.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "300938",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300938 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.14、10.97、2.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300939",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300939 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300940",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300940? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300941",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 300941 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300942",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300942? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.21、46.87、53.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "300943",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300943 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "300945",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 300945, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.69、18.10、11.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300946",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 300946 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 300946 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "300947",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300947? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.97、37.86、23.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "300948",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300948, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.34、9.99、9.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "300949",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300949 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.04、35.30、30.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "300950",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300950 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "300951",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300951 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.66、28.36、20.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300952",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300952 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300953",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300953 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "300955",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 300955 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "300956",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 300956? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300957",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300957 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.31、45.04、12.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "300958",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300958 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "300959",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300959 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300960",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 300960 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "300961",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 300961 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "300962",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) indicator for stock 300962 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300963",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300963 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "300964",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 300964 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300965",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300965? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.77、18.08、32.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "300966",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300966, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.78、16.96、16.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "300968",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300968? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.87、13.37、5.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "300969",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300969 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "300970",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300970 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.27、57.14、9.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "300971",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300971? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.61、41.29、81.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "300972",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300972 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300973",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 300973 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "78.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "300975",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 300975 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300976",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300976 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "300977",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300977 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.17、40.08、37.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "300978",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 300978 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "300979",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300979. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "300980",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 300980: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300981",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300981 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.75、55.48、62.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300982",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300982 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.19、53.86、60.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "300983",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 300983? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "72.98、65.93、87.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "300984",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 300984. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "300985",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300985 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.17、16.66、16.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "300986",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 300986 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "300987",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300987, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.10、15.70、15.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "300988",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300988: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "300989",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300989 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.39、52.27、67.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "300990",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300990, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.17、47.00、43.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "300991",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300991 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.42、57.11、76.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "300992",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 300992? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "300993",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300993 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.78、10.85、9.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "300994",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300994, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.44、17.17、14.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "300995",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 300995 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "300996",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 300996, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.52、14.78、14.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "300997",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 300997 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "300998",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 300998 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.45、18.94、17.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "300999",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 300999: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "301000",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301000 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 301000 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "301001",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301001 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "301002",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 301002’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.30、17.46、15.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "301003",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 301003 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "301004",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301004? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "301005",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301005, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.72、32.66、29.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "301006",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301006 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.09、38.02、23.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "301007",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301007, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "301008",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301008 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.47、11.46、-0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "301009",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301009 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.31、13.44、10.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "301010",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301010 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.53、40.01、41.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "301011",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301011 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 301011 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "301012",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301012 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "301013",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301013? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "301015",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 301015’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.85、18.19、17.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "301016",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301016? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.68、24.30、37.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "301017",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301017, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.73、11.88、11.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "301018",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301018 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 301018 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "301019",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301019: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301020",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301020 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 301020 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "301021",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301021 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.97、29.28、27.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "301022",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 301022 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "301023",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301023 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 301023 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "301024",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301024 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "301025",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301025 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.73、69.85、63.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "301026",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301026 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "301027",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 301027 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "83.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "301028",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301028? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "301029",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301029, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.45、22.80、21.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "301030",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301030? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.71、15.50、16.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "301031",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301031 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "301032",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301032 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.22、10.63、3.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "301033",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 301033? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "301035",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301035 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.00、53.14、43.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "301036",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301036? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.34、15.01、4.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "301037",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301037 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "301038",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301038 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "301039",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301039? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.33、38.61、61.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "301040",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301040, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.16、23.40、20.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "301041",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 301041? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "301042",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301042 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.20、40.85、44.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "301043",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 301043 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "301045",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301045: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "301046",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301046, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "301047",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301047 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "301048",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301048 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "301049",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301049 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.97、72.84、55.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "301050",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301050 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.92、14.16、-1.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "301051",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301051 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.55、28.69、28.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "301052",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 301052? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "301053",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301053 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301055",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301055? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "67.04、68.36、64.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "301056",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301056. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "301057",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301057, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.80、16.10、14.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "301058",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301058 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "301059",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301059: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "301060",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301060? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "301061",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301061 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "301062",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301062 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 301062 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "301063",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301063, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "301065",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301065? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "301066",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 301066? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "301067",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301067 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "301068",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301068? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.07、53.63、45.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "301069",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301069? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "301070",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301070, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "301071",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 301071? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "301072",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301072? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.36、33.53、-5.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "301073",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 301073 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "301075",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301075, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "69.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301076",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301076. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "301077",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 301077 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "301078",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301078? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "73.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "301079",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301079 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.47、63.54、72.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "301080",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301080, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.20、49.83、46.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "301081",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301081, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301082",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301082 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "301083",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301083 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 301083 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "301085",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301085 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "301086",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301086: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "301087",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301087 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "301088",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 301088 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "301089",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 301089 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "301090",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301090, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "301091",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301091, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.30、35.72、33.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "301092",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301092 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.14、35.12、14.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "301093",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 301093 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "301095",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301095 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 301095 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "301096",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301096? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "87.14、82.11、97.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "301097",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301097: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "301098",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301098? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.43、54.46、48.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "301100",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301100 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 301100 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "301101",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301101, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.61、48.27、38.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "301102",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301102? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "301103",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301103 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.16、54.68、53.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "301105",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 301105 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "301106",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301106 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "301107",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301107 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "301108",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301108, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.97、31.21、25.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "301109",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301109 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "301110",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301110 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "301111",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301111 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "78.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "301112",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301112 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.50、35.18、25.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "301113",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301113, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.60、20.01、19.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "301115",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301115 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "301116",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301116, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.69、11.14、10.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "301117",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301117 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "301118",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301118 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "301119",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 301119 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "301120",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for the stock price of 301120 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "301121",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301121? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.97、16.86、2.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "301122",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301122 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "301123",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 301123 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "301125",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301125 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "301126",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301126 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "301127",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301127 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "301128",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301128? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.73、9.77、3.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "301129",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301129 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "301130",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301130. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "301131",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301131, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.04、48.14、43.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "301132",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301132? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.74、42.73、15.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "301133",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301133 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "301135",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301135 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "301136",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301136 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "301137",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301137 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "301138",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301138 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "58.72、67.18、41.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "301139",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301139. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "301141",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301141 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.61、16.40、5.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "301148",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301148, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.62、20.02、18.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "301149",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301149? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.92、52.97、4.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "301150",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301150 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 301150 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "301151",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301151, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.69、16.08、15.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "301152",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301152 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.78、33.53、7.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "301153",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301153? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.56、29.61、65.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "301155",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301155 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.35、34.50、28.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301156",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301156, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.62、21.25、17.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "301157",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301157? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "301158",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301158 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.09、23.56、22.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "301159",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301159. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "301160",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301160 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "301161",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) indicator for stock 301161 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "301162",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 301162? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "301163",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301163 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "301165",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301165 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.95、13.86、29.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "301166",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 301166 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301167",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301167, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "301168",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 301168 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301169",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301169: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "301170",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301170 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.31、25.57、24.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "301171",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301171 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.97、17.71、15.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "301172",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301172, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.32、27.20、26.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "301175",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301175 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "301176",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301176, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.57、16.91、16.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "301177",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301177, what was its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "301178",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301178 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "75.69、76.06、74.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "301179",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301179 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.04、13.57、13.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "301180",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301180 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.53、33.28、22.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "301181",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301181, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.75、25.44、23.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "301182",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301182 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.46、14.78、13.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "301183",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301183 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "301185",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301185 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 301185 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "301186",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301186 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "73.85、66.39、88.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "301187",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301187 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.34、25.17、22.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "301188",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301188 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.71、50.09、27.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "301189",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301189: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "301190",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301190 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "301191",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301191 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "301192",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301192 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "301193",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301193 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "301195",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301195? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "301196",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 301196 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "301197",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301197, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "301198",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 301198 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "301199",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 301199 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "301200",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301200 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 301200 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "301201",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 301201 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "301202",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301202, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.05、42.00、38.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "301203",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301203 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.15、30.34、29.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "301205",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301205 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.22、15.98、7.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "301206",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301206, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.90、29.00、26.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "301207",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301207 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "301208",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301208 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "301209",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301209, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "301210",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301210 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.76、24.57、-4.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "301211",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301211? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.19、43.48、27.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "301212",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301212, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.90、28.67、25.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "301213",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301213 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "301215",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301215 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "59.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "301216",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301216 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "301217",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301217, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.84、10.48、10.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "301218",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301218. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "301219",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 301219 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "301220",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301220? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.16、22.40、45.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "301221",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) indicator for stock 301221 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "301222",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301222 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.64、35.30、27.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "301223",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 301223 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "301225",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301225 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "301226",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301226? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.42、15.41、6.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "301227",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301227? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "301228",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301228 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "301229",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301229 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "301230",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301230 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.85、56.56、78.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "301231",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301231. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "301232",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301232: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "301233",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301233, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.83、51.36、48.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "301234",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301234 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "301235",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301235, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.40、23.42、21.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "301236",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301236, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "301237",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301237: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "301238",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301238? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.96、28.84、-0.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "301239",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301239? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "301246",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301246. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "301248",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301248 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "301251",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for the stock 301251? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "301252",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 301252? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "301255",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301255, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.20、44.24、39.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "301256",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301256? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "301257",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301257 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.97、28.88、26.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "301258",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301258? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.59、60.65、12.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "301259",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301259, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.72、42.88、32.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "301260",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301260 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "301261",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301261 ​​from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "101.25、87.82、74.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "301262",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301262? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.50、30.34、42.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "301263",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301263, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "84.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "301265",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301265: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "301266",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301266 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.93、18.03、5.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "301267",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301267: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "301268",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301268 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.69、22.92、10.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "301269",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301269 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "301270",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301270? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "301272",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301272 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.29、16.26、1.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "301273",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301273 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.69、19.27、8.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "301276",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301276? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.14、43.06、4.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "301277",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 301277 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "301278",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301278? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.01、18.25、-3.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "301279",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301279 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 301279 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "301280",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 301280 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "301281",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301281? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.84、37.96、13.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "301282",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301282, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.68、21.00、20.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "301283",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301283 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 301283 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "301285",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 301285’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.53、29.36、27.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "301286",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301286? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.71、24.32、16.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "301287",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301287, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.51、34.21、31.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "301288",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301288. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "301289",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301289 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "301290",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301290? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.54、61.93、57.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "301291",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301291 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.06、40.78、35.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "301292",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301292? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.37、32.40、5.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "301293",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301293. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "301295",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301295? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "301296",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301296 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "301297",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301297 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.23、59.28、32.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "301298",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301298 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.03、15.48、5.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "301299",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301299 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 301299 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "301300",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301300? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "301301",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301301 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "301302",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301302. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "301303",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 301303 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301305",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301305, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "301306",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301306 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.33、37.14、34.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "301307",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301307 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.69、31.83、22.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "301308",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301308 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "301309",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301309? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.22、74.34、55.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "301310",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301310 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 301310 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "301311",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301311? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.28、40.91、45.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "301312",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301312 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 301312 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "301313",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301313, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "301314",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301314 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "301315",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301315 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "301316",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301316. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "69.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "301317",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301317. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "301318",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301318: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "301319",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301319, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "301320",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 301320 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301321",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301321 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "301322",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301322? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "301323",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301323? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.80、26.26、-11.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "301325",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301325, what is its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "301326",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301326. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "73.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "301327",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 301327’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.84、49.47、46.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "301328",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301328 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.53、34.50、7.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "301329",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301329, what was its most recent stock price 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "301330",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301330 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.85、29.56、28.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "301331",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301331 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.11、56.42、46.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "301332",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301332, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "301333",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301333 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "69.31、61.50、84.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "301335",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301335 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "64.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "301336",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301336. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "301337",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301337? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "301338",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301338 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.69、68.20、33.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "301339",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301339 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "301345",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301345 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 301345 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "69.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "301348",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301348 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.53、20.38、8.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "301349",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301349. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "301353",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301353, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "301355",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) indicator for stock 301355 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "301356",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301356 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.23、52.73、27.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "301357",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301357 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "65.79、57.21、82.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "301358",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301358? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "301359",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301359 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.69、27.57、12.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "301360",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301360, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.53、46.08、44.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "301361",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301361, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.52、30.74、28.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "301362",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 301362 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "301363",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301363, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.89、24.39、22.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "301365",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301365 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.47、17.16、15.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "301366",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301366? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.31、25.88、63.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "301367",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301367 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.44、42.99、-0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "301368",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301368, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "75.95、67.33、58.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "301369",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301369, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.88、48.20、46.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "301370",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301370 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.51、10.22、9.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "301371",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301371. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "301372",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301372 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "301373",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301373? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "301376",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301376, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.97、19.73、17.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "301377",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301377 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.06、15.23、-3.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "301378",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) indicator for stock 301378 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "301379",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301379 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.60、15.09、7.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "301380",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301380 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "301381",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301381? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "301382",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301382 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.10、12.81、7.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "301383",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 301383 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "301386",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301386 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "53.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "301387",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301387 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.69、15.97、0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "301388",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301388 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.18、35.57、16.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "301389",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) indicator for stock 301389 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "301390",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator for stock 301390 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "301391",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301391 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "301392",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301392 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "301393",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301393, what was its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "68.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "301395",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301395 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "301396",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301396? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.54、37.91、30.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "301397",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301397 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "301398",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301398: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "301399",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301399, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.38、16.76、16.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "301408",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301408 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "69.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "301413",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301413, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "101.04、87.12、73.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "301418",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301418? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.60、30.49、12.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "301419",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301419? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "301421",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301421 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "301428",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301428 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "301429",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 301429 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "301439",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301439, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.73、15.11、14.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "301446",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301446? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "301448",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 301448? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "301456",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301456, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.48、23.47、22.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "301458",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301458 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.14、15.63、8.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "301459",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301459, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.56、44.52、34.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "301468",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301468, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.39、22.39、20.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "301469",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for stock 301469 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "301486",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301486 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 301486 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "301487",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301487, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.41、19.14、17.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "301488",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301488, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "81.16、68.41、55.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "301489",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301489 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "301498",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301498, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "113.45、108.53、103.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "301499",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 301499 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "301500",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301500. Its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "301502",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301502? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.83、38.48、24.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "301503",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301503, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.22、37.60、35.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "301505",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301505. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "301507",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301507 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "301508",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301508 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.94、29.50、72.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "301509",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301509 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "301510",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301510 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.12、32.55、28.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "301511",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301511 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "301512",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301512 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "301515",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301515 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.79、19.14、18.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "301516",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent stock price for stock 301516 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "301517",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301517 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.14、50.31、46.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "301518",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 301518, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.86、24.54、19.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "301519",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301519 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "301520",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 301520 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "301522",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301522 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "301525",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301525? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "301526",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301526. Its recent 14-day average true stock price range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "301528",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) indicator for stock 301528 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "66.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "301529",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 301529 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "301533",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301533, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.43、32.51、30.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "301536",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301536, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "63.97、58.53、53.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "301538",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301538 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.05、54.52、56.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "301539",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 301539 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "301548",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301548: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "301550",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301550: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "301551",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301551 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "301552",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301552, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "301555",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 301555 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "301556",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301556 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.82、18.61、34.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "301558",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301558 calculated on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "35.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "301559",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301559: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "301565",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301565? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.43、32.66、10.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "301566",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301566? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "301567",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301567? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "301568",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 301568: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "301571",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301571: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "301577",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301577: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "301578",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) indicator for stock 301578 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "301580",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301580? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.70、57.31、28.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "301581",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301581? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.75、42.31、49.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "301585",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 301585 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "301586",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 301586? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "301587",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301587: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "47.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "301588",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 301588. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "301589",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301589 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "301591",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 301591 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "301592",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) calculated for stock 301592 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "301596",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price calculated on May 30 for stock 301596? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "301598",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent stock price for stock 301598 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "52.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "301600",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301600? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.63、16.39、11.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "301601",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 301601, what was its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "301602",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 301602, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.36、25.26、24.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "301603",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent stock price 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301603: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "301606",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 301606 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.09、44.55、35.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "301607",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 301607 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.86、45.06、56.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "301608",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 301608, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "84.86、80.39、75.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "301611",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 301611 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "301613",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 301613 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 301613 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "301617",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301617: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "301618",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 301618 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "301622",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "The most recent Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) indicator for stock 301622 between March 4 and May 30, 2025 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "301626",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 301626’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Give me the values ​​directly. What are the values ​​of the upper rail, middle rail and lower rail in order? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "76.28、72.31、68.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "301628",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 301628 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? _______, _______, _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.58、20.54、-3.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "301631",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 301631 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "301633",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 301633? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "74.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "302132",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 302132? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "600000",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600000 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "600004",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600004 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "18209601"
  },
  {
    "id": "600006",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600006 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600006 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "127082668"
  },
  {
    "id": "600007",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600007 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600007 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2723096"
  },
  {
    "id": "600008",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600008 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600009",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600009 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5151501"
  },
  {
    "id": "600010",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600010, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "147249226"
  },
  {
    "id": "600011",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600011 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600011 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "45663874"
  },
  {
    "id": "600012",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600012 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "600015",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600015 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600016",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600016: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "218941084"
  },
  {
    "id": "600017",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600017: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "600018",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600018? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "600019",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600019. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "600020",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600020 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "600021",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600021 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "600022",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600022 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "23388343"
  },
  {
    "id": "600023",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600023 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "600025",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600025 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "600026",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 600026: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "600027",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600027 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600027 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "600028",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600028 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "111087634"
  },
  {
    "id": "600029",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600029 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "600030",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600030 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600031",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600031 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "600032",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600032 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600033",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600033 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "600035",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600035, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "600036",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600036 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600036 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "600037",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600037? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "600038",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600038 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "600039",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600039 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "600048",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600048? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "600050",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600050 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "600051",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600051 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "600052",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600052 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600053",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600053? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "600054",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600054, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "600055",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600055 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4590214"
  },
  {
    "id": "600056",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600056 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600056 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600057",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600057 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "600058",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600058 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600059",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600059 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "600060",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600060 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "600061",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600061, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "600062",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600062 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "600063",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600063 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "600064",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600064 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "600066",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600066. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12990278"
  },
  {
    "id": "600067",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600067: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "22119609"
  },
  {
    "id": "600071",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600071. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "600072",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600072 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "600073",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600073 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13402674"
  },
  {
    "id": "600075",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600075? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "600076",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600076 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600078",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600078? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "600079",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600079 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600080",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600080 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600081",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 600081 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "36914687"
  },
  {
    "id": "600082",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600082 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600082 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "600084",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600084 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "600085",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600085 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "600088",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600088. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "600089",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600089: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "600094",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600094? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "600095",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600095 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "56872780"
  },
  {
    "id": "600096",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600096 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "600097",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600097: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "3489707"
  },
  {
    "id": "600098",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600098. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600099",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600099. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "600100",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 600100 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "600101",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600101, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600103",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600103 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "600104",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600104 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "600105",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 600105 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "600106",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600106 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "600107",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600107. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600108",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600108 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "600109",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600109, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600110",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600110. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "600111",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600111 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "600113",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600113 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600113 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "600114",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600114 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-3.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "600115",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600115 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "600116",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600116 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "600117",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600117: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8695997"
  },
  {
    "id": "600118",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600118, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "14770046"
  },
  {
    "id": "600119",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600119 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "600120",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600120 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "37039522"
  },
  {
    "id": "600121",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600121: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "600123",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600123. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "600125",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600125? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "600126",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600126 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-3.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "600127",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600127? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "600128",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600128 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "600129",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600129 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "600130",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600130 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "600131",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600131. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "600132",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600132 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "600133",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600133 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "600135",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600135, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7522115"
  },
  {
    "id": "600136",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600136. Its latest stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "600137",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600137 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13228049"
  },
  {
    "id": "600138",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600138 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6614434"
  },
  {
    "id": "600141",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600141. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "600143",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600143 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600143 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "600148",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600148 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600148 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "600149",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600149 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "600150",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600150: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "600151",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600151 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "600152",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 600152: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "600153",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600153 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600155",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600155, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "600156",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600156, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "600157",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600157. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "600158",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600158, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "600159",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600159 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "600160",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600160 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "600161",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600161 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12536547"
  },
  {
    "id": "600162",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600162? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "600163",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600163 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600165",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600165 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-3.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "600166",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600166, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "600167",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600167 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600168",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600168 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "600169",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600169 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "600170",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600170 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "600171",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600171 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "14934077"
  },
  {
    "id": "600172",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600172: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "600173",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600173 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "600176",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600176, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "15046902"
  },
  {
    "id": "600177",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600177. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "600178",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600178: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "30505032"
  },
  {
    "id": "600179",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600179, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "54874060"
  },
  {
    "id": "600180",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600180 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "600182",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600182 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1588081"
  },
  {
    "id": "600183",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600183 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600183 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "600184",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600184 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600185",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600185 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600185 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "17273275"
  },
  {
    "id": "600186",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600186. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "600187",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600187 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "600188",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600188, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "600189",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600189. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "600190",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600190 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "600191",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600191 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600192",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600192 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "600193",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600193 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "600195",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600195 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11783585"
  },
  {
    "id": "600196",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600196 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "600197",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600197 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600197 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600198",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600198, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "600199",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600199. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "15030104"
  },
  {
    "id": "600200",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600200 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "600201",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600201 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "600202",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600202 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600203",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600203 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "600206",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 600206 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "600207",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 600207 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "48706090"
  },
  {
    "id": "600208",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600208 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "59520419"
  },
  {
    "id": "600210",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600210 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "600211",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600211. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "600212",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600212 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "600215",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600215 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "600216",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600216 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600216 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "48814709"
  },
  {
    "id": "600217",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600217. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600218",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600218 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "600219",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600219: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "600221",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600221 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "600222",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600222, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600223",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600223? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "600226",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600226 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "26114268"
  },
  {
    "id": "600227",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 600227 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "19230513"
  },
  {
    "id": "600228",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600228 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 600228 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "600229",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600229. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "600230",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600230 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600230 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "600231",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600231 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "600232",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600232 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "600233",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600233, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600234",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600234 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "600235",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600235 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600236",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600236 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "600237",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600237 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "600238",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600238 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "600239",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600239, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "600241",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600241 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 600241 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "600243",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600243 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "600246",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600246 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "33688322"
  },
  {
    "id": "600248",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600248 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "15404296"
  },
  {
    "id": "600249",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600249. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "600250",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600250 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "600251",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600251 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600251 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "600252",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600252 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "600255",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600255 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600256",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600256 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "600257",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 600257 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "600258",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600258. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600259",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600259, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "41.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "600261",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600261 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 600261 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "600262",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600262 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "600265",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600265, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "600266",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600266? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "600267",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600267 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600267 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "16549427"
  },
  {
    "id": "600268",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600268: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "14935631"
  },
  {
    "id": "600269",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600269. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600271",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600271 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "600272",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600272 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "600273",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600273, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11037315"
  },
  {
    "id": "600276",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600276 calculated on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "41538641"
  },
  {
    "id": "600278",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600278 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "600279",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600279. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "61983430"
  },
  {
    "id": "600280",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600280: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "600281",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600281, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "600282",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of stock price 600282? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "600283",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600283 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "600284",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600284 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "600285",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600285 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "600287",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600287 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "600288",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600288, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600289",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600289 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "600292",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600292 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "600293",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600293 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "600295",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600295 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "600298",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600298 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "600299",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600299 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "600300",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600300 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "600301",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600301 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "600302",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600302 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7222340"
  },
  {
    "id": "600303",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600303, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "600305",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600305 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600305 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "600307",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600307. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "20059950"
  },
  {
    "id": "600308",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600308 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "600309",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600309 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "600310",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600310 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600312",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600312 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "600313",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600313: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "600315",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600315 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-3.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "600316",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600316. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5898204"
  },
  {
    "id": "600318",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600318 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "600319",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600319 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "600320",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 600320 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "600322",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600322: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "600323",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600323 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "600325",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600325 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "17924031"
  },
  {
    "id": "600326",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600326, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "600327",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600327 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "600328",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600328 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5836330"
  },
  {
    "id": "600329",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600329 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "600330",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600330 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9935762"
  },
  {
    "id": "600331",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600331 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "600332",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600332 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600333",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600333. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "600335",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600335: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "600336",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600336: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "600337",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600337 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "26916136"
  },
  {
    "id": "600338",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600338 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600339",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600339 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "600340",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600340. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "600343",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600343 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "600345",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600345. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "600346",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average volume indicator for stock 600346 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6550998"
  },
  {
    "id": "600348",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600348 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600348 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "600350",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price 600350: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600351",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600351 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "600352",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600352 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "600353",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600353 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600353 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "600354",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600354, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600355",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600355 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "600356",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600356 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "600358",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600358 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "600359",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 600359 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9149314"
  },
  {
    "id": "600360",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600360 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "600361",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600361 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "600362",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600362. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "600363",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600363 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "600365",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600365 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6013093"
  },
  {
    "id": "600366",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600366 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "600367",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600367 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "600368",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600368 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "24545730"
  },
  {
    "id": "600369",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600369. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "600370",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600370 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "600371",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600371 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "600372",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600372: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "600373",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600373? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "600375",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600375 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600375 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "77365556"
  },
  {
    "id": "600376",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600376, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "600377",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 600377: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "600378",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600378 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "3263673"
  },
  {
    "id": "600379",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600379 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "600380",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600380, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "15319388"
  },
  {
    "id": "600381",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600381 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "600382",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600382: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "600383",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600383 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "600386",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 600386 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "600388",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600388 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600389",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600389 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "600390",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600390 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "600391",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600391 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600392",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600392? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "600395",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600395 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8765445"
  },
  {
    "id": "600396",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600396 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600397",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600397 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "600398",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600398 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "600399",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600399 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "600400",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent share price of stock 600400 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600403",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600403 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600403 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "600405",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600405. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "600406",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600406 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600406 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "600408",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600408: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "600409",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600409. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "600410",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600410 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "86594304"
  },
  {
    "id": "600415",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 600415: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "600416",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600416 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "19991199"
  },
  {
    "id": "600418",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600418 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "74614504"
  },
  {
    "id": "600419",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600419, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "600420",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 600420 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "600421",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600421 calculated on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6589120"
  },
  {
    "id": "600422",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600422 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8217783"
  },
  {
    "id": "600423",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600423 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600425",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 600425 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "600426",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600426 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11439730"
  },
  {
    "id": "600428",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600428 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600428 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "600429",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600429: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "600433",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600433, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "600435",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600435, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "600436",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600436 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "204.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "600438",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600438 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600438 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "28589444"
  },
  {
    "id": "600439",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600439 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "600444",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600444 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600444 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "600446",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600446 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "600448",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600448 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-5.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "600449",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600449, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10782653"
  },
  {
    "id": "600452",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600452 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "600455",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600455? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "600456",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600456 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "600458",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600458 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "600459",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600459 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "600460",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600460, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "600461",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600461, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5548644"
  },
  {
    "id": "600463",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600463 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "25146851"
  },
  {
    "id": "600467",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600467 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "600468",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600468 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "212478399"
  },
  {
    "id": "600469",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600469. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "600470",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600470: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "600475",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600475 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9705179"
  },
  {
    "id": "600476",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of stock price 600476 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600477",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600477 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600477 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "14595982"
  },
  {
    "id": "600478",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600478? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "600479",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600479? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600480",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 600480 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "600481",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600481. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "600482",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600482? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "600483",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600483 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "600486",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600486, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "600487",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600487 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600488",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600488? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "600489",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600489? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "600490",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600490 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "600491",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600491 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "600493",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600493 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600493 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "30405203"
  },
  {
    "id": "600495",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600495? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "600496",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600496 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12228410"
  },
  {
    "id": "600497",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600497, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "600498",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600498? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "600499",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600499 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600499 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "600500",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600500. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "18356104"
  },
  {
    "id": "600501",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600501: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "600502",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600502, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "600503",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600503 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of the stock price of stock 600503 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "600505",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600505? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "600506",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600506 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "600507",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600507? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600508",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600508 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600508 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600509",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600509 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600509 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "600510",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600510. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "600511",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600511? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "600512",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600512 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600513",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600513 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600515",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600515 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "35298784"
  },
  {
    "id": "600516",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600516 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10785197"
  },
  {
    "id": "600517",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600517 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600518",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600518 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600518 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "600519",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600519, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1538.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "600520",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600520 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "600521",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600521: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "600522",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600522 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "600523",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600523 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "600525",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600525. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12461452"
  },
  {
    "id": "600526",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600526. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "600527",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600527 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600527 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600528",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600528 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "600529",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 600529 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8082338"
  },
  {
    "id": "600530",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600530 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-4.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "600531",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600531 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600533",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600533 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "600535",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600535. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600536",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600536 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "45.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "600537",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600537, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "600538",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600538 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "600539",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600539, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "600540",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600540 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "600543",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600543 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "600545",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600545 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "30882596"
  },
  {
    "id": "600546",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600546 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600546 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "600547",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600547 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "20763079"
  },
  {
    "id": "600548",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600548 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "600549",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600549 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "16708455"
  },
  {
    "id": "600550",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600550 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600550 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "600551",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600551? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "600552",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600552: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "600556",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600556 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "600557",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600557 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "600558",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600558 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "600559",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600559 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7612596"
  },
  {
    "id": "600560",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600560? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "600561",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600561 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "600562",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600562 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "600563",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600563 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "102.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "600566",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600566 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "600567",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600567: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "84656621"
  },
  {
    "id": "600568",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of stock price 600568? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "600569",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600569 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "600570",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600570 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "600571",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600571 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "37607843"
  },
  {
    "id": "600572",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600572, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "28466039"
  },
  {
    "id": "600573",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600573? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "600575",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600575, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "600576",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600576 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600577",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600577. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "600578",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600578: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "39140727"
  },
  {
    "id": "600579",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600579 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13171656"
  },
  {
    "id": "600580",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600580, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "600581",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600581. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600582",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600582 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600582 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600583",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600583 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600583 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600584",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600584 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13570065"
  },
  {
    "id": "600585",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600585, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "600586",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600586, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600587",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 600587 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6131740"
  },
  {
    "id": "600588",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600588: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "600589",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600589 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "600590",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600590 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-4.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "600592",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600592 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600593",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600593 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "600594",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600594 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "600595",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600595 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "25854561"
  },
  {
    "id": "600596",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600596 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "14284669"
  },
  {
    "id": "600597",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600597, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "600598",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600598 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "17907829"
  },
  {
    "id": "600599",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600599 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600599 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "600600",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average volume indicator for stock 600600 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8823187"
  },
  {
    "id": "600601",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600601: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600602",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600602 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "21259934"
  },
  {
    "id": "600603",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600603 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "600604",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600604, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "600605",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600605 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600605 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600606",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600606. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "38619388"
  },
  {
    "id": "600608",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600608 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4243616"
  },
  {
    "id": "600609",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600609: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "600610",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600610 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600610 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "600611",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600611 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "600612",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600612? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "600613",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600613 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "600615",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600615? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "600616",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600616: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-5.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "600617",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600617, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "600618",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600618 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4430313"
  },
  {
    "id": "600619",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600619 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "600620",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600620 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600621",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600621 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "16216852"
  },
  {
    "id": "600622",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600622 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "600623",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600623? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "600624",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600624 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600624 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600626",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600626? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600628",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600628 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "600629",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600629 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "18100420"
  },
  {
    "id": "600630",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600630 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "600633",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600633 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "600635",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600635. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "600636",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600636 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "600637",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 600637 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600638",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600638 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "600639",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600639 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "600640",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600640. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "600641",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600641: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600642",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600642? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "600643",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600643, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "600644",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600644. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-4.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "600645",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 600645 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8622478"
  },
  {
    "id": "600648",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600648 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "600649",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600649 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "14240247"
  },
  {
    "id": "600650",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600650? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "600651",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 600651 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "600653",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600653? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "600654",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600654 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "26281704"
  },
  {
    "id": "600655",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600655 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "16511169"
  },
  {
    "id": "600657",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600657 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "600658",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600658. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "600660",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600660 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600661",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600661? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "600662",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600662 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "600663",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600663 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "600664",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600664, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "600665",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600665 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "600666",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600666 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "600667",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600667 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "600668",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600668. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "600671",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600671 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "600673",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600673 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12483697"
  },
  {
    "id": "600674",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600674 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 600674 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "600675",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600675, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "600676",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600676, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "600678",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600678 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "600679",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600679? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "600681",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600681 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "600682",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600682 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "600683",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600683? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "600684",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600684. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600685",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600685 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600685 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7568818"
  },
  {
    "id": "600686",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600686 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "600688",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600688? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "600689",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600689 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "3739714"
  },
  {
    "id": "600690",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600690 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "600691",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 600691 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "18234417"
  },
  {
    "id": "600692",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600692, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6022540"
  },
  {
    "id": "600693",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600693 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "600694",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600694 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "600696",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600696 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600697",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600697 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5484580"
  },
  {
    "id": "600698",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: After careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600698 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "600699",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600699 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "36559340"
  },
  {
    "id": "600702",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600702 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "600703",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600703 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600703 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "25569510"
  },
  {
    "id": "600704",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600704 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "600706",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600706 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600706 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "600707",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600707 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "600708",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600708 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600708 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "600710",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600710: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "600711",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600711 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "600712",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600712 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600713",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600713. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600714",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600714 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "600715",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600715 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600715 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "600716",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 600716 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8534140"
  },
  {
    "id": "600717",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 600717 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "14373727"
  },
  {
    "id": "600718",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600718 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "600719",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600719 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600720",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600720 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "600721",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600721, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "600722",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600722 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "600724",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600724 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "600725",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600725 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "600726",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 600726 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "600727",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600727 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "600728",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600728 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "27948175"
  },
  {
    "id": "600729",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600729 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "600730",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600730: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10332521"
  },
  {
    "id": "600731",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600731 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "600732",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600732 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "600733",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of stock price of stock 600733: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "600734",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600734 calculated on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "36953300"
  },
  {
    "id": "600735",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600735 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "34724254"
  },
  {
    "id": "600736",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600736 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "600737",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600737 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600738",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600738, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "600739",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600739 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "600740",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600740 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9731269"
  },
  {
    "id": "600741",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600741, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "600742",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600742 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "600743",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600743. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "600744",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600744 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "121473268"
  },
  {
    "id": "600745",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600745 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "600746",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600746 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "600748",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600748 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6610727"
  },
  {
    "id": "600749",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600749. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "600750",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600750. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "600751",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600751 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "600753",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600753, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "600754",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600754, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600755",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600755. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12527451"
  },
  {
    "id": "600756",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600756, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600757",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600757, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "600758",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600758 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600759",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600759 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "600760",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600760 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "600761",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600761 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "600763",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600763 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "600764",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600764 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600764 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "600765",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 600765: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "600768",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600768? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "600769",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600769 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4300764"
  },
  {
    "id": "600770",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600770 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "151125706"
  },
  {
    "id": "600771",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600771 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "600773",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600773 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "600774",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600774: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9037936"
  },
  {
    "id": "600775",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600775 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600775 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "600776",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600776 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6011559"
  },
  {
    "id": "600778",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600778 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11021081"
  },
  {
    "id": "600779",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600779: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "600780",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600780 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "600782",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 600782: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "600783",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600783? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "600784",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600784? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "600785",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 600785 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600787",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600787 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600787 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "134905470"
  },
  {
    "id": "600789",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of stock price of stock 600789: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "600790",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600790? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "600791",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600791 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6624930"
  },
  {
    "id": "600792",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600792 calculated on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7111680"
  },
  {
    "id": "600793",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600793. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "600794",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600794, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "600795",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600795 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600796",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600796 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "600797",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600797 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "42895019"
  },
  {
    "id": "600798",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600798 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "600800",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600800 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "600801",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600801? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "600802",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 600802 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5339625"
  },
  {
    "id": "600803",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 600803 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "600805",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600805 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600807",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600807 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "600808",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600808 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "600809",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600809 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5122974"
  },
  {
    "id": "600810",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600810 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "600812",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600812. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "600814",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600814 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600814 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "600815",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600815 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "600816",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600816 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "600817",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600817? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600818",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600818? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "600819",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600819 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "600820",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600820, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "23722945"
  },
  {
    "id": "600821",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600821 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "600822",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600822 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "600824",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600824 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "600825",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600825, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10830066"
  },
  {
    "id": "600826",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600826 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 600826 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "600827",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600827 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "600828",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 600828 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "600829",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600829 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "600830",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600830 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "600831",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600831 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600831 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "600833",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600833. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "600834",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600834 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600835",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600835 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600835 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13753650"
  },
  {
    "id": "600838",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600838? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "600839",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600839 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 600839 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "600841",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600841. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "600843",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600843: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "600844",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600844? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "24896380"
  },
  {
    "id": "600845",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600845 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "600846",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600846, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "600847",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600847, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "600848",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600848. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "600850",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600850: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "600851",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600851? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "600853",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600853 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "600854",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600854 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "600855",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600855 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "600857",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600857 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "600858",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600858 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "600859",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600859 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "600860",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600860 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "600861",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600861. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1807128"
  },
  {
    "id": "600862",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600862 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "600863",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600863. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "600864",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600864 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "600865",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600865? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "600866",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600866 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "600867",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 600867 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "600868",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600868 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "600869",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600869 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "600871",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600871: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "600872",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600872 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9621224"
  },
  {
    "id": "600873",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of stock price of stock 600873: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "600874",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 600874 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "600875",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600875 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "600876",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 600876 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2194942"
  },
  {
    "id": "600877",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600877 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "600879",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 600879 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "600880",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600880 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "52370169"
  },
  {
    "id": "600881",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600881 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "600882",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600882 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "600883",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600883 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600883 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5079482"
  },
  {
    "id": "600884",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600884 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "600885",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 600885: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "3804353"
  },
  {
    "id": "600886",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600886 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "600887",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600887 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "600888",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600888 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "600889",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600889. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13490461"
  },
  {
    "id": "600892",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600892 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "600893",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600893, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "19479609"
  },
  {
    "id": "600894",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600894. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "600895",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600895? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "600897",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600897. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "600900",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600900? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "600901",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600901? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "600903",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600903 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "600905",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600905 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "600906",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600906. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10774881"
  },
  {
    "id": "600908",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600908? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "600909",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600909 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "600916",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600916, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "600917",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600917 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600918",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600918 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "600919",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600919. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "85899840"
  },
  {
    "id": "600925",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600925 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5902492"
  },
  {
    "id": "600926",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 600926 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "93343279"
  },
  {
    "id": "600927",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600927? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "600928",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600928 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "600929",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600929, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "600933",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600933 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9642141"
  },
  {
    "id": "600935",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600935 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "600936",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600936? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "600938",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 600938 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "21798369"
  },
  {
    "id": "600939",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600939 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "600941",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600941? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "115.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "600955",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600955 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600955 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "600956",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600956 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "600958",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600958 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "600959",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600959 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "600960",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600960? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "600961",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600961 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "600962",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600962 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "600963",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 600963 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "600965",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600965, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "600966",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600966 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "600967",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent 20-day moving average of stock price for stock 600967 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "600968",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600968 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "600969",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of stock price 600969? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "600970",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 600970 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "600971",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600971, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "600973",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 600973 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "600975",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 600975 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "600976",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600976 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "600977",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600977 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "600979",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600979 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "31391659"
  },
  {
    "id": "600980",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 600980 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "600981",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 600981 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "600982",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 600982: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "600983",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600983 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2364580"
  },
  {
    "id": "600984",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600984 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600984 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12939430"
  },
  {
    "id": "600985",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 600985. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "600986",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 600986 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "600987",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600987 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "600988",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600988? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-3.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "600989",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of stock price 600989? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "600990",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 600990? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "600992",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 600992, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "600993",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600993 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 600993 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4814583"
  },
  {
    "id": "600995",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 600995 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "600996",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600996 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600996 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "600997",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 600997 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5780438"
  },
  {
    "id": "600998",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 600998 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 600998 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "600999",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 600999 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "601000",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601000 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "601001",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601001 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 601001 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "601002",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601002 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 601002 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "601003",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601003 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "601005",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601005 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "601006",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601006, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "601007",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601007 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9719294"
  },
  {
    "id": "601008",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601008, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "601009",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601009? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "601010",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601010 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "601011",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 601011 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "601012",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601012 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "601015",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601015, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "601016",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 601016 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "601018",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601018. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "601019",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 601019 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "601020",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601020, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "601021",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601021 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601021 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "601022",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601022 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "601033",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 601033 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "601038",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601038 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "601058",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601058 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "601059",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601059 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12055492"
  },
  {
    "id": "601061",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 601061 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "601065",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601065 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "601066",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601066 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "601068",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601068 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "601069",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601069 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "28029439"
  },
  {
    "id": "601077",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601077 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601077 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "601083",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601083 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "601086",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601086 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "601088",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601088 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 601088 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "16481484"
  },
  {
    "id": "601089",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601089: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "601096",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601096 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "601098",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601098 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "601099",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 601099 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "601100",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601100 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "601101",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601101: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "601106",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601106. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "601107",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 601107 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "601108",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601108 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "21223660"
  },
  {
    "id": "601111",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601111 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "57619917"
  },
  {
    "id": "601113",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601113 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "601116",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601116, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "601117",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 601117: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "601118",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601118 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "601121",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601121: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "601126",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601126 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "601127",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601127 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "132.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "601128",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 601128 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "43583339"
  },
  {
    "id": "601133",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 601133 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "3496106"
  },
  {
    "id": "601136",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601136 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11111656"
  },
  {
    "id": "601137",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601137: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "601138",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601138? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "601139",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601139 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6261820"
  },
  {
    "id": "601155",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601155. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "601158",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 601158 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "601162",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601162 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "92456442"
  },
  {
    "id": "601163",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601163 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 601163 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2083813"
  },
  {
    "id": "601166",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601166 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601166 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "601168",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601168: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "601169",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 601169 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "601177",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601177 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601177 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "601179",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601179 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601179 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "601186",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601186? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "601188",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601188? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "601198",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601198 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 601198 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "601199",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601199. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "601200",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601200 calculated on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7635480"
  },
  {
    "id": "601208",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 601208 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "601211",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 601211 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "31115175"
  },
  {
    "id": "601212",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 601212 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "601216",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 601216 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "601218",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 601218 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "601222",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601222, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11637412"
  },
  {
    "id": "601225",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 601225 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "601226",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601226 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "601228",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601228 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "601229",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601229. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "601231",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601231 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "601233",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 601233 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12895076"
  },
  {
    "id": "601236",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601236 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "601238",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601238 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 601238 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "601279",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601279 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "601288",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601288 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "601298",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601298 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "601311",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601311. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "601318",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 601318 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "33429482"
  },
  {
    "id": "601319",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601319 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601319 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "601326",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601326. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12531204"
  },
  {
    "id": "601328",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601328. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "601330",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 601330 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11406078"
  },
  {
    "id": "601333",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601333: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "601336",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 601336 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "601339",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 601339 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-4.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "601360",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 601360 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "46168969"
  },
  {
    "id": "601366",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601366? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "601368",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601368, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "601369",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 601369 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "601375",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601375 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "21617197"
  },
  {
    "id": "601377",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601377. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "601388",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601388 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "601390",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601390 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "601398",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601398 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "601399",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601399? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "601456",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601456 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "18475554"
  },
  {
    "id": "601500",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601500. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "601512",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601512? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "601515",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601515 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "30903371"
  },
  {
    "id": "601518",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 601518 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11273464"
  },
  {
    "id": "601519",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601519 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "601528",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601528 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "601555",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601555 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "601566",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601566, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "601567",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 601567: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "601568",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601568: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "601577",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 601577 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "27294098"
  },
  {
    "id": "601579",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601579 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "601588",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601588 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13207870"
  },
  {
    "id": "601595",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601595. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "601598",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 601598 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "17677222"
  },
  {
    "id": "601599",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601599 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "16613762"
  },
  {
    "id": "601600",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601600 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 601600 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "103029194"
  },
  {
    "id": "601601",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601601. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "26360513"
  },
  {
    "id": "601606",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601606 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "601607",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601607 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "601608",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601608. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "601609",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601609 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "601611",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601611: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "601615",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601615 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "601616",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 601616 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "601618",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 601618 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "601619",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601619 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "601628",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601628 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "601633",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601633 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "601636",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 601636 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13093187"
  },
  {
    "id": "601658",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601658 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "116335231"
  },
  {
    "id": "601665",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601665 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 601665 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "601666",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601666 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "601668",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601668. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "124752500"
  },
  {
    "id": "601669",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 601669 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "38830567"
  },
  {
    "id": "601677",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601677. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "601678",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601678 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601678 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "601686",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 601686 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "601688",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601688 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601688 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "601689",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601689. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "601696",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601696 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10387410"
  },
  {
    "id": "601698",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601698 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "601699",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601699 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "601700",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 601700 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "601702",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601702 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "601717",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601717 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "601718",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601718 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 601718 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "27972107"
  },
  {
    "id": "601727",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601727. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "601728",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601728 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601728 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "601766",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601766 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "601777",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of stock price of stock 601777: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "601778",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601778 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "601788",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601788 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601788 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "601789",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601789 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "601798",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 601798 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10766040"
  },
  {
    "id": "601799",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601799 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "140.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "601800",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average volume indicator for stock 601800 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "15864797"
  },
  {
    "id": "601801",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601801 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "601808",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601808 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5558287"
  },
  {
    "id": "601811",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 601811 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "601816",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601816? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "601818",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 601818 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "601825",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601825 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "601827",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601827? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "601828",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601828 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "601838",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601838 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average value of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "601857",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601857: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "601858",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601858, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "14073740"
  },
  {
    "id": "601860",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601860 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "601865",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601865, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "601866",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601866 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "142093243"
  },
  {
    "id": "601868",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601868 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 601868 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "601869",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 601869 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2545115"
  },
  {
    "id": "601872",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601872 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "601877",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601877 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "601878",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601878 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "601880",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601880? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "601881",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601881. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "601882",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601882 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601882 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "601886",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601886, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7405161"
  },
  {
    "id": "601888",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601888: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "601890",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 601890 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "601898",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601898: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "601899",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601899. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.93"
  },
  {
    "id": "601900",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601900, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "601901",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 601901: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "21248947"
  },
  {
    "id": "601908",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 601908 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-3.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "601916",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601916? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "601918",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601918 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "601919",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 601919, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "601921",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601921 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "601928",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601928. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8503653"
  },
  {
    "id": "601929",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601929 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601929 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "601933",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601933. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "601939",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601939 calculated on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "55577815"
  },
  {
    "id": "601949",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601949 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601949 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "601952",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601952 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601952 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "601956",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 601956 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "91684307"
  },
  {
    "id": "601958",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601958? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "601963",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601963? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "601965",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601965 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 601965 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "601966",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 601966 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "601968",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 601968. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "601969",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601969 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8032468"
  },
  {
    "id": "601975",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601975 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "601985",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 601985: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "601988",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 601988 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "601989",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601989 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "601990",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 601990 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10598242"
  },
  {
    "id": "601991",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601991: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "601992",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 601992 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "601995",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 601995 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "33.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "601996",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 601996 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "601997",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 601997 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "601998",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 601998 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 601998 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "601999",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 601999: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "603000",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603000 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 603000 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "603001",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603001: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "603002",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603002 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "603004",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603004 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603004 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "603005",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603005 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12899796"
  },
  {
    "id": "603006",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603006 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "17691790"
  },
  {
    "id": "603007",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603007. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "603008",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603008 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603008 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "603009",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603009 calculated on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "19392817"
  },
  {
    "id": "603010",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603010 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "603011",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603011 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "603012",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 603012 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7032596"
  },
  {
    "id": "603013",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603013, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "19521171"
  },
  {
    "id": "603015",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603015? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "603016",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603016: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2966094"
  },
  {
    "id": "603017",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603017 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603017 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "603018",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603018 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "603019",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603019, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "61.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "603020",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603020 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "603021",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603021 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "603022",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603022 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.88"
  },
  {
    "id": "603023",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603023 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7972659"
  },
  {
    "id": "603025",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603025 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2475258"
  },
  {
    "id": "603026",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603026 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "603027",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of stock price of stock 603027: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "603028",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603028. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "603029",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603029 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "603030",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603030 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of the stock price of stock 603030 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603031",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603031 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "603032",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603032, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "603033",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603033 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "603035",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603035? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "603036",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603036 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "603037",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603037. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5554184"
  },
  {
    "id": "603038",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603038 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "603039",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603039 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "603040",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 603040 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "603041",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603041: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12657180"
  },
  {
    "id": "603042",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603042 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "603043",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603043 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603045",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603045 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "603048",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603048 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603048 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.40"
  },
  {
    "id": "603050",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 603050 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "603051",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 603051 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "603052",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603052 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603052 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "603053",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603053 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "603055",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603055 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "603056",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603056 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "603057",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603057 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "603058",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603058. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "603059",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 603059 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603060",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603060 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "603061",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603061 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "79.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "603062",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603062 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "603063",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603063. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "603065",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 603065 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "34003067"
  },
  {
    "id": "603066",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603066 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "603067",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603067, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603068",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603068 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603068 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "603069",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 603069 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "603070",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603070 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "603071",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 603071 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "603072",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 603072 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "603073",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603073 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of the stock price of stock 603073 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "603075",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603075 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "603076",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 603076 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "603077",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603077: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "72232777"
  },
  {
    "id": "603078",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603078 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "603079",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603079 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "603080",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 603080 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "603081",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 603081 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "603082",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603082, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "603083",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603083. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "603085",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603085, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7644920"
  },
  {
    "id": "603086",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603086 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 603086 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-3.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "603087",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 603087 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "50.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "603088",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603088. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "603089",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603089 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "603090",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603090 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "603091",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603091? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "603093",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603093. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "603095",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603095 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "603096",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603096, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "603097",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603097 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "603098",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603098 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "603099",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603099 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "603100",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603100 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "603101",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603101 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 603101 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "17577246"
  },
  {
    "id": "603102",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603102: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "3341562"
  },
  {
    "id": "603103",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603103 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603105",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603105 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "603106",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603106 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "603107",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603107, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "603108",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603108 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "603109",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603109 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603110",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603110: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "603111",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603111 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "603112",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603112 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "603113",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603113. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "603115",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603115. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2191480"
  },
  {
    "id": "603116",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603116 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "603117",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603117 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "603118",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603118 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "603119",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603119 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603121",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603121 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603121 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "603122",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603122 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "603123",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603123 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "603125",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603125 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6664864"
  },
  {
    "id": "603126",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603126 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "603127",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average volume indicator for stock 603127 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "37225287"
  },
  {
    "id": "603128",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603128 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "54327523"
  },
  {
    "id": "603129",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603129. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "179.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "603130",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603130. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603131",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603131? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "603132",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603132 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "603135",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603135? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-5.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "603136",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603136 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.65"
  },
  {
    "id": "603137",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603137 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "603138",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603138 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "603139",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 603139 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603150",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603150 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "603151",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603151. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "603153",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603153 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "603155",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603155 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2053512"
  },
  {
    "id": "603156",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 603156 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2904310"
  },
  {
    "id": "603158",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603158 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603159",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 603159 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "603160",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603160? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "603161",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603161 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "603162",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603162 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603163",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603163 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "603165",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603165. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "603166",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 603166 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "603167",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603167 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "603168",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603168 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7168535"
  },
  {
    "id": "603169",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 603169 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "603170",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603170 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "603171",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603171, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "42.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "603172",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603172 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1545627"
  },
  {
    "id": "603173",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603173: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.35"
  },
  {
    "id": "603176",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603176 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "603177",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603177 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603178",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603178: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "603179",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603179 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5445179"
  },
  {
    "id": "603180",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603180 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "876692"
  },
  {
    "id": "603181",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603181, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "603182",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603182 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its stock price 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "603183",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603183: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "603185",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603185 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "603186",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 603186 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "603187",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 603187: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603188",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603188: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12325163"
  },
  {
    "id": "603189",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603189 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7669620"
  },
  {
    "id": "603190",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603190. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1433774"
  },
  {
    "id": "603191",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603191 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603191 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "603192",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603192 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603193",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603193 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "603194",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603194. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7912143"
  },
  {
    "id": "603195",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603195 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1573095"
  },
  {
    "id": "603196",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603196 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "603197",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603197 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 603197 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5526853"
  },
  {
    "id": "603198",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603198: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5966988"
  },
  {
    "id": "603199",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603199 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "603200",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603200 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7448742"
  },
  {
    "id": "603201",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603201. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "603203",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603203 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1324791"
  },
  {
    "id": "603205",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603205 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 603205 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2196718"
  },
  {
    "id": "603206",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603206: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "603207",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603207 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "603208",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603208, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "603209",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603209, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "603211",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603211 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "603212",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603212? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "603213",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603213 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "603214",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603214, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "603215",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603215 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "603216",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603216? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "603217",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603217 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "603218",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603218 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5912413"
  },
  {
    "id": "603219",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603219 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "603220",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 603220 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "603221",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603221 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603222",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603222. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603223",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603223 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "603225",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603225 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.38"
  },
  {
    "id": "603226",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603226 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603226 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "603227",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603227 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "603228",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603228, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "603229",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603229 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "603230",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603230 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "603231",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603231 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "603232",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603232 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "24070457"
  },
  {
    "id": "603233",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603233 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6736936"
  },
  {
    "id": "603235",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603235 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "603236",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603236 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "603237",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603237 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "12821010"
  },
  {
    "id": "603238",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603238. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603239",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603239. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.61"
  },
  {
    "id": "603255",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603255 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1389824"
  },
  {
    "id": "603256",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603256: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "18033308"
  },
  {
    "id": "603258",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603258 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "603259",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603259 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603259 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "62.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "603260",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603260 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 603260 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1131892"
  },
  {
    "id": "603261",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603261: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "603266",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603266 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4907828"
  },
  {
    "id": "603267",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603267 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.18"
  },
  {
    "id": "603268",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603268 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "40.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "603269",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603269 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "603270",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603270 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603270 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "603272",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603272? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "603273",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603273. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "603275",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 603275 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "39.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "603276",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603276 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "603277",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603277, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "603278",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of stock price of stock 603278: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "603279",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603279: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "603280",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 603280 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "603281",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 603281 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603282",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 603282 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603283",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603283 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "43.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "603285",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603285 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "603286",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 603286 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "603288",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603288 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13012743"
  },
  {
    "id": "603289",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603289 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "603290",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603290 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.96"
  },
  {
    "id": "603291",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603291 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "603296",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 603296 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "70.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "603297",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603297 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "603298",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603298 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "603299",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603299 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "603300",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603300 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "603301",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603301 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "603303",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603303 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.99"
  },
  {
    "id": "603305",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603305: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "603306",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603306 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "603307",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603307 calculated on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "725563"
  },
  {
    "id": "603308",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603308 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "603309",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603309 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "603310",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603310 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.83"
  },
  {
    "id": "603311",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603311 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "603312",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603312, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "861432"
  },
  {
    "id": "603313",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603313 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "16682389"
  },
  {
    "id": "603315",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603315 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "603316",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603316, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6299047"
  },
  {
    "id": "603317",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603317 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "603318",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603318 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 603318 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "603319",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603319 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-7.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "603320",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603320 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "603321",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603321, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11824003"
  },
  {
    "id": "603322",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 603322 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11266055"
  },
  {
    "id": "603323",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603323 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "603324",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 603324 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.27"
  },
  {
    "id": "603325",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 603325 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "91.06"
  },
  {
    "id": "603326",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603326 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "603327",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603327: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.91"
  },
  {
    "id": "603328",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603328 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "603329",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603329, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "3731190"
  },
  {
    "id": "603330",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603330 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603330 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603331",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 603331 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9583538"
  },
  {
    "id": "603332",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603332, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "39247707"
  },
  {
    "id": "603333",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 603333 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "603335",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603335 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "603336",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603336 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "603337",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603337? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "603338",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603338 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6830856"
  },
  {
    "id": "603339",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603339 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.80"
  },
  {
    "id": "603341",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603341 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "603344",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603344? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4027009"
  },
  {
    "id": "603345",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603345 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "3615070"
  },
  {
    "id": "603348",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603348: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "603350",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603350 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603350 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "603351",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603351 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603351 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "27.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "603353",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603353. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.47"
  },
  {
    "id": "603355",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603355 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603355 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "603356",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603356 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1877040"
  },
  {
    "id": "603357",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603357 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "603358",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603358 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603358 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "603359",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603359, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.49"
  },
  {
    "id": "603360",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603360. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "603363",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603363? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.33"
  },
  {
    "id": "603365",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603365 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.92"
  },
  {
    "id": "603366",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603366: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "42344612"
  },
  {
    "id": "603367",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603367 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "603368",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603368. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "603369",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 603369 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "46.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "603373",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603373: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "603375",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603375 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603375 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "34.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "603377",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 603377 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "603378",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603378 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.43"
  },
  {
    "id": "603379",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603379. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "603380",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 603380 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "603381",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603381 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.29"
  },
  {
    "id": "603383",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603383. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2439778"
  },
  {
    "id": "603385",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603385 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "603386",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 603386 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.11"
  },
  {
    "id": "603387",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603387: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "603388",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603388. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "603389",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603389 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7240091"
  },
  {
    "id": "603390",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603390, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "603391",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603391 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "603392",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603392? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "603393",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603393 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.68"
  },
  {
    "id": "603395",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603395. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "44.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "603396",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603396 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603398",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603398 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "603399",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603399 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "7029144"
  },
  {
    "id": "603408",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603408 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "603416",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603416 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "60.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "603421",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603421 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603421 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "603429",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603429: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "603439",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 603439 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.24"
  },
  {
    "id": "603444",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603444 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "603456",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603456. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "603458",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603458 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603466",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603466 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "603477",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent 20-day moving average of stock price for stock 603477 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "20.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "603486",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603486 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "55.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603488",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603488, what is its most recent 6-day stock price deviation (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "603489",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603489 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "603496",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603496 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "603499",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603499 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 603499 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "603500",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603500: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "603501",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603501 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "130.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "603505",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of stock price of stock 603505: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.73"
  },
  {
    "id": "603506",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603506 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "603507",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603507 calculated on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11822967"
  },
  {
    "id": "603508",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603508: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "603511",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603511? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.30"
  },
  {
    "id": "603515",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603515: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "603516",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 603516 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6206748"
  },
  {
    "id": "603517",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603517 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "603518",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603518 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "603519",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 20-day moving average of the most recent stock price of stock 603519 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.10"
  },
  {
    "id": "603520",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603520 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "603527",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603527 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "603528",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603528? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "603529",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603529, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "37.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "603530",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603530 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "603533",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603533 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "603535",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603535, what was its average trading volume over the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "18114027"
  },
  {
    "id": "603536",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603536. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.21"
  },
  {
    "id": "603538",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603538 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.85"
  },
  {
    "id": "603551",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603551 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "603556",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603556 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.81"
  },
  {
    "id": "603557",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603557 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "603558",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603558, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.90"
  },
  {
    "id": "603559",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603559 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "603565",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603565 on May 30: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10936684"
  },
  {
    "id": "603566",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603566, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.54"
  },
  {
    "id": "603567",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603567 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "603568",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603568 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.56"
  },
  {
    "id": "603569",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603569 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "603577",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603577 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "603578",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 603578 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "603579",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603579, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "24.57"
  },
  {
    "id": "603580",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603580. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4149482"
  },
  {
    "id": "603583",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603583. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.14"
  },
  {
    "id": "603585",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603585. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603586",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603586 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.86"
  },
  {
    "id": "603587",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603587 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "12.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "603588",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 603588 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.02"
  },
  {
    "id": "603589",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603589 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 20-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603589 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "36.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "603590",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603590 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "603595",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603595. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "18.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "603596",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603596 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "57.31"
  },
  {
    "id": "603598",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603598 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.76"
  },
  {
    "id": "603599",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603599. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "39718847"
  },
  {
    "id": "603600",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 603600 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5664460"
  },
  {
    "id": "603601",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 603601 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "20023457"
  },
  {
    "id": "603602",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603602? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "603605",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603605: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "95.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "603606",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603606 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "48.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603607",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603607 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "31.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "603608",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of stock price 603608 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "603609",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603609 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "603610",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603610 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603610 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "603611",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603611. Its average trading volume in the last 5 days from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "25862779"
  },
  {
    "id": "603612",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average volume indicator for stock 603612 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5476733"
  },
  {
    "id": "603613",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603613 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "603615",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603615 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "21.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "603616",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603616 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "603617",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603617 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603617 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.32"
  },
  {
    "id": "603618",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603618 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.26"
  },
  {
    "id": "603619",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603619 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "603626",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603626 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "603628",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603628 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2637331"
  },
  {
    "id": "603629",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603629. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "603630",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603630, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "603633",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603633, what was its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.17"
  },
  {
    "id": "603636",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603636 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9474395"
  },
  {
    "id": "603637",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603637 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "603638",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 603638 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.19"
  },
  {
    "id": "603639",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603639, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.28"
  },
  {
    "id": "603648",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603648 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 603648 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6840340"
  },
  {
    "id": "603650",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603650 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603655",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603655, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.72"
  },
  {
    "id": "603656",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603656 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2002828"
  },
  {
    "id": "603657",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603657 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "603658",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603658 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "603659",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603659, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "16.08"
  },
  {
    "id": "603660",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603660 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "603661",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603661 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 603661 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "603662",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603662 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.64"
  },
  {
    "id": "603663",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 603663 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603665",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603665 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "22.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "603666",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the calculated 5-day average trading volume of stock 603666 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4427209"
  },
  {
    "id": "603667",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 603667 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "603668",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603668 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-2.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603669",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the calculated 5-day average trading volume of stock 603669 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "13164436"
  },
  {
    "id": "603676",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603676 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603677",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603677 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "603678",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603678 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "603679",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603679 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.00"
  },
  {
    "id": "603680",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603680, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603681",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603681 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "36751670"
  },
  {
    "id": "603682",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603682 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.05"
  },
  {
    "id": "603683",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603683 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.63"
  },
  {
    "id": "603685",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 603685 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "603686",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603686 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.55"
  },
  {
    "id": "603687",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603687 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "603688",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603688 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "30.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "603689",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603689 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.98"
  },
  {
    "id": "603690",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent 20-day moving average of stock price for stock 603690 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "25.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "603693",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603693 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "603696",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603696 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "19068816"
  },
  {
    "id": "603697",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603697, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.50"
  },
  {
    "id": "603698",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average volume indicator for stock 603698 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2815515"
  },
  {
    "id": "603699",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603699 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "28.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "603700",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603700 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "3206000"
  },
  {
    "id": "603701",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603701 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.01"
  },
  {
    "id": "603703",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603703 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "6707244"
  },
  {
    "id": "603706",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603706 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "603707",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603707 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 603707 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "14269007"
  },
  {
    "id": "603708",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603708 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4731838"
  },
  {
    "id": "603709",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average volume indicator for stock 603709 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2580378"
  },
  {
    "id": "603711",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603711 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "603712",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603712 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 603712 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "11480462"
  },
  {
    "id": "603713",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603713? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "49.82"
  },
  {
    "id": "603716",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603716 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "603717",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603717 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "6.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "603718",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day moving average indicator of the stock price of stock 603718 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "7.09"
  },
  {
    "id": "603719",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603719 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "15763914"
  },
  {
    "id": "603721",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603721 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "603722",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603722? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "38.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "603725",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603725. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-8.44"
  },
  {
    "id": "603726",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603726 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2710100"
  },
  {
    "id": "603727",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603727. Its most recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603728",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603728 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "56.87"
  },
  {
    "id": "603729",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603729. Its most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.84"
  },
  {
    "id": "603730",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603730 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "603733",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603733 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603733 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "603737",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603737? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "32.66"
  },
  {
    "id": "603738",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 603738 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "603739",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603739? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "603755",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent 20-day moving average of stock price for stock 603755 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "26.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "603757",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603757 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 603757 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1614684"
  },
  {
    "id": "603758",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 603758 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.77"
  },
  {
    "id": "603759",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average price increase and decrease (%) indicator of stock 603759 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603766",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603766 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.03"
  },
  {
    "id": "603767",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603767 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its 5-day average volume value on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "33515290"
  },
  {
    "id": "603768",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603768 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.53"
  },
  {
    "id": "603773",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average rise and fall of the stock price of stock 603773 (%): _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "603776",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603776 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603777",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603777? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.71"
  },
  {
    "id": "603778",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) indicator of stock 603778 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "603779",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603779 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.78"
  },
  {
    "id": "603786",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603786? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "54.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "603787",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603787 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "11.46"
  },
  {
    "id": "603788",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603788 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) value of stock price of stock 603788 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.89"
  },
  {
    "id": "603789",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 603789 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.60"
  },
  {
    "id": "603790",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603790, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "17.74"
  },
  {
    "id": "603797",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603797 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.41"
  },
  {
    "id": "603798",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603798 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) on May 30 as: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.04"
  },
  {
    "id": "603799",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603799 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.75"
  },
  {
    "id": "603800",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603800 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "23.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "603801",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603801 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603801 on May 30 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "603803",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603803 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.79"
  },
  {
    "id": "603806",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603806: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "9923316"
  },
  {
    "id": "603808",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603808 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4461594"
  },
  {
    "id": "603809",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 603809 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.23"
  },
  {
    "id": "603810",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603810? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.95"
  },
  {
    "id": "603811",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 20-day moving average indicator of stock price 603811 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "9.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603813",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603813 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.51"
  },
  {
    "id": "603815",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603815? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "603816",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603816 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the five-day average trading volume of stock 603816 on May 30 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4764481"
  },
  {
    "id": "603817",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603817 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "603818",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 603818 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "16510591"
  },
  {
    "id": "603819",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603819: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "15.25"
  },
  {
    "id": "603822",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 20-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603822? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "51.37"
  },
  {
    "id": "603823",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603823. Its recent 20-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "10.45"
  },
  {
    "id": "603825",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day average rise and fall (%) of the recent stock price of stock 603825 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "1.67"
  },
  {
    "id": "603826",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) of stock 603826: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-1.22"
  },
  {
    "id": "603828",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the last 5-day average trading volume of stock 603828 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "8066388"
  },
  {
    "id": "603829",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603829 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate its 5-day average trading volume on May 30 as: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "2594929"
  },
  {
    "id": "603833",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603833 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603836",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average volume indicator for stock 603836 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "4805296"
  },
  {
    "id": "603838",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603838 on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "4.69"
  },
  {
    "id": "603839",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average volume indicator for stock 603839 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "28228221"
  },
  {
    "id": "603843",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603843, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "3.15"
  },
  {
    "id": "603848",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603848, what is the 5-day average price change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.34"
  },
  {
    "id": "603855",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603855. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "19.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603856",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603856 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1403276"
  },
  {
    "id": "603858",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603858, what is the 5-day average change (%) of its recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.70"
  },
  {
    "id": "603859",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603859 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is its 6-day stock price deviation rate (BIAS6) value on May 30? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.16"
  },
  {
    "id": "603860",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603860 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.97"
  },
  {
    "id": "603861",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 5-day average trading volume indicator for stock 603861 was _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "10943036"
  },
  {
    "id": "603863",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603863 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.59"
  },
  {
    "id": "603866",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603866 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the 5-day moving average value of the stock price of stock 603866 on May 30 was _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.52"
  },
  {
    "id": "603867",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603867. Its recent 5-day average price increase or decrease (%) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "-0.12"
  },
  {
    "id": "603868",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603868 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.48"
  },
  {
    "id": "603869",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 6-day deviation rate (BIAS6) of the stock price of stock 603869 on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.94"
  },
  {
    "id": "603871",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603871 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 20-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "14.39"
  },
  {
    "id": "603876",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "For stock 603876, what is its most recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "8.58"
  },
  {
    "id": "603877",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the calculated 5-day average trading volume of stock 603877 on May 30? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "1118829"
  },
  {
    "id": "603878",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "What is the 5-day average trading volume of stock 603878 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please fill in the blank:_______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "5118139"
  },
  {
    "id": "603879",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603879 on May 30? Please fill in the blank:_______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "2.62"
  },
  {
    "id": "603880",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603880. Its recent 5-day moving average of stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "5.42"
  },
  {
    "id": "603881",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "We are analyzing the recent trend of stock 603881 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025). We need to calculate the 5-day moving average of its stock price on May 30: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.20"
  },
  {
    "id": "603882",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please calculate the 5-day moving average of the stock price of stock 603882 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025: _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "29.13"
  },
  {
    "id": "603883",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Please fill in the following blanks: Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 5-day average trading volume of stock 603883: _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "19809073"
  },
  {
    "id": "603885",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the average trading volume of stock 603885 in the last 5 days? _______. (accurate to one digit)",
    "answer": "16572338"
  },
  {
    "id": "603886",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 5-day moving average of the recent stock price of stock 603886 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Just give me the value. _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "13.07"
  },
  {
    "id": "603887",
    "type": "Fill in the blanks",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 5-day average increase or decrease (%) of the stock price of stock 603887? _______. (keep two decimal places)",
    "answer": "0.36"
  },
  {
    "id": "603888",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 603888 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? A: 37.99, B: 33.99, C: 45.99, D: 29.99.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603889",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603889. Its latest 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.08, B: 0.11, C: 0.14, D: 0.17.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603890",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 603890 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 12.11, B: 15.87, C: 14.01, D: 16.23.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603893",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 603893? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 14.2, B: 17.8, C: 19.3, D: 16.4.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603895",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 603895 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 52.86, 43.65, 71.29, B: 41.62, 33.28, 54.83, C: 65.86, 54.65, 88.29, D: 39.86, 38.65, 61.29.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603896",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 603896, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 24.16, 21.24, 18.32, B: 23.2, 21.24, 19.28, C: 21.24, 19.28, 17.32, D: 25.16, 21.24, 17.32.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603897",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 603897, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 31.26, 27.38, 23.49, B: 30.76, 26.78, 22.79, C: 32.48, 27.35, 22.22, D: 29.65, 26.32, 23.01.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603898",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 603898 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 70.12, 73.45, 68.91, B: 85.67, 81.32, 88.04, C: 65.39, 76.21, 71.83, D: 77.73, 79.01, 75.18.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603899",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603899. Its latest 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.79, B: 0.63, C: 0.95, D: 0.52.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603900",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 603900 was the value of which of the following options. A: 62.85, B: 69.65, C: 77.45, D: 55.35.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603901",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 603901 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.48, B: 0.55, C: 0.62, D: 0.75.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603903",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 603903, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 7.85, 7.22, 6.58, B: 7.12, 7.22, 7.32, C: 8.02, 7.22, 6.42, D: 7.58, 7.22, 6.85.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603906",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603906 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of stock price of stock 603906 on May 30? A: 0.7, B: 0.63, C: 0.84, D: 0.56.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603908",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 603908 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 41.62, 39.97, 45.88, B: 46.6, 44.41, 50.98, C: 51.6, 49.41, 55.98, D: 39.6, 37.41, 43.98.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603909",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 603909 from the following options. A: 0.18, B: 0.23, C: 0.21, D: 0.27.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603912",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 603912? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 30.45, B: 35.78, C: 28.67, D: 32.94.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603915",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603915 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 14-day average true range (ATR14) value on May 30? A: 0.71, B: 0.85, C: 0.55, D: 0.93.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603916",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 603916, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 9.87, 8.95, 8.03, B: 9.29, 8.67, 8.06, C: 10.11, 9.14, 8.17, D: 8.74, 8.03, 7.32.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603917",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 603917 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 32.85, B: 41.98, C: 37.93, D: 47.62.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603918",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 603918, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 17.25, 16.52, 15.79, B: 19.52, 17.84, 16.16, C: 18.12, 17.45, 16.78, D: 18.84, 17.15, 15.47.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603919",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 603919 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.38, B: 0.30, C: 0.46, D: 0.25.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603920",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 603920 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.85, B: 1.05, C: 1.25, D: 1.45.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603922",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 603922? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 60.32, B: 68.45, C: 65.51, D: 72.13.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603926",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603926 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.72, B: 0.98, C: 1.15, D: 0.87.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603927",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 603927 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 60.33, 46.05, 88.89, B: 42.23, 32.24, 62.22, C: 78.43, 59.87, 115.56, D: 36.20, 27.63, 53.33.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603928",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603928 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 603928 on May 30? A: 31.25, B: 33.16, C: 35.47, D: 29.84.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603929",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603929 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 15.8, 20.1, -5.3, C: 10.93, 17.02, -1.27, D: 8.7, 19.3, -3.4.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603931",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 603931 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 20.15, B: 24.15, C: 18.15, D: 22.15.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603933",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 603933 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: -0.18, B: -0.22, C: -0.14, D: -0.26.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603936",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603936 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 603936 on May 30? A: 0.02, B: 0.04, C: 0.06, D: 0.08.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603937",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 603937 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 11.5, 8.9, 7.3, B: 10.5, 9.2, 8.0, C: 10.0, 9.41, 8.83, D: 9.5, 9.0, 8.5.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603938",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 603938? Please select from the following options: A: 25.8, 35.7, 10.1, B: 42.1, 55.2, 17.9, C: 30.2, 40.1, 11.3, D: 36.72, 48.57, 13.02.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603939",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 603939 is the value of which of the following options. A: 33.92, B: 37.31, C: 28.56, D: 42.40.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603948",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 603948, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 18.93, 18.05, 17.17, B: 19.92, 19.05, 18.19, C: 20.82, 19.85, 18.88, D: 17.93, 17.05, 16.17.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603949",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 603949 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.38, B: 0.52, C: 0.46, D: 0.61.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603950",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 603950 from the following options. A: 20.35, B: 22.78, C: 19.86, D: 21.22.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603955",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 603955? Please select from the following options: A: 32.74, 51.3, -4.39, B: 22.92, 35.91, -6.15, C: 42.56, 66.69, -2.38, D: 19.64, 41.04, -8.78.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603956",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603956 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 31.2, 27.8, 49.5, B: 34.78, 28.18, 47.96, C: 38.2, 29.5, 51.7, D: 29.4, 26.3, 43.1.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603958",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 603958 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 52.33, B: 63.33, C: 58.33, D: 48.33.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603959",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 603959? Please select from the following options: A: 48.73, 31.98, 61.24, B: 83.54, 71.66, 97.81, C: 52.34, 48.71, 95.67, D: 69.62, 59.97, 88.92.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603960",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 603960 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: (21.33, 19.28, 17.22), B: (27.73, 25.06, 22.39), C: (15.86, 13.49, 11.12), D: (24.79, 22.12, 19.45).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603966",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 603966 on May 30 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.35, B: 0.44, C: 0.53, D: 0.28.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603967",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 603967 was the value of which of the following options. A: 12.25, B: 18.30, C: 15.25, D: 10.50.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603968",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 603968 from the following options. A: -0.15, B: 0.05, C: 0.1, D: -0.0.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603969",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 603969, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 7.68, 6.94, 6.19, B: 6.53, 6.94, 7.35, C: 8.52, 6.94, 5.35, D: 7.68, 7.94, 6.19.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603970",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 603970 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 603970 on May 30? A: 0.03, B: 0.04, C: 0.05, D: 0.06.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603976",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 603976, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 18.78, 17.45, 16.12, B: 16.28, 17.35, 18.42, C: 17.98, 17.35, 16.72, D: 19.58, 17.35, 15.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603977",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 603977? Please select from the following options: A: 15.57, 30.03, 20.01, B: 28.91, 20.51, 13.35, C: 20.02, 27.01, 18.87, D: 22.24, 25.02, 16.69.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603978",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603978 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? A: -0.12, B: -0.15, C: -0.09, D: -0.18.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603979",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 603979 on May 30? A: 1.15, B: 1.44, C: 1.75, D: 2.16.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603980",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603980 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 11.38, 20.08, -6.02, B: 21.14, 37.30, -11.02, C: 16.26, 28.69, -8.6, D: 13.82, 25.02, -10.88.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603982",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603982 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? A: -0.03, B: -0.10, C: 0.07, D: -0.05.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603983",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 603983. Its latest stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -1.96, B: -2.35, C: -1.57, D: -2.74.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603985",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 603985 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 22.34, B: 19.12, C: 15.89, D: 24.76.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603986",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 603986 on May 30? A: 2.85, B: 4.27, C: 3.56, D: 5.34.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603987",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 603987 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? A: 60.21, B: 58.75, C: 67.32, D: 64.52.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603988",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 603988, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 23.04, 21.31, 19.59, B: 20.74, 21.31, 21.89, C: 25.34, 21.31, 17.29, D: 23.04, 24.31, 19.59.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603989",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 603989 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: -0.08, B: -0.06, C: -0.04, D: -0.10.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603990",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 603990 on May 30 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.55, B: 0.75, C: 0.66, D: 0.82.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603991",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 603991 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 55.21, B: 65.81, C: 50.67, D: 60.81.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603992",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 603992 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: (23.69, 22.7, 21.71), B: (18.5, 21.5, 24.5), C: (25.8, 22.3, 19.6), D: (20.4, 23.1, 25.7).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603993",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 603993 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: -0.02, B: -0.03, C: -0.04, D: -0.01.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "603995",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 603995? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 0.18, B: 0.27, C: 0.24, D: 0.32.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "603997",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 603997 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.38, B: 0.55, C: 0.42, D: 0.48.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "603998",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 603998? Please choose from the following options: A: 64.28, 55.33, 82.2, B: 55.00, 49.00, 70.00, C: 75.00, 65.00, 95.00, D: 50.00, 40.00, 60.00.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "603999",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 603999 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.008, B: 0.01, C: 0.012, D: 0.015.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605001",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 605001 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 48.76, B: 59.34, C: 52.58, D: 65.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605003",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for stock 605003 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.13, B: -0.09, C: -0.15, D: -0.11.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605005",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 605005 on May 30? A: 90.85, B: 85.23, C: 105.32, D: 72.14.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605006",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605006 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 31.41, 38.46, 17.31, B: 39.84, 48.08, 21.64, C: 24.08, 30.77, 13.85, D: 46.07, 57.69, 25.97.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605007",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605007 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 20.0, 30.0, 5.0, C: 16.5, 24.03, 1.43, D: 10.0, 20.0, 0.5.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605008",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 605008, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 18.96, 17.26, 15.56, B: 16.43, 14.76, 13.09, C: 19.33, 17.56, 15.79, D: 17.73, 16.26, 14.8.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605009",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605009 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 21.8, 35.73, -6.05, B: 15.26, 46.45, -9.08, C: 28.34, 25.01, -3.93, D: 19.62, 39.31, -8.47.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605011",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 605011, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 25.95, 23.54, 21.12, B: 24.95, 23.54, 22.12, C: 23.95, 23.54, 23.12, D: 26.95, 23.54, 20.12.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605016",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 605016 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: -0.27, B: -0.42, C: -0.34, D: -0.51.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605018",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 605018 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 605018 on May 30? A: 42.12, B: 63.12, C: 57.12, D: 53.12.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605020",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 8.41, B: 7.21, C: 10.11, D: 6.32.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605028",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 605028, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 17.98, 17.25, 16.52, B: 17.56, 17.03, 16.5, C: 16.82, 16.45, 15.89, D: 18.21, 17.65, 16.92.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605033",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 605033 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.72, B: 0.98, C: 0.84, D: 1.02.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605050",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 605050 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.42, B: 0.65, C: 0.38, D: 0.54.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605055",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 605055, its stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 44.39, B: 38.75, C: 51.23, D: 60.12.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605056",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 605056. Its latest stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.015, B: -0.01, C: -0.005, D: -0.02",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605058",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605058 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.45, B: 0.65, C: 0.51, D: 0.39.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605060",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605060 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 15.3, 20.3, 12.4, B: 25.4, 28.7, 19.8, C: 17.8, 22.5, 10.2, D: 20.35, 23.33, 14.4.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605066",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 605066 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 28.35, B: 33.82, C: 23.47, D: 41.69.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605068",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 605068, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 21.62, 19.32, 17.02, B: 21.62, 19.32, 17.02, C: 24.92, 19.32, 13.72, D: 17.30, 19.32, 21.34.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605077",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 605077 on May 30? A: 52.89, B: 68.32, C: 47.65, D: 60.93.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605080",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 605080, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 34.14, 30.3, 26.46, B: 37.55, 33.33, 29.11, C: 27.31, 24.24, 21.17, D: 44.38, 39.39, 34.40.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605081",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605081 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 71.76, 76.58, 62.11, B: 81.76, 86.58, 72.11, C: 91.76, 96.58, 82.11, D: 61.76, 66.58, 52.11.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605086",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 605086 on May 30? A: 0.49, B: 0.53, C: 0.61, D: 0.72.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605088",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605088 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 10.68, 15.65, 1.05, B: 7.68, 10.65, 0.55, C: 11.68, 13.65, 0.95, D: 8.68, 12.65, 0.75.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605089",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 605089 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 605089 on May 30? A: 0.59, B: 0.63, C: 0.47, D: 0.71.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605090",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 605090 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 27.72, 26.06, 24.4, B: 28.15, 25.89, 24.1, C: 29.64, 24.54, 22.9, D: 25.27, 26.83, 25.9.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605098",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 605098, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 39.42, 37.63, 35.83, B: 37.42, 35.63, 33.83, C: 38.42, 36.63, 34.83, D: 36.42, 34.63, 32.83.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605099",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 605099 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 18.2, 22.3, 26.4, B: 21.5, 23.7, 25.9, C: 20.8, 22.1, 23.4, D: 24.65, 22.3, 19.95.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605100",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 23.29, 20.96, 18.63, B: 26.29, 19.96, 17.63, C: 20.29, 22.96, 21.63, D: 25.29, 18.96, 16.63.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605108",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 605108 is the value of which of the following options. A: -0.35, B: -0.29, C: -0.23, D: -0.17.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605111",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 605111, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 33.98, 31.14, 28.30, B: 31.14, 30.04, 28.94, C: 32.24, 31.14, 30.04, D: 34.50, 31.14, 27.78.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605116",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 605116 is the value of which of the following options. A: 48.32, B: 57.89, C: 61.24, D: 51.96.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605117",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 605117 on May 30? A: 1.9, B: 2.3, C: 1.4, D: 2.8.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605118",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 605118 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 18.5, 19.3, 20.1, B: 20.24, 19.28, 18.33, C: 17.3, 18.2, 19.1, D: 21.8, 20.5, 19.2.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605122",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 605122 from the following options. A: 0.08, B: 0.13, C: 0.11, D: 0.15.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605123",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 605123, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.58, B: 0.65, C: 0.85, D: 0.72.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605128",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 605128 from the following options. A: 1.27, B: 1.52, C: 0.98, D: 1.83.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605133",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 605133 on May 30? A: 2.15, B: 2.39, C: 2.78, D: 1.91.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605136",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 605136, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 19.76, 10.8, 4.35, B: 17.26, 13.8, 7.35, C: 17.26, 10.8, 4.35, D: 14.26, 8.8, 2.35.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605138",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 605138 on May 30? A: -0.20, B: -0.15, C: -0.19, D: -0.17.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605151",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 605151 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 605151 on May 30? A: 64.05, B: 58.92, C: 73.48, D: 60.08.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605155",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 605155 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 28.75, B: 32.34, C: 36.12, D: 25.98.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605158",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 605158, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 9.07, 8.19, 7.31, B: 8.23, 8.19, 8.15, C: 8.51, 8.19, 7.86, D: 7.66, 8.19, 8.72.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605162",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 605162 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.15, B: 0.22, C: 0.12, D: 0.19.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605166",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 605166, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 13.3, 11.95, 10.6, B: 17.29, 15.53, 13.77, C: 9.31, 7.77, 6.23, D: 15.96, 14.34, 12.72.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605167",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605167 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 58.5, 63.9, 70.2, B: 73.21, 77.48, 64.68, C: 85.6, 90.3, 59.8, D: 60.1, 70.4, 75.2.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605168",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 605168 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: 32.64, B: 42.64, C: 37.64, D: 27.64.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605169",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 605169 is the value of which of the following options. A: -0.08, B: -0.06, C: -0.09, D: -0.07.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605177",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 605177? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 0.42, B: 0.38, C: 0.47, D: 0.52.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605178",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605178 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 76.37, 70.48, 88.17, B: 65.37, 63.48, 95.17, C: 89.37, 83.48, 77.17, D: 52.37, 58.48, 102.17.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605179",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 605179 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.06, B: -0.10, C: -0.08, D: -0.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605180",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 605180 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.01, B: 0.03, C: 0.04, D: 0.02.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605183",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605183? Please select from the following options: A: 34.58, 43.88, 15.99, B: 24.21, 30.72, 10.19, C: 44.95, 57.04, 20.79, D: 17.29, 21.94, 7.99.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605186",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 605186 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 14.39, 20.0, 25.61, B: 20.56, 20.0, 19.44, C: 17.48, 20.0, 22.52, D: 23.64, 20.0, 16.36.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605188",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 605188 on May 30? A: 52.32, B: 64.31, C: 58.47, D: 49.15.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605189",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605189? Please select from the following options: A: 35.2, 42.7, 68.1, B: 78.3, 63.9, 92.5, C: 50.1, 39.4, 71.2, D: 62.91, 51.37, 86.0.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605196",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 605196, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.77, B: 0.62, C: 0.93, D: 0.55.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605198",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 605198 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.33, B: -0.44, C: -0.57, D: -0.22.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605199",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605199? Please select from the following options: A: 32.92, 27.85, 41.37, B: 60.14, 51.71, 77.64, C: 47.03, 39.78, 61.53, D: 58.76, 48.94, 76.21.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605208",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 605208, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.72, B: 0.98, C: 0.65, D: 0.85.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605218",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 605218, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 22.56, 21.6, 20.63, B: 27.56, 24.6, 19.63, C: 19.56, 20.6, 21.63, D: 21.56, 22.6, 23.63.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605222",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 605222 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 38.71, B: 40.71, C: 42.71, D: 44.71.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605228",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 605228, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 12.78, 11.34, 10.69, B: 11.55, 11.34, 10.98, C: 11.96, 11.34, 10.72, D: 11.62, 11.34, 10.84.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605255",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605255 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.58, B: 0.75, C: 0.62, D: 0.69.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605258",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605258 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 22.6, 25.16, 17.48, B: 15.82, 32.71, 22.72, C: 29.38, 17.61, 11.36, D: 18.08, 29.19, 21.85.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605259",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 605259 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.06, B: 0.08, C: 0.10, D: 0.12.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605266",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605266 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 78.9, 45.6, 12.3, C: 61.56, 66.64, 51.41, D: 51.41, 66.64, 61.56.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605268",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 605268, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 11.75, 9.28, 6.81, B: 10.54, 8.75, 7.03, C: 12.07, 9.01, 5.93, D: 9.28, 8.75, 8.21.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605277",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605277 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 19.49, 19.49, 19.5, B: 13.64, 13.64, 13.65, C: 25.34, 25.34, 25.35, D: 11.70, 11.70, 11.70.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605286",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 605286 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: -0.15, B: -0.13, C: -0.11, D: -0.09.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605287",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 605287 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.15, B: 0.23, C: 0.19, D: 0.27.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605288",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605288? Please select from the following options: A: 39.17, 50.94, 28.64, B: 73.17, 82.94, 53.64, C: 53.17, 62.94, 33.64, D: 63.17, 72.94, 43.64.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605289",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 605289 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: -0.06, B: -0.07, C: -0.05, D: -0.10.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605296",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 605296 from the following options. A: 0.68, B: 0.74, C: 0.81, D: 0.92.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605298",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 605298, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 13.87, 13.21, 12.55, B: 14.12, 13.57, 13.02, C: 13.51, 12.97, 12.44, D: 13.23, 12.79, 12.35.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605300",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 605300 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.16, B: 0.19, C: 0.13, D: 0.22.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605303",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 605303 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 605303 on May 30? A: 0.08, B: 0.1, C: 0.12, D: 0.15.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605318",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 605318 on May 30? A: -0.79, B: -0.53, C: -0.85, D: -0.66.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605319",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 605319 on May 30? A: 1.58, B: 1.75, C: 1.32, D: 2.10.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605333",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 605333. Its recent 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.89, B: 1.12, C: 1.35, D: 1.58.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605336",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 605336 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 605336 on May 30? A: 58.32, B: 64.71, C: 61.47, D: 52.19.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605337",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 605337 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 605337 on May 30? A: 0.21, B: 0.33, C: 0.55, D: 0.41.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605338",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 605338, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 68.77, B: 65.32, C: 73.21, D: 59.14.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605339",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 605339 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: 0.12, B: 0.15, C: 0.18, D: 0.21.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605358",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 605358 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.45, B: 0.69, C: 0.57, D: 0.72.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605365",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 605365, its 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.25, B: 0.35, C: 0.18, D: 0.3.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605366",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 605366 on May 30? A: 0.22, B: 0.18, C: 0.27, D: 0.33.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605368",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 605368. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 20.52, B: 23.68, C: 27.96, D: 31.24.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605369",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 605369 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 18.43, 26.89, 35.35, B: 21.48, 28.57, 35.66, C: 30.68, 26.89, 23.09, D: 24.53, 27.12, 30.31.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605376",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605376 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30?Please choose from the following options: A：12.3、13.4、11.5，B：9.8、10.5、8.7，C：14.6、15.2、13.9，D：11.36、11.91、10.24。",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605377",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 605377 on May 30? A: 0.12, B: 0.10, C: 0.14, D: 0.08.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605378",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605378?Please choose from the following options: A：28.49、31.14、27.18，B：35.49、37.14、32.18，C：42.49、44.14、37.18，D：24.49、29.14、26.18。",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605388",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 605388 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? A: 75.62, B: 85.42, C: 81.82, D: 91.22.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605389",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 605389, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 37.16, 33.42, 29.68, B: 35.58, 33.42, 31.25, C: 34.87, 32.15, 30.43, D: 35.58, 33.42, 31.25.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605398",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 605398? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: -0.34, B: -0.27, C: -0.41, D: -0.17.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605399",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 605399 is the value of which of the following options. A: 45.21, B: 47.67, C: 52.43, D: 43.89.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605488",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605488 from March 4, 2025, to May 30, 2025, what are the values of the K, D, and J lines of its stochastic indicator (KDJ) on May 30? Please choose: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 55.2, 32.1, 67.8, C: 43.64, 40.05, 50.82, D: 33.4, 50.1, 62.7.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605499",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 605499, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose from the following options: A：312.84、285.9、258.95，B：270.84、245.9、220.95，C：330.84、305.9、280.95，D：312.84、285.9、258.95。",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605500",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 605500, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 7.56, 7.33, 7.1, B: 9.83, 7.33, 5.04, C: 6.35, 7.33, 8.32, D: 8.28, 7.33, 6.42.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605507",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 605507 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 67.28, 60.96, 79.92, C: 50.12, 70.85, 90.45, D: 80.36, 55.21, 65.78.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605555",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605555 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? A: -0.01, B: -0.03, C: -0.02, D: -0.04.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605566",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 605566 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 52.34, B: 61.78, C: 49.87, D: 56.62.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605567",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 605567? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 55.35, B: 50.23, C: 62.14, D: 48.97.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605577",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 605577, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 13.78, 12.57, 11.36, B: 12.89, 12.57, 12.25, C: 14.13, 12.57, 10.69, D: 11.94, 12.57, 13.20.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605580",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 605580? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: -0.13, B: -0.09, C: -0.11, D: -0.15.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "605588",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 605588. Its latest stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.62, B: -0.34, C: -0.59, D: -0.48.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "605589",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605589 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 52.47, 34.62, 88.16, B: 36.73, 24.23, 61.71, C: 68.21, 44.99, 114.61, D: 46.22, 31.16, 79.34.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "605598",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 605598 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 40.12, B: 43.44, C: 47.21, D: 50.33.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "605599",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 605599. Its latest stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.15, B: 0.25, C: 0.21, D: 0.30.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688001",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688001 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 18.45, 25.98, 33.51, B: 22.37, 26.89, 31.42, C: 27.89, 24.67, 21.35, D: 26.36, 25.07, 23.78.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688002",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688002 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 72.69, 69.5, 79.06, B: 50.88, 51.65, 63.35, C: 94.49, 90.35, 102.78, D: 43.61, 48.65, 55.34.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688003",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688003 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 51.75, 45.99, 63.28, B: 54.75, 48.99, 66.28, C: 57.75, 51.99, 69.28, D: 50.75, 47.99, 65.28.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688004",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688004 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 12.3, 35.6, 58.9, B: 45.7, 55.2, 25.4, C: 39.36, 49.69, 18.71, D: 27.8, 63.4, 12.5.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688005",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688005 from the following options. A: 0.38, B: 0.52, C: 0.40, D: 0.46.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688006",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688006. Its latest 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 28.95, B: 32.50, C: 23.10, D: 37.00.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688008",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688008 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 1.45, B: 1.98, C: 1.72, D: 2.15.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688010",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688010, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 1.47, B: 1.32, C: 1.62, D: 1.18.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688011",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688011 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.60, B: 0.75, C: 0.90, D: 0.50.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688012",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688012 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? A: -0.52, B: -0.89, C: -0.67, D: -0.45.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688013",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688013 is the value of which of the following options. A: 72.12, B: 65.32, C: 89.12, D: 80.12.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688015",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 688015 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 49.03, B: 51.25, C: 46.87, D: 53.14.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688016",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688016 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 39.07, 35.44, 52.86, B: 60.11, 57.34, 65.66, C: 78.14, 74.54, 85.36, D: 42.08, 39.14, 56.96.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688017",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 688017 is the value of which of the following options. A: 3.8, B: 5.2, C: 4.6, D: 6.1.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688018",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688018? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: -1.82, B: -2.42, C: -1.62, D: -2.02.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688019",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688019, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 189.48, 178.51, 167.54, B: 132.64, 124.96, 117.28, C: 246.32, 232.06, 217.80, D: 151.58, 142.81, 134.04.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688020",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688020, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 35.76, 33.39, 31.02, B: 34.24, 33.39, 32.53, C: 37.66, 33.39, 29.12, D: 32.83, 33.39, 33.95.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688021",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688021 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? A: -0.10, B: -0.06, C: -0.08, D: -0.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688022",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688022 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? A: -0.15, B: -0.09, C: -0.18, D: -0.12.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688023",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688023 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 45.09, 30.07, 75.15, B: 31.56, 21.05, 52.61, C: 58.62, 39.09, 97.69, D: 22.55, 15.04, 37.58.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688025",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688025 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688025 on May 30? A: -0.31, B: -0.41, C: -0.51, D: -0.21.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688026",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 688026 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.05, B: 0.10, C: 0.07, D: 0.09.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688027",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688027 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 6.21, B: 7.92, C: 5.89, D: 7.11.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688028",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688028 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 12.98, 17.67, 3.6, B: 9.09, 12.37, 2.52, C: 16.87, 22.97, 4.68, D: 5.19, 7.07, 1.44.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688029",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688029’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 68.43, 64.31, 60.18, C: 55.23, 58.12, 61.34, D: 82.14, 77.65, 73.45.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688030",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688030 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688030 on May 30? A: 0.35, B: 0.47, C: 0.42, D: 0.51.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688031",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688031 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 21.03, 18.43, 39.22, B: 37.76, 31.60, 50.09, C: 25.18, 21.07, 33.39, D: 31.47, 26.33, 41.74.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688032",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the historical market data of stock 688032 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of stock 688032 on May 30? A: 36.72, B: 30.58, C: 44.06, D: 25.41.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688033",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688033’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 9.5, 6.7, B: 6.56, 5.95, 5.34, C: 8.12, 7.23, 6.45, D: 4.98, 4.32, 3.76.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688035",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688035 on May 30? A: 1.20, B: 1.35, C: 1.44, D: 1.60.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688036",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688036 from the following options. A: -0.03, B: -0.07, C: -0.10, D: -0.05.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688037",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688037 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 32.29, B: 28.12, C: 37.56, D: 41.87.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688038",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688038? Please select from the following options: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 15.01, 18.69, 7.67, C: 18.01, 21.69, 10.67, D: 10.01, 15.69, 5.67.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688039",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyzing the recent trend of stock 688039 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 30.21, B: 37.65, C: 34.85, D: 41.23.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688041",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688041, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 147.85, 141.06, 134.27, B: 157.23, 141.06, 124.89, C: 153.46, 141.06, 128.66, D: 150.96, 141.06, 131.15.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688045",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688045? Please select from the following options: A: 42.64, 35.15, 57.6, B: 31.98, 28.12, 74.88, C: 55.43, 45.68, 40.32, D: 29.85, 30.15, 68.92.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688046",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 688046 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.15, B: 0.19, C: 0.23, D: 0.27.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688047",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688047. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 62.35, B: 59.78, C: 66.88, D: 72.15.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688048",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688048, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 68.9, 59.7, 51.3, C: 60.2, 57.4, 48.6, D: 62.86, 56.08, 49.29.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688049",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688049 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 34.6, 26.21, 51.39, B: 24.22, 18.35, 35.97, C: 45.0, 34.0, 67.0, D: 20.76, 15.73, 28.83.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688050",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688050 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: 0.15, B: 0.28, C: 0.42, D: 0.55.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688051",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock price 688051 is the value of which of the following options. A: 52.34, B: 61.78, C: 56.67, D: 49.82.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688052",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688052 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 15.3, 30.2, 90.1, B: 35.2, 25.6, 70.3, C: 50.3, 35.7, 60.2, D: 41.66, 28.32, 68.33.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688053",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688053, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 29.83, 27.67, 25.51, B: 32.81, 27.67, 22.53, C: 26.85, 27.67, 28.49, D: 29.83, 30.44, 31.01.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688055",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 40.12, B: 43.33, C: 47.69, D: 38.91.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688056",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688056? Please select from the following options: A: 13.29, 14.41, 8.76, B: 8.18, 9.49, 5.58, C: 10.23, 11.86, 6.97, D: 11.25, 13.05, 7.67.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688057",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 62.13, B: 75.42, C: 59.87, D: 68.61.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688058",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688058 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688058 on May 30? A: 33.09, B: 37.56, C: 28.62, D: 41.21.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688059",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688059, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 78.12, 69.03, 60.24, B: 76.82, 69.03, 61.24, C: 73.52, 69.03, 64.54, D: 79.52, 69.03, 58.54.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688060",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock price 688060 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.15, B: 0.35, C: 0.28, D: 0.42.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688061",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688061 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 15.33, 20.54, 8.9, B: 28.33, 33.54, 17.9, C: 20.33, 25.54, 10.9, D: 23.33, 28.54, 12.9.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688062",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688062, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 25.18, 21.05, 16.92, B: 20.18, 17.05, 13.92, C: 32.18, 27.05, 22.92, D: 18.18, 15.05, 11.92.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688063",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688063, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 47.12, 45.29, 43.46, B: 45.29, 43.08, 40.86, C: 43.08, 40.86, 38.65, D: 47.86, 45.29, 42.72.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688065",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688065 from the following options. A: 0.87, B: 1.21, C: 1.09, D: 1.32.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688066",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688066 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 37.32, 27.49, 53.98, B: 67.44, 51.05, 100.27, C: 43.11, 33.67, 65.43, D: 51.88, 39.27, 77.1.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688067",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688067 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: 0.0, B: 0.1, C: -0.2, D: 0.3.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688068",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688068. Its latest stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.7, B: 0.9, C: 1.1, D: 1.3.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688069",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 688069 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.05, B: -0.03, C: -0.04, D: -0.06.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688070",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688070 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 1.49, B: 2.23, C: 1.67, D: 1.86.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688071",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688071 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688071 on May 30? A: 1.99, B: 2.39, C: 1.59, D: 2.79.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688072",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688072 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 32.05, B: 35.02, C: 38.07, D: 41.11.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688073",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688073, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 41.2, 42.1, 43.0, B: 45.7, 43.9, 42.1, C: 43.92, 42.16, 40.4, D: 40.4, 42.16, 43.92.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688075",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688075 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.15, B: 0.22, C: 0.41, D: 0.33.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688076",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 688076 on May 30? A: -1.33, B: -1.59, C: -1.10, D: -1.70.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688077",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688077, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 28.97, 25.32, 21.67, B: 27.64, 25.32, 22.99, C: 26.31, 25.32, 24.33, D: 29.99, 25.32, 20.65.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688078",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688078 from the following options. A: 0.72, B: 0.98, C: 0.87, D: 1.05.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688079",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688079 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: 0.03, B: 0.07, C: 0.10, D: 0.05.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688080",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688080 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: (46.97, 44.21, 41.44), B: (52.32, 48.63, 44.94), C: (39.85, 36.54, 33.23), D: (57.68, 53.41, 49.14).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688081",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688081 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 13.78, 18.0, 5.34, C: 10.6, 23.4, 7.2, D: 17.9, 21.6, 3.8.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688082",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688082 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 25.11, B: 29.11, C: 27.11, D: 31.11.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688083",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 688083? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 38.12, B: 47.35, C: 50.19, D: 42.27.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688084",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688084 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please select: A: (38.43, 28.33, 58.63), B: (26.90, 19.83, 41.04), C: (53.80, 39.66, 82.08), D: (31.55, 22.66, 46.90).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688085",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688085, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 35.29, B: 40.29, C: 45.29, D: 50.29.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688087",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688087 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 41.5, 33.9, 59.8, B: 58.9, 48.2, 76.3, C: 50.76, 42.3, 67.7, D: 65.2, 51.7, 84.1.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688088",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688088? Please choose from the following options: A: 15.3, 20.5, 27.9, B: 25.4, 23.8, 29.6, C: 18.6, 19.2, 24.7, D: 21.85, 21.18, 23.19.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688089",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688089 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 37.27, 45.56, 20.7, B: 26.09, 31.89, 14.5, C: 52.18, 63.78, 29.0, D: 18.64, 22.78, 10.3.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688090",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688090 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 46.52, 43.9, 41.28, C: 55.82, 52.68, 49.54, D: 38.21, 36.7, 34.1.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688091",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688091? Please select from the following options: A: 42.64, 33.05, 61.85, B: 79.19, 61.37, 114.86, C: 60.92, 47.21, 88.35, D: 52.83, 39.15, 76.28.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688092",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688092 on May 30? A: 45.03, B: 57.03, C: 63.03, D: 51.03.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688093",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688093’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 27.61, 26.19, 24.76, B: 29.87, 25.43, 23.12, C: 25.35, 26.91, 27.48, D: 23.18, 27.82, 26.53.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688095",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 688095 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? A: 25.15, B: 27.15, C: 29.15, D: 31.15.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688096",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688096 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: -0.72, B: -1.10, C: -0.86, D: -0.60.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688097",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688097. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.12, B: 0.06, C: 0.05, D: 0.08.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688098",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688098, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 6.07, 5.79, 5.51, B: 5.25, 5.00, 4.75, C: 6.79, 6.41, 6.03, D: 4.86, 4.63, 4.40.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688099",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 688099? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: -0.29, B: -0.38, C: -0.47, D: -0.19.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688100",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688100. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 20.33, B: 30.12, C: 25.41, D: 18.76.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688101",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688101 from the following options. A: 0.17, B: 0.23, C: 0.25, D: 0.21.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688102",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688102 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 56.48, 41.66, 86.12, B: 42.34, 31.23, 72.45, C: 73.42, 54.19, 111.96, D: 39.54, 28.91, 60.27.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688103",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688103 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.92, B: 1.14, C: 1.37, D: 1.59.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688105",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688105, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 23.68, 22.03, 20.38, B: 21.97, 22.03, 22.09, C: 22.77, 22.03, 21.29, D: 24.58, 22.03, 19.48.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688106",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688106 from the following options. A: 0.42, B: 0.61, C: 0.72, D: 0.53.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688107",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 688107 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.79, B: 0.63, C: 0.95, D: 0.52.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688108",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688108 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 13.5, 9.8, 7.2, B: 10.99, 10.05, 9.11, C: 12.1, 9.3, 8.6, D: 11.8, 9.5, 8.3.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688109",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688109, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.31, B: -0.21, C: -0.26, D: -0.18.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688110",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688110. Which of the following options is the value of its latest 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025? A: 1.24, B: 1.76, C: 1.45, D: 1.55.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688111",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688111 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 7.16, B: 6.32, C: 8.59, D: 5.12.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688112",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688112 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 15.05, 17.43, 14.28, B: 18.05, 18.43, 17.28, C: 20.05, 21.43, 19.28, D: 13.05, 14.43, 12.28.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688113",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688113, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 38.79, 35.54, 32.29, B: 34.25, 32.97, 31.69, C: 35.54, 34.25, 32.97, D: 39.09, 35.54, 32.00.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688114",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688114. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 7.43, B: 11.15, C: 13.94, D: 9.29.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688115",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688115 on May 30? A: 2.24, B: 1.98, C: 2.75, D: 3.12.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688116",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688116, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 1.12, B: 1.4, C: 1.68, D: 1.96.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688117",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688117 on May 30? A: 68.21, B: 70.12, C: 74.33, D: 82.56.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688118",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688118, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 27.93, 24.03, 20.13, B: 25.15, 24.03, 22.91, C: 26.46, 24.03, 21.6, D: 28.83, 24.03, 19.23.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688119",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688119? Please select from the following options: A: 59.04, 57.33, 62.47, B: 41.33, 40.13, 43.73, C: 76.75, 74.53, 81.21, D: 35.42, 34.40, 37.48.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688120",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688120 from the following options. A: 27.86, B: 30.86, C: 34.86, D: 37.86.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688121",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688121, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 14.9, 11.63, 8.37, B: 12.0, 11.63, 11.26, C: 13.0, 11.63, 10.26, D: 15.6, 11.63, 9.74.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688122",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688122 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 45.21, B: 59.78, C: 48.63, D: 51.84.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688123",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688123, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 2.24, B: 2.02, C: 2.79, D: 1.68.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688125",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688125 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 11.36, 17.74, 2.6, B: 14.36, 19.74, 3.6, C: 17.36, 22.74, 4.6, D: 10.36, 16.74, 1.6.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688126",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688126, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 19.35, 18.73, 18.11, B: 18.09, 17.45, 16.81, C: 18.73, 18.09, 17.45, D: 17.45, 18.09, 18.73.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688127",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688127 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 21.27, 15.00, 36.50, B: 39.51, 27.83, 62.93, C: 24.31, 17.10, 58.62, D: 30.39, 21.38, 48.41.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688128",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688128. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.28, B: -0.34, C: -0.22, D: -0.19.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688129",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688129? Please select from the following options: A: 18.64, 31.42, -12.75, B: 26.63, 44.88, -9.87, C: 34.62, 58.33, -6.91, D: 20.51, 38.22, -15.32.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688130",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688130. Its latest stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.03, B: 0.05, C: 0.04, D: 0.06.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688131",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688131 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688131 on May 30? A: 58.01, B: 60.01, C: 64.01, D: 62.01.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688132",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688132 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 23.36, 20.19, 17.02, B: 16.35, 14.13, 11.91, C: 29.39, 26.25, 23.11, D: 32.70, 28.27, 24.83.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688133",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688133 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688133 on May 30? A: 32.12, B: 36.67, C: 41.34, D: 29.85.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688135",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688135, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 42.31, B: 57.14, C: 49.72, D: 61.85.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688136",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688136, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 52.68, 41.68, 30.67, B: 48.68, 37.68, 26.67, C: 54.68, 43.68, 32.67, D: 50.68, 39.68, 28.67.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688137",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688137, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 65.55, B: 60.32, C: 72.11, D: 58.97.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688138",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688138. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 20.5, B: 23.8, C: 27.4, D: 31.2.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688139",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 688139 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 38.12, B: 47.89, C: 42.32, D: 51.65.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688141",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688141 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: -0.72, B: -0.43, C: -0.68, D: -0.54.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688143",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688143 from the following options. A: 1.15, B: 1.38, C: 0.92, D: 1.57.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688146",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688146 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 27.99, 28.29, 28.59, B: 28.77, 28.29, 27.81, C: 29.67, 27.43, 25.19, D: 26.13, 29.14, 29.88.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688147",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688147. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 30.12, B: 35.89, C: 33.46, D: 28.71.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688148",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688148. Its latest 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.11, B: 0.17, C: 0.19, D: 0.14.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688150",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688150? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 0.79, B: 0.83, C: 0.69, D: 0.95.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688151",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688151 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.35, B: 0.46, C: 0.58, D: 0.29.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688152",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688152 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 15.2, 30.1, 40.5, B: 29.8, 18.7, 32.4, C: 23.6, 21.49, 27.81, D: 20.5, 25.6, 33.7.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688153",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688153, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 35.95, 33.04, 30.13, B: 31.74, 29.85, 27.96, C: 34.15, 31.24, 28.33, D: 33.04, 30.95, 28.85.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688155",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688155 from the following options. A: 0.48, B: 0.58, C: 0.38, D: 0.68.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688156",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688156, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 16.96, 15.81, 14.67, B: 15.96, 14.81, 13.67, C: 17.96, 16.81, 15.67, D: 14.96, 13.81, 12.67.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688157",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688157? Please select from the following options: A: 15.15, 20.14, 25.95, B: 20.08, 25.14, 30.95, C: 23.08, 21.14, 26.95, D: 26.08, 18.14, 32.95.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688158",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688158 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 10.23, 11.55, 8.76, B: 13.98, 15.40, 10.21, C: 9.85, 11.20, 7.93, D: 11.57, 12.83, 9.05.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688159",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688159? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 59.02, B: 55.15, C: 63.87, D: 49.89.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688160",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688160 from the following options. A: -3.10, B: -2.58, C: -2.07, D: -3.44.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688161",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688161 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 19.09, 26.3, 33.51, B: 22.86, 27.97, 33.08, C: 27.28, 26.3, 25.33, D: 24.55, 25.87, 27.19.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688162",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 688162 on May 30? A: -0.06, B: -0.10, C: -0.12, D: -0.08.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688163",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 688163 on May 30? A: 0.15, B: 0.18, C: 0.12, D: 0.20.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688165",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688165 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 10.88, 19.97, -7.32, B: 8.37, 15.36, -5.63, C: 11.72, 19.97, -7.32, D: 6.89, 12.29, -4.51.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688166",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688166, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 51.87, 49.38, 46.89, B: 53.25, 50.15, 47.05, C: 52.07, 49.58, 47.1, D: 50.95, 48.49, 45.03.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688167",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688167 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 42.05, B: 51.24, C: 39.87, D: 46.08.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688168",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688168, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 58.02, B: 69.62, C: 46.42, D: 75.43.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688169",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688169 from the following options. A: 1.87, B: 2.08, C: 2.31, D: 2.54.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688170",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688170 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688170 on May 30? A: 0.15, B: -0.25, C: 0.0, D: 0.35.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688171",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688171 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 40.2, B: 50.3, C: 38.7, D: 45.2.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688172",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688172 on May 30? A: 0.4, B: 0.32, C: 0.5, D: 0.2.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688173",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688173’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 13.1, 11.7, B: 14.58, 13.14, 11.69, C: 16.3, 14.4, 12.9, D: 11.9, 10.8, 9.5.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688175",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 688175 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.55, B: 0.72, C: 0.68, D: 0.85.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688176",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688176, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.12, B: 0.24, C: 0.30, D: 0.18.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688177",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688177 from the following options. A: 1.06, B: 1.27, C: 0.85, D: 1.59.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688178",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688178 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? A: -0.05, B: -0.07, C: -0.09, D: -0.11.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688179",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688179, its 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.32, B: 0.55, C: 0.42, D: 0.60.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688180",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688180 on May 30? A: 0.95, B: 1.05, C: 1.30, D: 1.18.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688181",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688181 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 43.87, 42.89, 45.85, B: 30.71, 30.02, 32.09, C: 57.03, 55.76, 59.61, D: 26.32, 25.73, 27.51.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688182",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688182 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 1.12, B: 1.32, C: 1.52, D: 0.92.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688183",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688183 is the value of which of the following options. A: 34.50, B: 42.17, C: 38.34, D: 45.92.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688184",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688184 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 13.2, 10.5, 7.8, B: 9.8, 8.6, 7.4, C: 11.5, 9.3, 7.9, D: 10.16, 9.18, 8.2.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688185",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688185, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 1.82, B: 1.64, C: 2.18, D: 1.45.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688186",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688186 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.76, B: 0.95, C: 1.14, D: 1.33.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688187",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688187 from the following options. A: 0.60, B: 0.90, C: 0.75, D: 0.50.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688188",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688188 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688188 on May 30? A: 24.32, B: 29.17, C: 31.83, D: 26.61.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688189",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688189 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.17, B: 0.15, C: 0.21, D: 0.19.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688190",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688190 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688190 on May 30? A: -1.2, B: -1.5, C: -1.8, D: -2.0.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688191",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688191, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.3, B: -0.7, C: -0.5, D: -0.9.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688192",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688192? Please select from the following options: A: 52.68, 47.89, 64.37, B: 71.85, 63.21, 93.12, C: 58.72, 51.43, 73.56, D: 65.25, 57.35, 81.03.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688193",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688193, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 39.81, 38.57, 37.33, B: 36.81, 35.57, 34.33, C: 42.81, 41.57, 40.33, D: 34.81, 33.57, 32.33.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688195",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688195 on May 30? A: 34.5, B: 38.2, C: 42.7, D: 51.3.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688196",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688196 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688196 on May 30? A: 0.55, B: 0.63, C: 0.77, D: 0.92.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688197",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688197 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 25.3, 31.4, 37.5, C: 30.2, 35.7, 41.3, D: 37.52, 33.12, 28.73.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688198",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688198, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: (113.6, 109.38, 105.15), B: (127.6, 113.38, 99.15), C: (100.6, 109.38, 118.15), D: (113.6, 129.38, 105.15).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688199",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on a careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the recent Bollinger Bands (BOLL) values for stock 688199, specifically the upper, middle, and lower bands? Please choose: A: 17.56, 18.29, 19.02, B: 19.24, 18.29, 17.33, C: 16.85, 18.29, 19.73, D: 19.89, 18.29, 16.69.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688200",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688200 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 3.27, B: 5.23, C: 4.36, D: 6.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688201",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688201 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 39.76, 30.12, 67.83, B: 78.12, 61.03, 104.31, C: 58.12, 45.03, 84.31, D: 68.12, 55.03, 94.31.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688202",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688202 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 62.61, 53.86, 80.11, B: 43.83, 37.70, 56.08, C: 79.39, 69.02, 104.14, D: 31.31, 26.93, 40.06.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688203",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 688203 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.1, B: 0.0, C: 0.1, D: 0.2.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688205",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688205 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 28.0, 55.0, 80.0, C: 58.04, 51.15, 44.25, D: 35.0, 60.0, 90.0.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688206",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688206 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 39.12, 27.81, 58.37, B: 75.67, 52.65, 121.73, C: 50.45, 35.10, 86.92, D: 63.06, 43.87, 101.44.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688207",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688207 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: 0.32, B: 0.25, C: 0.40, D: 0.18.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688208",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688208? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 28.5, B: 32.2, C: 36.9, D: 41.7.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688209",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 688209, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 19.57, 18.31, 17.05, B: 18.95, 17.91, 16.87, C: 19.31, 18.17, 17.03, D: 19.84, 18.63, 17.42.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688210",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688210 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.55, B: 0.72, C: 0.48, D: 0.63.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688211",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688211, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 34.34, 29.39, 24.44, B: 27.47, 29.39, 31.26, C: 37.77, 29.39, 21.01, D: 31.91, 29.39, 26.87.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688212",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688212, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 51.96, 47.94, 43.93, B: 50.96, 47.94, 44.93, C: 53.96, 47.94, 41.93, D: 49.96, 47.94, 45.93.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688213",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688213, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 110.03, 98.59, 87.15, B: 95.03, 87.49, 79.95, C: 100.03, 92.49, 84.95, D: 105.03, 94.49, 83.95.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688215",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688215 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688215 on May 30? A: 0.98, B: 1.05, C: 1.25, D: 1.12.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688216",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688216 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: 0.08, B: 0.06, C: 0.12, D: 0.15.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688217",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688217 from the following options. A: 52.65, B: 59.57, C: 67.43, D: 73.21.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688218",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688218 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 32.5, 50.1, 10.7, B: 41.5, 60.3, 12.9, C: 38.23, 54.72, 5.23, D: 34.6, 58.9, 7.4.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688219",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688219 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 25.34, B: 33.76, C: 27.89, D: 29.48.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688220",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688220? Please select from the following options: A: 10.39, 12.86, 5.47, B: 13.51, 16.72, 7.11, C: 8.29, 10.29, 4.38, D: 15.58, 19.29, 6.56.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688221",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688221 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.25, B: 0.3, C: 0.35, D: 0.4",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688222",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688222, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.65, B: 0.85, C: 0.73, D: 0.95.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688223",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock price 688223? Please select the correct option from the options below.A: -0.02,B: -0.04,C: 0.01,D: -0.03",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688225",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688225 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 24.68, 19.63, 34.78, B: 17.28, 13.74, 24.35, C: 32.08, 25.52, 45.22, D: 20.32, 16.73, 28.67.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688226",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688226 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 48.75, B: 51.85, C: 57.65, D: 62.35.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688227",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688227 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 41.2, 51.6, 62.9, B: 55.2, 48.3, 43.1, C: 50.65, 50.95, 50.05, D: 60.1, 52.8, 59.7.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688228",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688228 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 14.37, 17.77, 9.54, B: 8.74, 10.52, 4.06, C: 16.58, 20.51, 11.73, D: 11.05, 13.67, 5.8.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688229",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688229 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 39.37, 27.7, 62.72, B: 51.18, 35.99, 81.54, C: 27.56, 19.39, 43.90, D: 47.25, 33.24, 75.27.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688230",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688230 from the following options. A: 0.48, B: 0.6, C: 0.72, D: 0.3",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688231",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688231 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 68.96, 24.83, 107.23, C: 48.96, 34.83, 77.23, D: 34.27, 24.38, 54.06.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688232",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688232, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.15, B: -0.08, C: -0.11, D: -0.13.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688233",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688233, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 29.66, 27.81, 25.95, B: 25.66, 27.81, 29.95, C: 29.66, 30.81, 25.95, D: 29.66, 27.81, 22.95.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688234",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688234 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 50.24, B: 55.24, C: 62.24, D: 47.24.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688235",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Assume that you are analyzing the market data of stock 688235. Its latest 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 8.32, B: 10.12, C: 9.55, D: 11.46.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688236",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688236. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 60.42, B: 57.65, C: 67.54, D: 63.79.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688237",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 688237 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.21, B: -0.17, C: -0.26, D: -0.31.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688238",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688238 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.05, B: 0.07, C: 0.09, D: 0.11.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688239",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688239. Its latest stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -1.25, B: -2.10, C: -1.67, D: -0.83.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688244",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688244, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 45.19, 42.15, 39.11, B: 40.19, 37.15, 34.11, C: 43.19, 39.15, 35.11, D: 42.19, 38.15, 34.11.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688246",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688246, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 32.08, 29.98, 27.89, B: 27.12, 28.98, 30.84, C: 35.29, 31.48, 27.67, D: 29.98, 32.08, 27.89.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688247",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688247 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.22, B: 0.28, C: 0.34, D: 0.19.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688248",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 688248 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? A: 42.34, B: 55.67, C: 48.94, D: 61.23.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688249",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688249 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688249 on May 30? A: 32.15, B: 41.56, C: 39.87, D: 36.73.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688251",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688251, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 23.13, 21.27, 19.42, B: 20.82, 21.27, 21.73, C: 25.44, 21.27, 16.97, D: 21.27, 23.13, 19.42.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688252",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688252, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 25.96, 23.37, 20.79, B: 24.58, 23.37, 22.15, C: 23.18, 23.37, 23.56, D: 27.04, 23.37, 19.70.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688253",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688253’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 25.3, 33.6, 41.9, C: 34.39, 32.42, 30.45, D: 42.3, 39.6, 36.9.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688255",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688255 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 7.2, 9.85, 1.88, B: 5.04, 6.89, 1.32, C: 9.36, 12.81, 2.44, D: 7.2, 9.85, 1.88.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688256",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688256? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 8.23, B: 7.15, C: 9.87, D: 6.42.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688257",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688257 on May 30? A: 20.52, B: 23.12, C: 26.98, D: 18.76.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688258",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688258 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 52.3, 48.9, 45.5, C: 48.92, 45.52, 42.11, D: 62.1, 55.3, 48.7.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688259",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688259? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 27.89, B: 40.12, C: 39.87, D: 33.33.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688260",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 688260 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.04, B: -0.05, C: -0.03, D: -0.06.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688261",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688261 is the value of which of the following options. A: 30.21, B: 35.41, C: 42.13, D: 27.98.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688262",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688262? Please select from the following options: A: 17.28, 13.47, 29.85, B: 32.10, 25.80, 43.65, C: 24.69, 19.24, 35.59, D: 14.81, 11.54, 21.36.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688265",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688265 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688265 on May 30? A: 0.58, B: 0.65, C: 0.85, D: 0.73.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688266",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688266 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 5.37, B: 4.98, C: 6.12, D: 3.89.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688267",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688267 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 41.5, 43.2, 39.8, B: 46.2, 47.12, 44.36, C: 50.1, 49.3, 46.7, D: 39.8, 42.4, 41.2.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688268",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688268, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 1.12, B: 1.67, C: 1.39, D: 0.98.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688269",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688269, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 32.16, 30.46, 28.76, B: 34.16, 32.46, 30.76, C: 31.16, 29.46, 27.76, D: 33.16, 31.46, 29.76.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688270",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688270 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of stock price of stock 688270 on May 30? A: 1.41, B: 1.27, C: 1.69, D: 1.06.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688271",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688271, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 2.02, B: 2.52, C: 3.02, D: 1.82.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688272",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688272 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 10.56, 12.51, 6.65, B: 15.56, 17.51, 11.65, C: 12.56, 14.51, 8.65, D: 14.56, 16.51, 10.65.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688273",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 688273 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 48.21, B: 59.87, C: 62.14, D: 53.42.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688275",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688275 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688275 on May 30? A: 0.08, B: 0.10, C: 0.06, D: 0.12.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688276",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688276 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 18.31, 20.92, 23.53, B: 21.31, 20.92, 20.54, C: 24.31, 20.92, 17.54, D: 19.31, 20.92, 22.54.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688277",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688277 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.15, B: 0.35, C: 0.29, D: 0.42.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688278",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688278? Please select from the following options: A: 61.02, 56.04, 77.49, B: 85.52, 77.04, 102.49, C: 59.52, 67.04, 88.49, D: 77.52, 69.04, 94.49.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688279",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688279? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 10.16, B: 12.19, C: 8.13, D: 15.24.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688280",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688280 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: -0.15, B: -0.23, C: -0.31, D: -0.07.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688281",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688281, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.45, B: 0.65, C: 0.55, D: 0.75.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688282",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688282, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 48.12, 45.39, 42.66, B: 44.25, 41.78, 39.31, C: 49.68, 46.53, 43.38, D: 46.35, 42.99, 39.64.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688283",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688283 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of stock price of stock 688283 on May 30? A: 0.83, B: 0.75, C: 0.95, D: 0.62.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688285",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688285 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688285 on May 30? A: 0.01, B: 0.03, C: 0.05, D: 0.07.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688286",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688286 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688286 on May 30? A: 2.85, B: 3.75, C: 3.34, D: 4.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688287",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688287? Please select from the following options: A: 41.2, 31.5, 60.8, B: 76.5, 58.3, 98.7, C: 39.3, 29.7, 56.2, D: 58.88, 44.99, 86.68.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688288",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688288? Please select from the following options: A: 34.32, 23.21, 56.54, B: 24.02, 16.25, 49.58, C: 44.62, 32.50, 63.80, D: 27.46, 18.57, 45.23.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688289",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688289 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 48.88, 38.38, 69.88, C: 63.54, 50.00, 90.84, D: 34.22, 26.87, 50.92.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688290",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688290, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 54.76, 53.02, 51.28, B: 58.96, 53.02, 47.09, C: 56.96, 53.02, 49.09, D: 55.96, 53.02, 50.09.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688291",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688291, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 24.76, 23.53, 22.30, B: 21.34, 20.23, 19.12, C: 25.89, 23.53, 21.17, D: 23.53, 22.7, 21.87.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688292",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688292 on May 30 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.52, B: 0.41, C: 0.65, D: 0.38.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688293",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688293, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 45.71, 43.12, 40.53, B: 43.12, 41.72, 40.31, C: 44.62, 42.34, 39.87, D: 42.12, 40.72, 39.31.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688295",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688295 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of stock price of stock 688295 on May 30? A: 0.71, B: 0.98, C: 0.89, D: 1.05.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688296",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688296 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 55.6, 62.3, 85.4, C: 70.2, 50.1, 68.7, D: 63.69, 56.63, 77.81.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688297",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 688297 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.18, B: -0.21, C: -0.15, D: -0.25.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688298",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688298? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 0.55, B: 0.7, C: 0.85, D: 0.95.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688299",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 688299 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.75, B: 0.95, C: 0.83, D: 0.65.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688300",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688300. Its latest stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.65, B: -0.42, C: -0.71, D: -0.53.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688301",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688301? Please select from the following options: A: 48.59, 42.26, 61.26, B: 34.01, 30.00, 51.00, C: 63.17, 54.94, 79.64, D: 29.16, 25.36, 42.88.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688302",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 688302, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 57.09, 48.52, 39.94, B: 59.19, 48.52, 37.84, C: 54.99, 48.52, 42.04, D: 61.29, 48.52, 37.84.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688303",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 688303 on May 30? A: -0.15, B: -0.11, C: -0.13, D: -0.17.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688305",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 688305 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 22.17, B: 30.17, C: 24.17, D: 26.17.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688306",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688306, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 11.18, 10.13, 9.09, B: 14.53, 10.13, 5.75, C: 9.86, 10.13, 10.40, D: 11.18, 13.17, 9.09.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688307",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688307 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 18.67, 23.45, 29.31, B: 29.43, 28.06, 26.7, C: 35.67, 27.89, 24.12, D: 24.56, 29.12, 30.45.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688308",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688308 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 32.1, 35.7, 31.9, B: 40.8, 42.9, 41.2, C: 36.31, 37.19, 34.55, D: 39.4, 36.8, 33.1.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688309",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688309 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 37.0, 41.3, 58.7, B: 66.9, 76.7, 97.3, C: 42.0, 51.3, 32.7, D: 51.44, 59.01, 36.28.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688310",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688310 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 87.06, B: 82.91, C: 91.21, D: 79.85.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688311",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688311 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688311 on May 30? A: 48.56, B: 52.29, C: 57.98, D: 61.55.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688312",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688312, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.25, B: -0.40, C: -0.33, D: -0.20.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688313",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688313 from the following options. A: 40.21, B: 45.73, C: 39.86, D: 43.47.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688314",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688314 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: -0.28, B: -0.34, C: -0.22, D: -0.38.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688315",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688315 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 32.07, 21.25, 55.7, B: 42.07, 30.25, 65.7, C: 52.07, 40.25, 75.7, D: 22.07, 10.25, 45.7.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688316",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688316, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 16.46, B: 24.70, C: 20.58, D: 27.84.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688317",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688317 from the following options. A: 0.09, B: 0.15, C: 0.10, D: 0.12.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688318",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688318? Please select from the following options: A: 37.39, 23.28, 65.6, B: 26.17, 16.29, 45.9, C: 48.61, 30.26, 85.3, D: 30.91, 19.43, 52.4.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688319",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688319 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.48, B: 0.6, C: 0.72, D: 0.3",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688320",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688320, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 47.1, 45.57, 43.94, B: 51.1, 45.57, 39.94, C: 49.2, 45.57, 41.94, D: 50.5, 45.57, 40.64.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688321",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 688321 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 70.23, B: 69.45, C: 82.31, D: 78.91.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688322",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688322 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: -0.91, B: -1.09, C: -0.73, D: -1.28.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688323",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of the stock price of stock 688323 on May 30? A: -0.1, B: 0.0, C: 0.1, D: 0.2.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688325",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688325 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688325 on May 30? A: -0.25, B: -0.41, C: -0.33, D: -0.17.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688326",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 688326 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 72.19, B: 87.19, C: 77.19, D: 82.19.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688327",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688327 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.05, B: 0.06, C: 0.04, D: 0.07.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688328",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688328, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.55, B: 0.71, C: 0.90, D: 0.35.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688329",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) indicator of stock price 688329 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.4, B: 0.6, C: 0.5, D: 0.7.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688330",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688330 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 51.2, 40.1, 75.8, B: 82.3, 65.9, 101.4, C: 61.8, 52.4, 90.3, D: 69.57, 56.82, 95.07.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688331",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688331 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: (61.93, 52.38, 42.84), B: (43.35, 36.67, 30.00), C: (78.51, 68.09, 57.68), D: (55.74, 47.14, 38.53).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688332",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688332? Please choose from the following options: A: 15.3, 28.6, 37.9, B: 36.96, 31.6, 47.69, C: 48.2, 25.3, 59.8, D: 24.7, 34.2, 61.5.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688333",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688333 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: -1.15, B: -0.78, C: -0.96, D: -1.32.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688334",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688334, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 17.95, 16.85, 15.75, B: 18.20, 17.00, 15.80, C: 16.50, 16.20, 15.90, D: 17.06, 16.75, 16.43.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688335",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688335 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: 0.08, B: 0.10, C: 0.06, D: 0.12.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688336",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688336, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 70.97, B: 76.97, C: 83.97, D: 68.97.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688337",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688337 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 18.97, 16.81, 23.29, B: 38.97, 36.81, 43.29, C: 28.97, 26.81, 33.29, D: 48.97, 46.81, 53.29.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688338",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688338 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 48.3, B: 57.9, C: 62.1, D: 52.7.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688339",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688339? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 39.88, B: 41.87, C: 37.89, D: 47.86.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688343",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688343 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 1.25, B: 1.62, C: 1.98, D: 2.35.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688345",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688345? Please select from the following options: A: 12.3, 35.6, 88.9, B: 25.8, 22.4, -15.6, C: 17.88, 29.63, -5.63, D: 10.2, 38.5, -12.7.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688347",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688347 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 51.07, 48.18, 56.86, B: 61.07, 58.18, 66.86, C: 49.07, 46.18, 54.86, D: 56.07, 53.18, 61.86.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688348",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688348. Its most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.09, B: -0.11, C: -0.07, D: -0.13.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688349",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688349 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.12, B: 0.18, C: 0.24, D: 0.30.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688350",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688350 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 62.3, B: 74.5, C: 69.1, D: 58.7.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688351",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688351’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 17.89, 21.32, 24.75, B: 21.56, 20.78, 19.93, C: 23.15, 22.13, 21.09, D: 22.15, 20.93, 19.71.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688352",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688352 is the value of which of the following options. A: -0.07, B: -0.09, C: -0.12, D: -0.05.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688353",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688353 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.41, B: 0.52, C: 0.65, D: 0.78.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688355",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688355, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.32, B: 0.52, C: 0.42, D: 0.62.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688356",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688356, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 74.35, 64.48, 54.61, B: 68.95, 64.48, 59.01, C: 77.56, 64.48, 51.40, D: 74.35, 64.48, 54.61.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688357",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688357, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 25.92, 25.14, 24.35, B: 22.37, 23.85, 25.33, C: 28.71, 24.35, 20.97, D: 26.13, 25.89, 25.65.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688358",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688358 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 27.16, 26.05, 24.94, B: 29.96, 28.94, 27.93, C: 32.96, 31.83, 30.70, D: 26.96, 25.85, 24.74.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688359",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688359 is the value of which of the following options. A: -0.81, B: -1.21, C: -1.01, D: -0.61.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688360",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688360 was the value of which of the following options. A: 38.75, B: 45.32, C: 34.17, D: 42.53.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688361",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 688361? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: -0.82, B: -0.98, C: -0.66, D: -1.23.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688362",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688362 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 25.34, B: 30.53, C: 36.64, D: 42.75.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688363",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688363 from the following options. A: -0.10, B: -0.15, C: -0.12, D: -0.09.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688365",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 34.75, B: 44.75, C: 32.25, D: 39.75.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688366",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688366? Please select from the following options: A: 43.92, 46.87, 38.02, B: 30.74, 32.81, 26.61, C: 57.10, 60.93, 59.43, D: 29.35, 32.81, 26.61.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688367",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688367 from the following options. A: 52.32, B: 58.11, C: 64.92, D: 49.13.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688368",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688368 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 40.32, B: 51.27, C: 44.63, D: 39.18.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688369",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688369 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 1.02, B: 1.35, C: 0.98, D: 1.27.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688370",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688370 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 30.72, 32.61, 26.92, B: 21.50, 22.83, 18.84, C: 39.94, 42.39, 35.00, D: 15.36, 16.31, 13.46.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688371",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688371 on May 30? A: 0.39, B: 0.49, C: 0.69, D: 0.29.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688372",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688372 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 18.90, 13.12, 27.35, B: 12.30, 9.60, 19.80, C: 15.49, 11.44, 23.57, D: 17.60, 10.80, 25.40.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688373",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688373, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 6.75, 6.16, 5.57, B: 6.89, 6.16, 5.43, C: 6.43, 6.16, 5.89, D: 6.57, 6.16, 5.75.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688375",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688375 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.11, B: 0.09, C: 0.13, D: 0.07.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688376",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688376. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 40.23, B: 45.54, C: 51.21, D: 38.96.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688377",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688377 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of stock price of stock 688377 on May 30? A: 0.53, B: 0.79, C: 0.66, D: 0.85.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688378",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688378? Please select from the following options: A: 27.11, 25.29, 30.74, B: 50.35, 47.98, 63.21, C: 32.48, 30.12, 40.65, D: 38.73, 36.14, 43.92.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688379",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688379 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 51.85, B: 47.62, C: 63.42, D: 38.14.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688380",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688380 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 12.3, 25.6, 38.9, B: 35.29, 28.07, 49.71, C: 45.8, 36.5, 64.3, D: 24.7, 19.3, 32.1.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688381",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688381? Please select from the following options: A: 14.28, 18.36, 5.38, B: 21.05, 27.54, 8.06, C: 17.54, 22.95, 6.72, D: 22.81, 30.83, 9.73.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688382",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688382? Please select from the following options: A: 71.2, 67.8, 91.4, B: 103.5, 91.6, 132.1, C: 62.4, 58.1, 80.7, D: 89.63, 82.92, 103.05.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688383",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688383, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 61.52, 49.7, 37.88, B: 52.35, 44.73, 36.18, C: 68.67, 54.67, 41.67, D: 55.37, 44.73, 34.09.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688385",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688385, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 1.23, B: 1.54, C: 1.85, D: 2.31.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688386",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688386 from the following options. A: 1.85, B: 2.10, C: 2.32, D: 2.75.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688387",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688387 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 50.12, B: 57.98, C: 48.65, D: 54.32.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688388",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688388 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: 0.11, B: 0.09, C: 0.13, D: 0.07.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688389",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688389 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.07, B: 0.09, C: 0.11, D: 0.13.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688390",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688390 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 32.12, B: 36.57, C: 34.34, D: 38.91.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688391",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 688391 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 34.12, B: 48.76, C: 52.31, D: 41.87.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688392",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688392, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: (52.18, 50.78, 49.39), B: (67.83, 55.86, 43.89), C: (46.96, 50.78, 54.59), D: (57.39, 50.78, 44.18).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688393",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688393, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 35.72, 31.21, 26.70, B: 33.82, 30.31, 26.80, C: 32.15, 29.03, 25.91, D: 37.20, 32.10, 26.90.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688395",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688395 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: -0.15, B: -0.11, C: -0.13, D: -0.17.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688396",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688396 on May 30? A: 0.75, B: 0.65, C: 0.95, D: 0.81.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688398",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688398 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: (19.8, 16.62, 13.44), B: (22.74, 18.28, 14.78), C: (16.83, 14.96, 13.00), D: (25.74, 21.61, 17.48).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688399",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688399 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 1.35, B: 1.69, C: 2.03, D: 1.01.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688400",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688400 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: -0.35, B: -0.55, C: -0.45, D: -0.65.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688401",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688401? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 33.2, B: 49.8, C: 52.1, D: 41.6.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688403",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688403, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.27, B: 0.22, C: 0.33, D: 0.18.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688408",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688408, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 51.2, 47.3, 43.4, B: 52.3, 46.72, 41.14, C: 54.1, 45.9, 39.3, D: 50.1, 48.5, 42.7.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688409",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688409 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 71.37, 65.97, 82.16, B: 78.37, 73.47, 89.66, C: 74.87, 69.47, 85.66, D: 77.87, 66.47, 82.66.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688410",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688410 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.06, B: 0.12, C: 0.10, D: 0.08.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688411",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 38.0, B: 42.0, C: 32.0, D: 46.0.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688416",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688416 from the following options. A: 42.15, B: 46.31, C: 50.47, D: 39.82.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688418",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688418 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 32.16, B: 36.16, C: 34.16, D: 38.16.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688419",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688419, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 37.56, 35.76, 33.96, B: 34.26, 33.62, 32.98, C: 38.32, 35.76, 33.20, D: 35.76, 34.69, 33.62.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688420",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688420, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 23.17, 22.27, 21.37, B: 20.17, 22.27, 24.37, C: 25.17, 22.27, 20.37, D: 23.17, 25.27, 21.37.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688425",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688425, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 4.12, 3.98, 3.84, B: 4.04, 3.97, 3.89, C: 4.35, 4.02, 3.69, D: 3.73, 3.97, 4.21.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688426",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688426? Please select from the following options: A: 51.65, 40.04, 74.89, B: 91.65, 80.04, 114.89, C: 71.65, 60.04, 94.89, D: 31.65, 20.04, 54.89.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688428",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688428? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 1.02, B: 1.53, C: 0.95, D: 1.27.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688429",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688429. Its recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.42, B: 0.35, C: 0.52, D: 0.28.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688432",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688432 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 11.6, 10.9, B: 11.39, 11.12, 10.86, C: 10.7, 10.4, 10.1, D: 13.2, 12.5, 11.8.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688433",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688433 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: -0.75, B: -0.45, C: -0.58, D: -0.65.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688435",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688435 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: -0.01, B: -0.05, C: -0.07, D: -0.03.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688439",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688439 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please choose from the following options: A: 18.27, 13.19, 28.43, B: 23.75, 17.15, 36.96, C: 12.79, 9.23, 20.00, D: 26.00, 18.00, 39.00.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688443",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688443 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: 0.15, B: 0.25, C: 0.35, D: 0.45.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688448",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688448. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 4.19, B: 6.30, C: 5.24, D: 7.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688449",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688449, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 41.71, 40.12, 38.53, B: 45.11, 40.12, 35.12, C: 42.11, 40.12, 38.12, D: 43.11, 40.12, 37.12.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688450",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688450, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.03, B: 0.04, C: 0.02, D: 0.01.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688455",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 688455?  A: 0.98, B: 1.46, C: 1.87, D: 2.12.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688456",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688456 from the following options. A: -0.05, B: -0.03, C: -0.04, D: -0.06.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688458",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688458 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 22.1, 33.4, 65.7, C: 39.8, 38.6, 29.4, D: 32.82, 33.46, 31.53.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688459",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688459 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 43.16, 35.13, 59.22, B: 30.21, 24.59, 41.45, C: 56.10, 49.68, 76.95, D: 28.95, 21.08, 37.87.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688466",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688466 on May 30 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.39, B: 0.49, C: 0.59, D: 0.69.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688468",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688468 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.02, B: -0.01, C: 0.01, D: 0.03.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688469",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688469, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 5.42, 4.8, 4.18, B: 4.44, 4.8, 5.16, C: 4.67, 4.8, 4.93, D: 4.93, 4.8, 4.67.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688472",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688472 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 17.14, 21.94, 7.55, B: 12.00, 15.36, 5.29, C: 22.28, 28.52, 9.82, D: 10.58, 17.55, 6.04.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688475",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688475 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 15.23, 14.12, 18.91, B: 17.08, 15.76, 19.73, C: 19.25, 17.82, 22.11, D: 13.46, 12.54, 16.13.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688478",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 688478 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 25.03, B: 35.03, C: 30.03, D: 40.03.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688479",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688479 from the following options. A: 42.36, B: 58.72, C: 61.54, D: 50.45.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688480",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688480 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688480 on May 30? A: 1.31, B: 1.12, C: 1.57, D: 0.98.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688484",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688484, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 45.23, B: 49.72, C: 55.31, D: 62.14.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688485",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 688485 was the value of which of the following options. A: 50.22, B: 57.68, C: 53.44, D: 49.87.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688486",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688486 on May 30? A: 20.12, B: 27.56, C: 32.48, D: 24.24.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688488",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688488 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.91, 11.72, 10.52, B: 10.23, 9.37, 8.41, C: 15.68, 13.47, 11.26, D: 14.12, 12.89, 11.65.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688489",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688489 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 60.02, B: 64.02, C: 68.02, D: 72.02.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688496",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688496. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 48.7, B: 56.9, C: 53.3, D: 61.5.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688498",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688498 from the following options. A: 42.33, B: 48.76, C: 51.21, D: 45.94.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688499",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688499’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 29.18, 27.97, 26.76, B: 25.89, 26.15, 27.03, C: 32.46, 28.97, 25.12, D: 27.64, 29.33, 28.15.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688500",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688500 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? A: -0.27, B: -0.34, C: -0.41, D: -0.19.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688501",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 688501, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 34.22, 30.65, 27.08, B: 29.13, 27.16, 25.19, C: 30.65, 28.71, 26.76, D: 32.32, 29.67, 27.02.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688502",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688502 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 9.7, B: 11.5, C: 12.3, D: 10.9.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688503",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688503 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688503 on May 30? A: -0.15, B: -0.18, C: -0.12, D: -0.20.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688505",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688505, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 72.12, B: 78.12, C: 84.12, D: 90.12.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688506",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688506 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 37.23, 28.90, 53.91, B: 104.26, 80.92, 150.95, C: 74.47, 57.80, 107.82, D: 52.13, 40.46, 75.47.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688507",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688507, its stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 30.21, B: 42.87, C: 28.93, D: 35.69.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688508",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688508 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688508 on May 30? A: -0.89, B: -1.07, C: -0.71, D: -1.25.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688509",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688509 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.09, B: 0.11, C: 0.13, D: 0.15.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688510",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688510 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.57, B: 0.85, C: 0.71, D: 0.93.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688511",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688511, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 18.97, 16.38, 13.79, B: 20.54, 16.12, 11.70, C: 17.42, 16.57, 15.71, D: 19.36, 16.27, 13.17.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688512",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688512? Please select from the following options: A: 29.47, 28.11, 32.2, B: 38.31, 36.54, 41.86, C: 20.63, 19.68, 22.54, D: 41.26, 39.35, 45.08.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688513",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688513? Please select from the following options: A: 68.99, 67.08, 79.82, B: 76.99, 72.08, 86.82, C: 83.99, 79.08, 93.82, D: 70.99, 65.08, 80.82.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688515",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688515, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 130.45, 97.98, 65.52, B: 118.84, 97.98, 77.12, C: 108.04, 97.98, 87.92, D: 97.24, 97.98, 98.72.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688516",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688516 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 25.12, 17.97, 48.41, B: 46.12, 34.97, 68.41, C: 30.12, 18.97, 52.41, D: 36.12, 24.97, 58.41.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688517",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688517 on May 30? A: 0.28, B: 0.23, C: 0.35, D: 0.19.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688518",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688518 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 10.72, 14.62, 3.95, B: 15.32, 20.88, 4.21, C: 19.92, 27.14, 5.47, D: 13.79, 18.79, 3.79.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688519",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688519 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 14.71, 15.13, 13.87, B: 27.33, 28.11, 25.77, C: 21.02, 21.62, 19.82, D: 27.33, 28.11, 25.77.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688520",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688520, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 41.06, 37.73, 34.4, B: 39.50, 36.80, 33.60, C: 43.20, 39.40, 35.60, D: 41.06, 37.73, 34.4.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688521",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688521, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 93.24, 86.49, 79.74, B: 121.21, 86.49, 51.84, C: 74.59, 86.49, 98.39, D: 90.39, 86.49, 82.64.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688522",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 688522 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.33, B: -0.44, C: -0.59, D: -0.27.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688523",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688523, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 23.76, 21.42, 19.08, B: 20.13, 18.93, 17.73, C: 21.42, 19.92, 18.42, D: 22.74, 20.91, 19.08.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688525",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688525 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 7.21, B: 9.35, C: 10.21, D: 8.67.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688526",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688526, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.15, B: -0.18, C: -0.12, D: -0.20.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688528",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688528, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 48.72, B: 54.88, C: 62.34, D: 50.21.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688529",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688529 from the following options. A: -0.19, B: -0.13, C: -0.16, D: -0.21.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688530",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688530. Its latest 14-day average true stock price volatility (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.35, B: 0.43, C: 0.31, D: 0.39.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688531",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688531 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688531 on May 30? A: 2.46, B: 2.95, C: 1.87, D: 3.69.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688533",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688533, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 25.97, 26.32, 26.67, B: 28.89, 26.32, 23.74, C: 31.45, 26.32, 21.19, D: 23.11, 26.32, 29.53.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688535",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688535 from the following options. A: 42.12, B: 47.89, C: 45.34, D: 49.67.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688536",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688536 is the value of which of the following options. A: -1.27, B: -2.17, C: -0.97, D: -1.67.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688538",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688538 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688538 on May 30? A: 51.85, B: 49.26, C: 57.39, D: 43.62.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688539",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688539 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 18.2, 25.7, 33.2, B: 27.43, 25.62, 23.82, C: 21.3, 24.9, 28.6, D: 32.6, 27.1, 21.5.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688543",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688543 from the following options. A: 1.25, B: 1.75, C: 1.56, D: 1.45.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688545",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688545 from the following options. A: -0.12, B: -0.18, C: -0.10, D: -0.15.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688548",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 688548, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 10.86, 10.24, 9.61, B: 12.13, 11.27, 10.40, C: 9.19, 8.71, 8.23, D: 14.12, 13.32, 12.52.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688549",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688549, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 7.11, 6.78, 7.44, B: 7.44, 7.11, 6.78, C: 6.78, 7.11, 7.44, D: 7.11, 7.44, 6.78.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688550",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688550 from the following options. A: 0.81, B: 1.23, C: 1.02, D: 0.67.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688551",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688551? Please select from the following options: A: 58.38, 57.29, 60.56, B: 78.38, 77.29, 80.56, C: 63.38, 62.29, 65.56, D: 68.38, 67.29, 70.56.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688552",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688552 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: (9.48, 17.19, -5.95), B: (12.32, 22.35, -7.73), C: (6.64, 12.03, -8.33), D: (15.17, 28.65, -10.71).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688553",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688553 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 100.93, 72.17, 81.75, B: 81.75, 72.17, 100.93, C: 61.31, 50.52, 70.65, D: 122.32, 86.60, 131.21.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688556",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688556, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.12, B: -0.27, C: -0.19, D: -0.33.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688557",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688557 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: 0.5, B: 0.7, C: 1.2, D: 0.9.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688558",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688558, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 25.69, 24.87, 24.06, B: 22.18, 24.87, 27.57, C: 28.26, 24.87, 21.50, D: 23.12, 24.87, 26.63.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688559",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688559 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 15.66, 20.66, 5.65, B: 12.66, 17.66, 2.65, C: 10.66, 15.66, 0.65, D: 14.66, 19.66, 4.65.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688560",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688560, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 14.28, 13.19, 12.10, B: 13.78, 12.69, 11.60, C: 13.28, 12.89, 12.49, D: 12.78, 12.39, 11.90.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688561",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688561 from the following options. A: 30.21, B: 36.87, C: 29.15, D: 34.41.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688562",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688562, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.55, B: 0.66, C: 0.44, D: 0.75.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688563",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688563, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 57.34, 54.19, 51.04, B: 56.24, 54.19, 52.14, C: 55.14, 54.19, 53.24, D: 58.34, 54.19, 50.04.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688565",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688565 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 10.41, 9.96, 9.51, B: 6.71, 6.36, 6.01, C: 8.01, 7.66, 7.3, D: 9.31, 8.86, 8.41.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688566",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688566 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 71.59, 68.57, 77.63, B: 73.59, 70.57, 79.63, C: 69.59, 67.57, 76.63, D: 72.59, 69.57, 78.63.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688567",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688567’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 13.64, 13.05, 12.46, B: 10.55, 12.12, 14.32, C: 15.89, 13.45, 11.23, D: 12.12, 13.78, 14.91.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688568",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688568? Please choose from the following options: A: 17.3, 15.8, 20.9, B: 20.42, 19.3, 22.67, C: 26.5, 25.1, 29.8, D: 14.3, 13.1, 17.6.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688569",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688569 on May 30? A: 0.25, B: 0.40, C: 0.33, D: 0.38.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688570",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688570 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 19.65, 25.24, 11.47, B: 38.35, 46.88, 21.31, C: 22.13, 30.05, 13.27, D: 29.5, 36.06, 16.39.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688571",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 688571? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: -0.05, B: -0.06, C: 0.05, D: -0.04.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688573",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 688573 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 42.35, B: 46.87, C: 51.45, D: 39.21.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688575",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688575, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 15.21, 14.98, 14.75, B: 13.81, 13.35, 12.89, C: 15.01, 14.69, 14.37, D: 16.21, 15.75, 15.29.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688576",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688576 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.95, B: 1.02, C: 1.25, D: 1.11.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688577",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688577 from the following options. A: 2.58, B: 2.32, C: 3.10, D: 2.85.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688578",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688578, its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 was the most recent value for which of the following options? A: 1.8, B: 2.4, C: 3.0, D: 1.2.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688579",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 688579, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 10.28, 9.57, 8.86, B: 11.35, 9.57, 7.79, C: 9.85, 9.57, 9.29, D: 9.29, 9.57, 9.85.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688580",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688580 is the value of which of the following options. A: -0.62, B: -1.02, C: -0.98, D: -0.82.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688581",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688581 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: (65.73, 61.86, 58.0), B: (59.16, 55.67, 50.2), C: (72.31, 68.05, 63.8), D: (62.15, 59.48, 56.7).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688582",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) for the stock 688582 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 0.25, B: 0.33, C: 0.41, D: 0.17.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688583",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the most recent share price of stock 688583 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 20.12, B: 24.67, C: 22.41, D: 26.89.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688584",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 688584, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 17.68, 17.35, 17.02, B: 18.92, 17.35, 15.78, C: 16.54, 17.35, 18.16, D: 17.35, 16.99, 16.62.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688585",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the recent stock price Bollinger Bands (BOLL) for stock 688585 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: (8.12, 7.58, 7.03), B: (10.56, 9.83, 9.10), C: (6.21, 5.97, 5.73), D: (11.38, 10.47, 9.56).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688586",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688586, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 11.23, 10.31, 9.42, B: 10.62, 10.11, 9.6, C: 12.03, 10.55, 8.92, D: 9.78, 9.85, 10.12.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688588",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688588 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 35.7, 21.5, 63.2, B: 50.1, 35.9, 80.3, C: 42.3, 28.21, 70.48, D: 30.6, 20.8, 55.7.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688589",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688589 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 28.45, B: 35.72, C: 33.14, D: 31.56.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688590",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688590, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.92, B: 0.75, C: 1.10, D: 0.60.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688591",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688591, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 40.18, 37.28, 34.37, B: 42.18, 37.28, 32.37, C: 44.18, 37.28, 30.37, D: 39.18, 37.28, 35.37.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688592",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688592 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of its stock price on May 30? A: 1.84, B: 2.24, C: 2.04, D: 1.64.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688593",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688593 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688593 on May 30? A: -0.21, B: -0.17, C: -0.23, D: -0.19.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688595",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688595 from the following options. A: 1.38, B: 1.12, C: 1.75, D: 0.95.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688596",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688596? Please select from the following options: A: 17.33, 14.28, 23.42, B: 24.76, 20.4, 33.46, C: 32.19, 26.52, 43.50, D: 15.85, 11.28, 20.14.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688597",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688597, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 11.5, 10.9, 10.3, B: 12.0, 11.0, 10.0, C: 11.43, 10.94, 10.45, D: 10.8, 10.5, 10.2.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688598",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688598, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.72, B: 0.98, C: 1.12, D: 0.88.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688599",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688599’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 14.4, 13.7, 13.0, B: 10.8, 12.4, 16.9, C: 17.3, 11.2, 10.1, D: 12.1, 14.5, 15.6.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688600",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688600? Please select from the following options: A: 49.15, 54.28, 39.88, B: 56.15, 61.28, 45.88, C: 63.15, 68.28, 52.88, D: 42.15, 48.28, 33.88.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688601",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688601 from the following options. A: 24.31, B: 28.97, C: 26.63, D: 31.25.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688602",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688602 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 63.97, 67.91, 56.09, B: 69.97, 73.91, 62.09, C: 64.97, 69.91, 58.09, D: 66.97, 70.91, 59.09.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688603",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688603 is the value of which of the following options. A: 28.12, B: 25.31, C: 33.74, D: 21.09.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688605",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) of stock 688605? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: -0.10, B: -0.08, C: -0.12, D: -0.06.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688606",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688606 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688606 on May 30? A: 0.7, B: 1.1, C: 0.9, D: 1.3.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688607",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688607 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 34.5, 67.8, 90.1, C: 60.2, 50.1, 20.3, D: 48.62, 57.93, 30.01.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688608",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688608 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688608 on May 30? A: -7.91, B: -9.49, C: -6.33, D: -12.86.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688609",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688609 on May 30? A: 0.29, B: 0.38, C: 0.47, D: 0.52.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688610",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688610, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 37.95, 35.65, 33.35, B: 36.43, 35.65, 34.86, C: 36.43, 35.65, 34.86, D: 34.86, 35.65, 36.43.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688611",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688611 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 1.06, B: 1.25, C: 1.45, D: 1.32.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688612",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688612 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 41.18, B: 38.76, C: 49.42, D: 34.32.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688613",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688613 on May 30? A: 72.12, B: 78.12, C: 84.12, D: 69.12.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688615",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688615? Please choose from the following options: A: 10.2, 13.5, 17.8, B: 18.9, 17.3, 15.2, C: 15.67, 16.19, 14.61, D: 13.4, 15.8, 16.7.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688616",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688616 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688616 on May 30? A: 0.21, B: 0.32, C: 0.18, D: 0.26.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688617",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688617 on May 30 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 12.79, B: 10.23, C: 15.35, D: 9.67.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688618",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688618 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 21.98, 21.23, 20.48, B: 22.11, 21.37, 20.63, C: 23.77, 22.63, 21.49, D: 20.45, 19.82, 19.19.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688619",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688619 on May 30 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.24, B: 0.36, C: 0.3, D: 0.21.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688620",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688620 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 13.5, 12.8, 12.1, B: 11.5, 10.9, 10.3, C: 14.2, 13.6, 13.0, D: 12.79, 11.97, 11.15.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688621",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688621? Please select from the following options: A: 76.04, 73.77, 80.59, B: 63.23, 61.22, 64.47, C: 98.85, 95.90, 104.77, D: 53.23, 51.64, 56.42.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688622",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688622? Please select from the following options: A: 55.12, 48.99, 79.81, B: 63.72, 51.33, 88.51, C: 71.32, 59.66, 95.72, D: 58.12, 45.77, 81.43.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688623",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688623, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 67.9, 61.8, 55.7, B: 62.4, 61.8, 61.2, C: 64.3, 61.8, 59.3, D: 61.5, 61.8, 62.1.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688625",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688625 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 55.19, 49.84, 44.49, C: 47.19, 43.84, 40.49, D: 50.19, 46.84, 43.49.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688626",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688626 is the value of which of the following options. A: 45.71, B: 42.33, C: 54.85, D: 39.12.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688627",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688627? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 62.58, B: 68.58, C: 74.58, D: 59.58.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688628",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of the recent stock price of stock 688628, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 37.19, 34.80, 32.41, B: 39.60, 35.20, 30.80, C: 36.75, 34.80, 32.85, D: 35.10, 33.20, 31.30.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688629",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688629 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: -1.02, B: -1.34, C: -0.98, D: -1.16.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688630",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688630 on May 30? A: 2.83, B: 3.11, C: 2.37, D: 4.25.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688631",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Suppose you are analyzing the market data of stock 688631. Its most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 52.3, B: 58.7, C: 64.9, D: 49.1.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688633",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688633, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 31.09, 28.58, 26.07, B: 32.09, 27.58, 25.07, C: 30.09, 28.58, 27.07, D: 29.09, 28.58, 28.07.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688636",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688636 is the value of which of the following options. A: 38.50, B: 45.10, C: 39.75, D: 42.05.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688638",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688638, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 53.52, B: 47.25, C: 65.13, D: 39.87.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688639",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688639 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: 0.32, B: 0.42, C: 0.52, D: 0.62.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688646",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of stock 688646 is the value of which of the following options. A: 37.5, B: 45.6, C: 41.25, D: 33.9.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688648",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688648 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: 4.21, B: 6.82, C: 3.98, D: 5.68.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688651",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688651 on May 30? A: 1.53, B: 1.38, C: 1.72, D: 1.92.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688652",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688652 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 60.89, 56.55, 52.22, C: 45.6, 60.89, 78.9, D: 52.22, 56.55, 60.89.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688653",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688653 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.03, B: 0.05, C: 0.04, D: 0.06.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688655",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688655 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: -0.02, B: 0.03, C: -0.06, D: -0.04.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688656",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688656 from the following options. A: 74.84, B: 70.32, C: 89.81, D: 62.15.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688657",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688657, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 31.25, B: 33.13, C: 35.47, D: 29.82.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688658",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688658, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 15.23, 14.76, 13.95, B: 17.48, 14.95, 12.03, C: 16.52, 14.8, 13.07, D: 18.21, 15.6, 12.34.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688659",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688659 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: -0.01, B: 0.03, C: -0.04, D: -0.02.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688660",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688660 on May 30? A: 0.37, B: 0.31, C: 0.45, D: 0.29.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688661",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688661 on May 30? A: 1.42, B: 1.71, C: 2.05, D: 1.12.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688662",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the recent stock price of stock 688662 from the following options. A: 17.25, B: 21.12, C: 19.08, D: 23.56.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688663",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688663 is the value of which of the following options. A: 0.25, B: 0.45, C: 0.15, D: 0.38.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688665",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688665, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 47.71, B: 43.94, C: 55.12, D: 39.86.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688667",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688667? Please choose from the following options: A: 30.5, 31.2, 32.9, B: 43.63, 42.97, 44.94, C: 55.2, 54.7, 56.1, D: 28.9, 29.6, 31.3.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688668",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688668? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 1.32, B: 1.78, C: 1.59, D: 1.94.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688669",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688669, its most recent stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: -0.11, B: -0.07, C: -0.13, D: -0.09.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688670",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688670 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 73.5, 73.23, 74.06, B: 61.9, 60.63, 62.76, C: 94.5, 94.92, 96.28, D: 58.8, 58.58, 59.25.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688671",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, which of the following options best matches the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688671 on May 30? A: 45.32, B: 49.84, C: 54.36, D: 62.10.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688676",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688676? Please select from the following options: A: 14.93, 15.14, 14.53, B: 25.88, 26.23, 25.18, C: 19.91, 20.18, 19.37, D: 28.87, 29.25, 28.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688677",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688677 on May 30 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 1.12, B: 1.68, C: 0.97, D: 1.39.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688678",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 688678 is the value of which of the following options. A: 22.53, B: 25.00, C: 18.00, D: 30.00.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688679",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688679 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 15.35, 11.24, 7.13, B: 18.35, 14.24, 10.13, C: 21.35, 17.24, 13.13, D: 12.35, 8.24, 4.13.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688680",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688680 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 14.94, 23.75, -5.38, B: 27.74, 44.11, -1.29, C: 21.34, 33.93, -3.84, D: 29.88, 47.50, -5.38.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688681",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688681, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 14.97, 13.68, 12.39, B: 13.87, 13.38, 12.89, C: 12.17, 13.48, 14.79, D: 13.47, 13.08, 12.69.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688682",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688682 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 48.87, B: 41.54, C: 62.19, D: 58.62.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688683",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688683 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? A: -0.45, B: -0.56, C: -0.70, D: -0.35.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688685",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688685 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 26.80, 18.86, 50.79, B: 49.78, 35.02, 79.58, C: 38.29, 26.94, 60.99, D: 53.61, 37.72, 85.39.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688686",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688686, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 97.56, 88.04, 81.32, B: 93.06, 88.04, 83.03, C: 90.32, 88.04, 85.76, D: 93.06, 88.04, 83.03.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688687",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of the stock price of stock 688687 on May 30 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? A: 62.89, B: 58.31, C: 75.47, D: 49.12.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688689",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688689 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: -0.15, B: -0.26, C: -0.38, D: -0.47.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688690",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688690 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 15.3, 21.6, 27.9, B: 25.7, 20.4, 15.1, C: 22.9, 21.55, 20.21, D: 20.8, 21.2, 21.6.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688691",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688691? Please choose from the following options: A: 15.37, 13.82, 19.65, B: 28.55, 23.17, 32.91, C: 18.23, 16.54, 23.78, D: 21.96, 19.74, 26.41.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688692",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688692, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 243.94, 222.62, 201.29, B: 219.55, 222.62, 225.70, C: 268.33, 222.62, 176.91, D: 243.94, 222.62, 201.29.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688693",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688693 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: 0.15, B: 0.0, C: -0.25, D: 0.3",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688695",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688695 on May 30 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.62, B: 0.85, C: 0.78, D: 0.93.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688696",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688696? Please select from the following options: A: 21.83, 27.52, 16.24, B: 38.69, 41.98, 31.89, C: 26.78, 35.24, 21.37, D: 29.76, 32.32, 24.64.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688697",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688697 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price Moving Average Convergence/Divergence Index (MACD) value on May 30? A: -0.13, B: -0.15, C: -0.10, D: -0.17.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688698",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688698 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 52.08, 48.41, 44.74, C: 67.70, 52.95, 39.17, D: 36.46, 43.57, 51.86.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688699",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688699 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.18, B: 0.34, C: 0.26, D: 0.42.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688700",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688700, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 39.18, 35.62, 32.06, B: 36.28, 34.54, 32.80, C: 34.96, 33.94, 32.92, D: 35.62, 33.94, 32.26.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688701",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688701? Please select from the following options: A: 34.96, 46.36, 12.16, B: 24.47, 32.45, 8.51, C: 45.45, 59.27, 15.81, D: 17.48, 23.18, 6.08.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688702",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the most recent share price of stock 688702 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 1.5, B: 1.9, C: 2.3, D: 1.1.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688707",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688707? Please choose from the following options: A: 40.25, 35.12, 50.36, B: 74.75, 66.94, 90.68, C: 57.5, 51.34, 69.84, D: 39.25, 45.12, 80.36.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688708",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyzing the recent trend of stock 688708 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), calculate the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) of its stock price on May 30? A: 68.97, B: 75.97, C: 65.97, D: 71.97.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688710",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688710 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate the 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of its stock price on May 30? A: 0.72, B: 0.88, C: 1.05, D: 1.22.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688711",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688711, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 50.21, B: 48.97, C: 53.43, D: 57.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688716",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true range (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688716 from the following options. A: 1.53, B: 2.10, C: 1.72, D: 1.91.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688717",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Between March 4 and May 30, 2025, the most recent stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of stock 688717 is the value of which of the following options. A: -0.47, B: -0.65, C: -0.32, D: -0.78.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688718",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please calculate the 14-day average true range (ATR14) value of the stock price of stock 688718 on May 30 and choose one of the correct options below. A: 0.25, B: 0.31, C: 0.37, D: 0.43.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688719",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688719 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day relative strength index (RSI12) value of the stock price of stock 688719 on May 30? A: 55.05, B: 65.05, C: 61.05, D: 50.05.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688720",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688720 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 25.4, 50.2, 65.8, C: 30.1, 42.7, 54.3, D: 42.87, 40.61, 38.36.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688721",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688721, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: (46.72, 43.18, 39.63), B: (49.52, 45.68, 41.23), C: (43.92, 40.58, 37.23), D: (50.23, 45.18, 40.32).",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688722",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688722, its most recent stock price 14-day average true range (ATR14) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 0.89, B: 0.99, C: 1.19, D: 1.39.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688726",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688726? Please select from the following options: A: 10.63, 15.41, 4.06, B: 21.63, 26.41, 10.06, C: 16.63, 21.41, 7.06, D: 13.63, 18.41, 5.06.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688728",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "From March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688728? Please select from the following options: A: 102.3, 95.6, 88.9, B: 75.3, 70.2, 110.4, C: 120.5, 115.7, 98.6, D: 89.07, 83.34, 100.54.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688733",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688733 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 53.83, 53.67, 54.14, B: 43.23, 42.17, 45.24, C: 69.98, 68.77, 70.38, D: 38.12, 37.99, 39.01.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688737",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "According to the historical market data of stock 688737 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price of stock 688737 on May 30? A: -0.83, B: -0.69, C: -0.55, D: -0.92.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688739",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688739 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 12.3, 45.6, 78.9, B: 55.73, 51.96, 63.25, C: 65.73, 61.96, 73.25, D: 85.73, 71.96, 93.25.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688750",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688750 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select from the following options: A: 36.30, 32.15, 54.60, B: 67.42, 59.71, 82.84, C: 46.67, 41.34, 57.35, D: 51.86, 45.93, 63.72.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688758",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688758 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 27.73, 32.09, 19.02, B: 20.34, 24.37, 13.85, C: 37.24, 42.76, 25.87, D: 19.41, 28.68, 15.72.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688766",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value in the recent stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) of stock 688766? Please select from the following options: A: 10.23, 11.02, 9.56, B: 9.84, 10.09, 9.34, C: 12.56, 13.21, 11.02, D: 7.63, 8.07, 6.98.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688767",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Through careful analysis of the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, among the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) values ​​of stock 688767, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 45.1, 42.3, 39.5, B: 47.8, 43.5, 39.2, C: 46.59, 43.1, 39.61, D: 44.2, 41.7, 39.1.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688768",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688768, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 51.32, 49.37, 47.42, B: 56.12, 49.37, 42.62, C: 57.23, 49.37, 41.51, D: 54.66, 49.37, 44.08.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688772",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) for the most recent share price of stock 688772 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 46.26, B: 43.14, C: 52.79, D: 38.91.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688776",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Analyze the recent trend of stock 688776 (from March 4 to May 30, 2025), and calculate its stock price moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) on May 30? A: 1.22, B: 1.58, C: 1.92, D: 2.34.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688777",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the most recent moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) for stock 688777 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: -0.18, B: -0.32, C: -0.24, D: -0.29.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688778",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Please calculate the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) value of stock price 688778 on May 30 based on the market performance from March 4 to May 30, 2025 and choose one of the correct options below. A: -0.68, B: -1.02, C: -0.98, D: -0.86.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688779",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of the most recent stock price for stock 688779 from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 4.97, 4.85, 4.74, B: 5.46, 4.37, 4.27, C: 4.22, 5.13, 5.01, D: 6.13, 3.98, 3.62.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688786",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By carefully analyzing the stock data provided from March 4 to May 30, 2025, please select the correct value of the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of stock 688786 from the following options. A: 0.65, B: 0.72, C: 0.85, D: 0.58.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688787",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the Bollinger Bands (BOLL) of stock 688787’s most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Please select the corresponding value combination: A: 110.64, 105.49, 100.34, B: 90.53, 85.38, 80.23, C: 100.59, 95.44, 90.29, D: 120.71, 115.56, 110.41.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688788",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Can you calculate the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of the stock's most recent stock price from March 4 to May 30, 2025? Choose the correct option from the following options. A: 42.18, B: 63.27, C: 39.56, D: 52.72.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688789",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "What is the moving average convergence/divergence indicator (MACD) of the stock price of stock 688789 on May 30 between March 4 and May 30, 2025? A: 2.0, B: 1.5, C: 2.5, D: 3.0.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688793",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Referring to the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the recent 14-day average true volatility (ATR14) of the stock price of stock 688793? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 1.59, B: 1.99, C: 2.39, D: 2.79.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688798",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688798 from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what are the K value, D value and J value of its stock price stochastic indicator (KDJ) value on May 30? Please choose: A: 10.9, 8.85, 14.98, B: 13.9, 11.85, 17.98, C: 11.9, 9.85, 15.98, D: 14.9, 12.85, 18.98.",
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": "688799",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "During the period from March 4 to May 30, 2025, in the recent stock price Bollinger Band (BOLL) of stock 688799, the values ​​of the upper track, middle track and lower track are in order? Please choose: A: 31.56, 24.33, 17.10, B: 47.01, 35.74, 24.47, C: 38.61, 31.87, 25.13, D: 41.73, 33.14, 24.54.",
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": "688800",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "By looking at the performance of stock 688800 between March 4 and May 30, 2025, what was its stock price's 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) value on May 30? A: 39.3, B: 42.1, C: 35.7, D: 51.2.",
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": "688819",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "For stock 688819, its most recent stock price 12-day relative strength indicator (RSI12) from March 4 to May 30, 2025 is the value of which of the following options? A: 35.01, B: 38.01, C: 41.01, D: 44.01.",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": "688981",
    "type": "Multiple choice questions",
    "question": "Based on the data from March 4 to May 30, 2025, what is the 12-day Relative Strength Index (RSI12) of stock 688981? Please select the correct option from the options below. A: 27.68, B: 35.42, C: 30.75, D: 38.12.",
    "answer": "C"
  }
]